Chapter 1656: Fang Yuan Was Saved

At this depth, the sea was entirely pitch black.

But Fang Yuan's vision was dark green.

"Alright, this new Gu that I exchanged for is quite useful, with it, I can barely see in the deep sea." Fang Yuan was quite happy.

The deep sea was complex, one could not shine light here carelessly, or predators might be lured to oneself unknowingly.

In this dark green area, there were some deep black patches.

They were black oil of course.

The black oil tangled and weaved together like huge pythons. They were almost still, but the visual impact was huge.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, the gills on his face moved as they took in oxygen from seawater, allowing him to breathe underwater.

Calming down, he carefully approached the black oil. He stretched out his arms and stopped when he was several meters away from the black oil.

Next, he activated his Gu worm. A bright blue light slowly gathered in his palms, the two blue lights formed into beams of light that shined into the black oil. Droplets and lumps of black oil flowed along the blue light beams and slowly gathered into Fang Yuan's palms.

Fang Yuan's palms were like two bottomless holes sucking in black oil.

Time passed, but Fang Yuan continued to keep his alertness up.

He not only maintained his investigative methods on the surroundings, he also paid attention to the primeval essence storage in his aperture.

Because he used multiple Gu worms at once, Fang Yuan's primeval essence expenditure was not low. After a while, he reached a critical level.

"It is time to stop and return to the sea surface. Sigh, my aptitude is too low, if I had A grade aptitude, I would be able to last much longer!"

Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, at the same time, he stopped using his Gu worms, preparing to leave.

But in the process of leaving, an accident happened.

Suddenly, a huge force emerged in the peaceful sea, sending Fang Yuan flying.

"Oh no, an impact current!"

Fang Yuan's heart shook, he wanted to use Gu worms to escape.

These impact currents seemed like normal seawater, but when lifeforms entered them, they would emit a strong pushing force.

Bam bam bam!

In the process of escaping, Fang Yuan met with several impact currents, his bones were fractured and blood oozed out of his nose and mouth.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his eyes were wide opened and bloodshot, he tried to find a way to escape this predicament.

But he was not in the best condition, he had used a lot of his primeval essence, at the same time, the scale of these impact currents was huge and Fang Yuan lacked the method to deal with them, he could only dodge using his luck.

Soon, Fang Yuan expended all his primeval essence, an impact current from behind pushed him into the black oil.

"Am I going to die here?" Fang Yuan could not escape, he watched as the black oil stuck to him, before it spread and devoured him.

His primeval essence was used up, but thankfully, the gills were made from transformation path Gu worms, they could last for some time.

But this was truly his last few moments.

"This is the final moment of my life… sigh, I wanted to accumulate more black oil to gather wealth and exchange for a way to get rid of my black oil corrosion from the market… but now, I do not need to worry about this problem anymore… hehehe…"

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly, he fell into deep despair.

Eventually, the black oil completely covered him, his body was enveloped by the black oil.

"Am I going to die…"

Death was approaching, but Fang Yuan was completely peaceful in his heart.

Or rather, more accurately, he was indifferent.

Towards his death, he was indifferent about it.

"Alright… so be it if I die."

"After coming to this world, after so many years, I have been wandering from place to place, I am just too tired, too tired."

"Who can truly avoid death?"

"I might as well rest now."

Fang Yuan shut his eyes.

After some unknown period of time, he slowly regained his senses.

In a daze, he heard someone who was around him speak.

"Saintess, why did you save this mortal Gu Master? All these years, haven't the humans bullied us enough!"

"That's right, Saintess, this is clearly an oil collecting Gu Master, this sea area belongs to us mermen. He is a thief that steals our black oil, he is too shameless. We can let him die on his own."

At this time, a kind and refreshing voice resounded: "Since we met, how can we leave him in the lurch? I know he is a human and not a merman, but he is still a living being. Humans bully us, but a lone Gu Master like him is innocent. He is here to steal black oil, but how much can a person take? He took such risks to steal black oil, it shows how ostracized and troubled he is, why should we be stingy in helping him?"

"Saintess, you are just too kind, is that fine?"

"He is not anyone important, he is too lowly, there is no use in saving him!"

Fang Yuan tried his best and slowly managed to open his eyes.

His field of vision was still blur, he saw three vague figures.

White, blue, and red.

Human body, fish tails… from the blur figures, he could tell that they were three mermen.

Merman was a type of variant human, they could breathe underwater naturally and live. Mermen were attached to rivers and water bodies, they were most skilled at water path. Be they male or female, they were very beautiful and good looking.

"Thank… thank you… I will repay this kindness. May I know your names?" Fang Yuan spoke with difficulty, his hoarse voice became smoother as he talked.

But this was his current limit, his body was too weak, he could not muster any strength, these words were all that he could say.

"Hmph, we do not need your repayment. If not for Saintess, we would not save a dirty human like you."

"You do not need to know our names, but Saintess is named Xie Han Mo, you should remember it, etch this into your memory forever! You were incredibly lucky to have been saved by Saintess."

"Alright, you two, enough." The white figure sighed in a gentle voice, she said to Fang Yuan: "Even though you feel weak now, I have already healed your injuries. You were corroded by black oil earlier, I cannot heal this injury in one try, but I have left you a Gu worm, you can heal yourself with it."

Saying so, the white figure brought her two attendants and left, getting out of Fang Yuan's vision.

Fang Yuan wanted to speak, but he had exhausted his strength, he could not speak.

The extreme fatigue and weakness had his vision turn black again.

This was what happened in the five hundred years of his previous life.

Fang Yuan's gaze became clear, he returned from his recollection.

At this time, he had already led the fishing village's Gu Masters back to the island.

This was one of the old village head's houses, it was not dark.

At dusk, the lingering rays of light entered the room through the windows.

Outside the window, seagulls were flying around the beach, chirping loudly.

The mermaid who was saved was a young woman, she was still unconscious now. After Fang Yuan saved her, her pale face had started to become rosy again. She had thick eyelashes that casted shadows on her face.

Looking at this mermaid girl, Fang Yuan was absent-minded for a bit.

Looking at her carefully, she did not look like Xie Han Mo from Fang Yuan's memories, their appearances were very different, even though both of them were equally beautiful.

"They are only similar in disposition, and…"

And the biggest difference between this mermaid girl and Xie Han Mo was the color of their scales.

Mermen had human bodies and fish tails, their scales were of varying colors. Blue and red were common, while white and black were very rare.

White scaled mermen and mermaids could become saints and saintesses, while black scaled were treated as cursed and inauspicious, they would be killed the moment they were born, their parents were often the killers.

Xie Han Mo was a white scaled mermaid, she was the saintess of the mermen tribe. And this mermaid girl had blue scales, it was very common among mermen.

"Master Chu." At this time, the old village head and the middle aged Gu Master arrived at the door.

Fang Yuan nodded lightly as they came in.

After collecting black oil from the deep sea, be it the old village head or the middle aged Gu Master, they looked at Fang Yuan with utmost respect.

On one hand, Fang Yuan had unfathomable strength, and on the other hand, Fang Yuan gave them immense benefits. Water shell Gu was so useful, they had all experienced it on this trip.

And most importantly, Fang Yuan promised after returning that he was going to create a Gu worm for them, this Gu worm would be very useful to them.

"Master Chu, food has been prepared. Should you…" The old village head smiled.

"I will take care of her, don't worry master. When she wakes up, I will bring her to you." The middle aged Gu Master added.

Fang Yuan looked at the mermaid girl as he shook his head, he walked out of the house: "No need to see me, when she wakes up, get her to leave. Even though this is the territory of humans, and her action is akin to stealing, in my opinion, she has a hard life, give me some face and let her off."

"Master Chu, don't worry, we will not find trouble with her!"

"Yeah, all these years, there had been many mermen who came here to steal black oil. We have always tried to turn a blind eye to it, after all, we cannot finish extracting all the black oil under the sea, it is fine to share some." The old village head chuckled.

Fang Yuan nodded.

He had already gotten whatever information he needed from the old village head and this young mermaid girl through soul search.

There was something interesting.

In the outside world, merfolk had lower status than humans, both sides had huge conflicts and often fought. But here, merfolk and humans had better relationships, they interacted a lot and were at peace, there were even instances of marriage between them.

"It seems that this grotto-heaven is the paradise of humans and also merfolk."

Chapter 1657: Clues of Regret Gu

Inside the small house, there was a huge turbulence.

Dark red lights moved like waves, surging around Fang Yuan.

He was refining Gu.

His ten fingers were outstretched, his two hands were holding onto an eerie ball.

This ball was basin-sized, it was flowing on the surface, this was the essence of the black oil that Fang Yuan extracted.

The Gu refinement was already at the late stage, now was a crucial moment.

Fang Yuan willed as a crack opened in his immortal aperture's entrance, he took out a piece of shiny golden scale.

The scale flew into the black oil ball, causing a small explosion. In Fang Yuan's vision, he saw that the instant the black oil ball exploded, it expanded rapidly. At the same time, the golden light shined in the black oil ball, before condensing into a small dot.

Fang Yuan's ten fingers vibrated, the black oil ball floated into the air and started to revolve around itself.

During the process, the golden light continued to flicker.

A stench started to spread, these were the impurities that Fang Yuan expelled.

The stench was about to permeate out of the house when the immortal formation's light flickered, it was like a pot lid that was blue in color, it trapped the stench and prevented it from going out.

This stench was an immortal material containing food path, it was more terrifying than the black oil. If mortals came into contact with it, they would die.

Fang Yuan's Gu refinement was already immortal level, because it involved two immortal materials. One was the black oil, the other was the golden scale, it was pulled from a desolate beast golden dragonfish.

After a series of deductions, Fang Yuan found that the golden dragonfish and the black oil had a high level of compatibility.

One scale was not enough of course, Fang Yuan continued to toss in more golden scales.

The black oil ball slowly turned into a black-gold color, a lot of incomplete Gu worm silhouettes were seen in the ball.

Fang Yuan was trying to refine gather oil Gu.

This was specially made for the Gu Masters of the fishing village. Fang Yuan created the recipe himself, he also used the information in Shadow Sect's true inheritance and Lang Ya's true inheritance as reference.

Fang Yuan was truly trying to help the fishing village's oil collecting Gu Masters.

The reason?

It was because of the Merit Obelisk's mission.

What was merit?

Fang Yuan had been thinking about this problem from the start.

Were the missions on the Merit Obelisk so simple? The more Fang Yuan thought about it, the more he could feel a certain objective that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was trying to achieve.

Thus, helping these fishing village Gu Masters was meant to complete the mission and also to ascertain the conjecture that Fang Yuan had in his mind.

Fang Yuan did bad things without feeling any remorse. Similarly, he did good things without any changes in emotion.

To be honest, he had already become indifferent towards good deeds and bad deeds, he did not care about kindness or evil. In this world, there were only two things, those that benefited him and those that harmed him.

Right now, in the face of Paradise Earth's true inheritance, Fang Yuan would be willing to commit good deeds to ensure that he gains the maximum benefits.

Xia Lin slowly opened her eyes, she was awake.

"I… am not dead." After being in a daze momentarily, she reacted and her eyes started to shine.

"You are quite a lucky mermaid, if we found you any later, you would be dead. You would be corroded into black oil." The middle aged Gu Master saw that the mermaid woke up and walked into the room.

"My name is Xia Lin, did you save me?" The mermaid girl struggled to get up.

"Not me, it was Master Chu. You should really thank him, he was the one who healed your injuries." The middle aged Gu Master smiled as he spoke.

The mermaid girl inspected herself upon the reminder, she was extremely happy after that.

"Unbelievable!"

"I was corroded by the black oil and was heavily injured, even the greatest healing Gu Master in my tribe would not be able to save me, but I am completely healed now."

The middle aged Gu Master smiled arrogantly: "Of course! It was Master Chu who saved you after all!"

Saying so, the middle aged Gu Master thought of the scene when Fang Yuan saved her, he made all of the Gu Masters dazzled, most of them could not regain their senses after a long while.

"Master Chu saved my life and healed my injuries, how can I not repay this kindness?" The mermaid girl pursed her lips, she showed a firm expression: "Sir, please bring me to him, no matter the price, I must repay him."

"Alright, follow me." The middle aged Gu Master considered it for a moment before walking out of the room.

The mermaid girl Xia Lin forced herself up, she used a Gu worm to create a wave that carried her as she moved behind the middle aged Gu Master.

The two went into an estate, they got past the garden and arrived in front of Fang Yuan's house.

Rumble!

Suddenly, a black-golden light burst up into the sky from the small house.

"This is?"

"What happened?"

This phenomenon could be seen from all over the surroundings, many of the Gu Masters in the village were alerted as they came to observe.

"After dinner, Master Chu said that he was going to refine Gu. He locked himself in the room and instructed that no one was to disturb him." The old village head watched as he said: "This means that Master Chu's Gu refinement has already made progress."

"Master Chu's Gu refinement attainment is simple too profound, look at this scene, his Gu refinement must not be simple at all."

"Thanks for stating the obvious, Master Chu is extraordinary, how can he be simple?"

Xia Lin listened carefully.

These Gu Masters' conversation made her think of a supreme Gu Master expert. He must have white hair, a kind temperament, a cool and composed nature, great strength, and immense kindness and magnanimity.

As the dark gold light faded, a fragrance spread around the area, a huge hole was created at the roof of the small house.

A moment later, the door of the small house was pushed open, Fang Yuan walked out.

The fishing village's Gu Masters were all waiting in anticipation, the moment Fang Yuan came out, they bowed and greeted: "Master Chu!"

The mermaid girl Xia Lin looked at Fang Yuan curiously, it turned out that Master Chu was so young, she did not expect this.

She quickly knelt down: "Master Chu, you saved my life. I need to repay this kindness even if I have to break all the bones in my body!"

"No need, it was just a simple matter." Fang Yuan gave the mermaid girl a glance, she was not Xie Han Mo after all.

The deceased had already passed on, she was gone with the wind.

Days later, Fang Yuan returned to the Merit Obelisk.

"Oh? A new mission appeared!" Fang Yuan's gaze focused on the changes of the obelisk.

There were ten missions originally, now there were still ten, but most of the content had changed.

On another side of the Merit Obelisk, the rankings had changed too.

"I am third…" Fang Yuan soon found his ranking.

He was a little joyful, his guesses were already affirmed.

Looking at this from Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's perspective, merit was helping others, it was the action of good deeds. Fang Yuan saw his ranking and compared it with the others, he was sure: If he did this alone and collected the black oil personally, he would not place third.

Of course, helping these Gu Masters without putting in work was not possible too.

Thus, after refining gather oil Gu, he distributed them and went into the sea, collecting most of the black oil, leaving only a small amount for the fishing village's Gu Masters.

At the base of the Merit Obelisk, there were some scattered information path mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan picked them up and looked into them.

As he expected, these were left behind by Miao Ming Shen and others, they had recorded their findings.

Some found that humans and mermen lived together in peace with equal statuses.

Some chose difficult missions, even though they killed the desolate beast, many humans were implicated and lost their lives. When they returned, they found that they were at the bottom of the ranking.

Some understood that the meaning of the merit board was to do good deeds and help people, but they had only guessed it, the conjecture was not confirmed.

These Gu Immortals were chosen by Miao Ming Shen personally, they were not idiots.

Miao Ming Shen's discovery made Fang Yuan's eyes shine. He found that they were not the first group who came in here, there were Gu Immortals who entered before.

The most valuable information came from Feng Jiang.

He found that there was a forbidden area in this paradise, it was a sea area that people called Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea.

In legend, after Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable turned this grotto-heaven into a paradise, he suppressed a supreme demon in this sea area, he set up a super immortal formation to make him regret and repent.

Thus, this supreme demon's cries of regret could be heard in the sea area all the time.

Fang Yuan saw this information, the name of a Gu worm appeared in his mind — regret Gu!

Chapter 1658: Sea Market Gambling Den

Fang Yuan dropped an information path mortal Gu casually in front of rank eight Immortal Gu House Merit Obelisk.

Inside this Gu worm, Fang Yuan truthfully mentioned his experience of collecting black oil on the small island, as well as his experiment towards the merit board, if Gu Immortals arrived after him, they would see this intel as well.

There was no need to hide anything.

Firstly, they had their own guesses already, and secondly, it was easy to verify.

Fang Yuan might as well reveal this before they had experimented.

"Or rather… in plain words, this secret is not a secret, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable set up this true inheritance intentionally, he wants people to carry out acts of kindness."

This was the style of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

At this point, Fang Yuan was already fully convinced that this was Paradise Earth's true inheritance.

Gu Masters and Gu Immortals leave behind their respective inheritances, this was the greatest cultural trait of this world.

Every inheritance contained the person's markings, their style, or their important unfulfilled wishes.

For example, the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance was to take revenge on Gu Yue clan, even in death he wanted revenge. Thus, he left the video behind of the Gu Yue clan leader's defeat, he dug the underground cave and lured Fang Yuan to destroy the Gu Yue clan's spirit spring.

Or like Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this was the luck path true inheritance left by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, the goal was to help the entire Huang Jin bloodline to maintain their rule of the region, it was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's act of helping his descendants.

And Hei Fan's true inheritance, Hei Fan originally intended to pass everything to his granddaughter, but with twists of fate, his wishes were not fulfilled.

And Shadow Sect's true inheritance, if Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had not failed and was not captured by Heavenly Court, this true inheritance would not exist. But against his wishes, he was captured and Fang Yuan remained as his lingering hope in this desperate situation, to increase his strength, Spectral Soul formed Shadow Sect's true inheritance.

Every inheritance was different. Paradise Earth's true inheritance was different from the rest, it was filled with serenity, kindness, warmth, and light.

"If one day, I fail and die, having no hope left at all, I will leave my inheritance behind as well." Fang Yuan thought, even though he was an otherworldly demon, he had lived, struggled, and fought in this world for so long, he had already assimilated into it.

If he created a Fang Yuan true inheritance, he would encourage his inheritor to pursue eternal life as well.

Time passed quickly, seventy to eighty days went by.

During this period, Fang Yuan did many missions, his name started to move up the rankings on the merit board.

Swish swish swish…

Ebb and flow, the moist sea breeze landed on his face, Fang Yuan had arrived at the sea market.

He took a mission, it was to punish an unscrupulous merchant in this sea market.

Sea markets were very popular in Eastern Sea, they varied in sizes. being small, middle, large, and super sea markets. If one classified them according to time, there would be temporary and permanent sea markets.

The sea market was the place where cultivation resources were gathered and exchanged, in this paradise, there were sea markets as well.

This was a permanent sea market. Even though it was not open all year round, most of the time during the year, it was open.

The core of the sea market was an island. This island would be submerged for a period each year, that was the time the sea market closed. When the island emerges, the sea market would open.

Outside the island, there were many Gu houses in the shape of boats, their decks would be linked together to form this peripheral sea market.

Standing on the deck, Fang Yuan was surrounded by people.

There were human Gu Masters and also mermen.

There were many mermen, almost half of the population, this was very rare in the five regions. After all, humans were the dominant race, the other variant humans were all suppressed and had no living space, they had to live while keeping a low profile.

"Come, come, take a look, this is a superb crystal coral."

"There are three Gu house River Boats left, quickly buy them before they are sold out!"

"Purchasing grand soil, I will buy as many as you can sell…"

Shouting, clamoring, and bargaining noises were everywhere, they entered Fang Yuan's ears as he felt a sense of liveliness around him.

Large numbers of Gu Masters were displaying goods on the deck and creating their stalls, very few mortals were in charge of the businesses.

Fang Yuan went past Gu house after Gu house, going towards the core island at the center of the sea market.

He had already investigated, the mission was to punish an unscrupulous merchant, and he was on the island.

Of course, the mission was just a secondary objective, his true goal was to obtain intel.

This sea market was the closest to Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea, because there was a large number of Gu Masters and forces here, Fang Yuan had a high chance of getting useful information about regret Gu here.

Even though Fang Yuan had arrived here for a long time, he did not manage to enter Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea even once.

Inside this paradise, Gu Immortals did not have much freedom of mobility.

Like the first mission, he could only move around the island, there was a limit to the distance he could go. Every mission had this same restriction.

To return to the Merit Obelisk, all the Gu Immortal had to do was to recite 'return' three times in their mind.

From this, Fang Yuan could feel Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's powerful methods. Even with Fang Yuan's deep foundations and rank eight cultivation level, he could not unravel Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements, even though he had not stopped researching about this Merit Obelisk and the paradise.

Other than that, Gu Immortals were also restricted in communication. Firstly, they could not connect to treasure yellow heaven or the outside world. Secondly, they could not talk to each other. Precisely so, they had to use the crude method of leaving information path mortal Gu in front of the Merit Obelisk.

"This should be the place." A moment later, Fang Yuan stopped in his tracks.

He was at a gambling den, the door had three words written on it, Golden Jade House.

Golden Jade House was at the center of the island, it was a place of highest authority in this sea market. Ordinary Gu Masters could not enter, this place had strict security.

But how could mortal methods stop Fang Yuan?

"I should attempt the rock gambling too." Fang Yuan smiled to himself.

Punishing the unscrupulous merchant did not mean killing them, Fang Yuan was a merchant once, he had managed his own gambling den, he knew what the perfect way to make a gambling den merchant suffer was.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan stepped in.

Memories surfaced in his mind once again…

"Hahaha, who will gamble with me? Even the saintess is afraid, would you people dare?" A muscular merman shouted arrogantly.

Around him, there were many human Gu Masters and mermen. Most of the mermen were looking at him angrily, they could only grit their teeth.

"This Lu Da is too despicable, he dares to provoke Saintess openly in the sea market!"

"He does not have the guts, he is merely backed by Frost Tide tribe's leader."

"This cannot go on, it will sully Saintess' reputation, what do we do?"

The blue scaled and red scaled guards looked at each other in worry.

"So what?" Xie Han Mo smiled: "Let him be arrogant, no matter how much reputation I lose, he cannot shake my foundation. Since he is doing this to provoke me now, it means they are already panicking. We do not need to bother with this, we can win if we continue with our original plan."

Hearing this, the red scaled and blue scaled guards felt a sense of realization.

"Saintess is right, this Lu Da is just a dancing clown."

"But I feel really bad for letting Saintess suffer such a humiliation, can't any of our mermen stand up to face this Lu Da?"

Xie Han Mo smiled: "Lu Da is a rank four expert, he has reputation built over a decade in this sea market. I understand why no mermen are standing up for us, we need to understand their circumstances."

As she said that, a voice reverberated in the area: "I will gamble with you!"

Who was it?

Who dared to challenge Lu Da's authority?

Everyone turned to look, a human Gu Master walked out of the crowd.

Xie Han Mo was stunned as the two guards said: "It's the human Gu Master we saved!"

The merman Gu Master Lu Da was very surprised, he frowned as he looked at Fang Yuan, saying in a grim tone: "Human Gu Master, these are the affairs of mermen, you really want to interfere?"

"To speak the truth, your saintess saved my life before, I need to repay this debt." Fang Yuan had a firm attitude, he spoke to Lu Da without fear.

"This lad…"

"We did not waste our effort in saving him."

The two guards nodded.

Xie Han Mo sighed: "Let's go out, he is an outsider, we cannot let him sacrifice himself for nothing."

The two guards were surprised, they quickly stopped her: "Saintess, you analyzed the situation earlier, we cannot show up. Once we do, we will fall into their trap."

In the den, Lu Da had a sinister expression as he laughed from anger: "Good! Human Gu Master, since you want to die, don't blame me. I have already explained the rules of the gamble, let's go, I will let you choose first, we will see who finds better Gu worms!"

"You can choose first." Fang Yuan's gaze flickered with mysterious light as he smiled calmly.

The first round was quick, Fang Yuan won.

The second round took a lot longer, but Fang Yuan still won.

"Human Gu Master, I underestimated you. Tell me your name, you are qualified to take up space in my memory." Lu Da had a solemn expression, he looked at Fang Yuan in a different light.

"I am Gu Yue Fang Yuan, remember that. I owned gambling dens in the past." Fang Yuan suddenly raised his voice: "The final round, go ahead."

Lu Da chose a rock silently, next, he shattered all of the rocks in the den.

"You are breaking the rules!" Fang Yuan's expression changed.

Lu Da laughed: "Rules? I said that both sides cannot attack each other, but that does not include these rocks. I can confirm that this rock contains a Gu worm, while you are empty-handed, no matter what Gu worm I have, you are bound to lose. Lad, you dared to interfere with just rank three cultivation level, and especially in the sea market that I have managed for a decade. Hehehe, you can suicide, I won't have to dirty my hands."

Fang Yuan raised his fists, ready to fight a battle to the death.

"Hold up." Everyone moved aside to open up a pathway as Xie Han Mo walked into the den with a cold expression.

Chapter 1659: Xia Lin's Rock Gambling

Pushing aside his memories.

Fang Yuan walked into Golden Jade House.

This gambling den was quite high-end, there were tens of huge rocks in the hall, behind the hall were many rooms with an assortment of rock dissecting Gu worms for the customers to enjoy using. Of course, experienced rock dissecting Gu Masters were also ready on-site.

Whether these rocks contained Gu worms, Fang Yuan could easily find out.

He was a Gu Immortal, immortal investigative methods could find mortal Gu with ease. Similarly, even if the Gu worm inside was extremely weakened, he could heal them.

Even if they could not be healed, don't forget that Fang Yuan was a refinement path quasi-supreme, he could obtain basically all the mortal Gu that were currently here with great ease.

Of course, there existed such things as immortal rocks as well, or rather, immortal materials. After Immortal Gu seal themselves and hibernate, the corresponding dao marks' immortal material would form on their surface. Most immortal investigative methods would be ineffective against them.

Fang Yuan was about to use his methods to teach this unscrupulous merchant in Golden Jade House a lesson when suddenly, he heard some commotion behind the hall.

"You are dishonest!" Mermaid Xia Lin shouted with anger and shock.

"I'm dishonest? Hehe, how so? This is clearly recorded in the information path Gu worm, even though you returned a sum, a large portion has not been repaid." Standing before the mermaid was a merman, he was large like a bear, there was a scar on his face, giving him a sinister aura.

"You, you, you!" Xia Lin pointed at the merman with red eyes: "You guys are shameless, you changed the agreement details, our contract was ten percent interest, but you raised it to sixty percent!"

The scarred merman's face became solemn, he looked at Xia Lin with a vicious gaze: "Young lady, you cannot spread fake news like that! Are you trying to ruin our reputation, this is detrimental to our business, who would come to our shop after this? Can you bear the cost of our losses?"

"Screw you! Even if I die, I will expose this shop's evil deeds."

The scarred merman changed his tone as he said eerily: "Die? You are too naive, sometimes, being alive is worse than dying."

Light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, this was a familiar voice, he was reminded of the mermaid girl from a few months ago.

Why was she here?

Xia Lin's tears fell from her face.

Several months ago, her only family member, her grandfather, died.

Merman sea funerals were very expensive. In order to bury her grandfather, she had to borrow primeval stones. To repay the debt, she had to take a risk and collect black oil, almost dying in the Earth Trench as a result. Fortunately, she met Fang Yuan and was saved miraculously.

Xia Lin also obtained gather oil Gu from Fang Yuan, her efficiency in collecting oil increased, she quickly gathered a huge amount of primeval stones from selling oil.

She brought these primeval stones to Golden Jade House to repay the debt but this shop was too shameless, they actually changed her agreement terms.

Xia Lin had the urge to die.

Her only family was gone, she was all alone in this world, she was ostracized by her tribe since a young age, all these circumstances made her feel lost and dejected, the world had turned grey, she could not find any joy in living.

"What is so scary about death? I'll die and end it all!"

Thinking of this, Xia Lin took action with a yell.

Swoosh!

An explosion was heard as a torrent was shot out.

The scarred merman did not expect that in this situation, a rank two Gu Master would dare to attack him, a rank three, in his territory, the Golden Jade House.

The scarred merman was caught unprepared, he was washed away by the torrent, crashing into the wall as many decorations shattered.

The commotion was huge, the Gu Masters who were quietly choosing and dissecting rocks all came to watch.

A large number of eyes turned to look at Xia Lin and the scarred merman.

"What happened?"

"Hehe, what else could it be, this Golden Jade House must have tricked the innocent again."

"Quiet, this Golden Jade House's owner is the tyrant around here."

"I heard that Golden Jade House often acts as loan sharks and exploits low ranked Gu Masters."

"Let's not attract trouble, this is the problem of mermen, we humans have nothing to do with it."

At this time, the scarred merman stood up from the rubble: "You have such guts to attack me, I will make you wish you were dead!"

He walked towards Xia Lin, she was pale with fright, suppressed by his aura, but she gritted her teeth and did not step back.

The distance between the two shortened, when the scarred merman was about to attack, he heard a voice: "Wait!"

The scarred merman's actions stopped, he changed his expression of anger and ruthlessness as he lowered his head towards the person: "Shopkeeper, what brings you here?"

This was Golden Jade House's owner, a big bellied yellow scaled merman.

The yellow scaled merman frowned, he shouted at the scarred merman: "What are you doing? Are you trying to destroy my shop?"

"Shopkeeper, she…"

Before the scarred merman finished his words, he was interrupted.

"How many times have I told you, we need to act peacefully, peace brings fortune, do you understand?"

"Yes, yes." The scarred merman did not dare to retort, he nodded like an obedient child.

A chill emerged in Xia Lin's heart.

She had gone through lots of difficulty, being brought up by her grandfather, she had experienced the bright and dark sides of life.

"Someone who can make this scarred merman so respectful must be more terrifying!" Xia Lin knew this clearly, she looked at this yellow scaled merman, her alertness was raised to its limit.

The yellow scaled merman looked at Xia Lin for some time before speaking: "Little lady, don't worry, I am an understanding person. With me around, I will ensure that nobody attacks you. But I want you to be reasonable as well, your debt is in black and white, do you want to deny it?"

Hearing this, Xia Lin felt enraged: "You guys were shameless, you changed the terms on your own, from ten percent to sixty percent interest. I do not owe you anything, I already repaid my debt."

The yellow scaled merman smiled even brighter now: "Little lady, to think that your acting skills are so profound at such a young age. But it is no use! No matter how convincing you are, without evidence, you cannot prove anything, we have the agreement here, it is clearly stated, everyone can tell who is in the wrong."

"You, you, you!" Xia Lin pointed at the yellow scaled merman, unable to say anything from anger.

The yellow scaled merman laughed as he waved his hand: "Forget it, you are a young girl, I will not bully you, others might say that my Golden Jade House is bullying customers. How about this, repay half the debt and I will let you go without any other problems."

"I am already very sincere. If you return it now, you will only pay thirty percent interest, isn't that market rate? Tell me which moneylender isn't operating at this price? You said that we had a ten percent interest? Who would believe you? Try and find it outside, which shop would give that price?"

Xia Lin's chest was bobbing up and down, her eyes were reddened.

The market was thirty percent, that was precisely why she borrowed from Golden Jade House. But to think that it was a trap, she had gotten scammed.

Seeing that Xia Lin was silent, the yellow scaled merman took out an information path mortal Gu: "This is our loan agreement, if you return the money, I will return you this Gu now."

Xia Lin was stunned before sneering: "I do not have enough primeval stones."

The yellow scaled merman laughed as he clapped: "Don't worry, you can use Gu worms instead. I know you have a gather oil Gu, you can use it to repay your debt."

Xia Lin heard this and realized at once: "So that is your true goal, you want my gather oil Gu? Hmph, this is a rank five Gu, are you insane! Even if I die, you won't get this Gu."

The surrounding Gu Masters went into a commotion upon hearing this.

"Gather oil Gu? Did I hear wrongly?"

"That rumored rank five Gu that is the hot topic recently? I heard it has incredible efficiency in gathering black oil!"

"Not just incredible, it is superb. Even though gather oil Gu is rank five, it does not expend primeval essence but the Gu Master's bone marrow, even rank one Gu Masters can use it!"

"I heard that some people overused the gather oil Gu and killed themselves."

"Sigh, those people have no restraint. If they use bone path Gu worms with it, gather oil Gu is very safe!"

Clap clap clap.

The yellow scaled merman clapped: "Young lady, you are a smart girl, I am sure you know the logic that fortune attract wolves. How can a rank two Gu Master like you own a rank five Gu? Take it out, even if I let you off, others will still come after you, hand it over and live a stable life, isn't that better?"

"No! Even if I die, I will not hand it over to a scumbag like you." Xia Lin resisted with determination.

The yellow scaled merman felt a headache.

It was difficult to take someone else's Gu worm, she only needed one thought to self-detonate the Gu, by then, the yellow scaled merman's plan would be ruined.

The best situation was for Xia Lin to hand it over.

Otherwise, he could use theft path methods.

But theft path Gu Masters did not exist in this paradise.

And even if there were theft path Gu Masters, stealing a rank five Gu was too hard!

The yellow scaled merman was not flustered, he had already planned this and expected the situation. He could not force Xia Lin too harshly now, thus, he took a step back.

"How about this, I will give you a chance, but you must do the same. We can gamble."

"Gamble?"

"We will gamble rocks and see who excavates Gu, and if we both do, which one is better. We will decide the winner from two out of three victories."

Xia Lin smiled coldly: "You are unscrupulous and went back on your words, how can I trust you after you changed the terms earlier?"

The yellow scaled merman thought about it, he suddenly waved his hand as an information path mortal Gu flew to Xia Lin.

Xia Lin received it with deep shock.

The yellow scaled merman added: "I can make an oath to the Sea God."

Mermen were different from humans, they had their racial religion, they believed in the Sea God. Making an oath using the Sea God's name was a huge matter, it proved that he was very sincere.

Almost every merman's faith was in the Sea God.

The yellow scaled merman said again in a sincere way: "What are you hesitating for? Rock gambling depends on skill but also luck. I gave you a chance, don't go overboard, I will tell you the truth, this is your only way out today, you should seize the chance."

The yellow scaled merman used both the stick and the carrot, Xia Lin was greatly flustered.

While she hesitated, a voice suddenly said in her mind: "Don't be afraid, gamble with him, I am here!"

"Master Chu!" Instantly, Xia Lin almost screamed from joy.

Fang Yuan added: "But you must change the gambling terms because this is too mild, if you trust me, we will make this a huge gamble!"

"I trust you, Master Chu!" Xia Lin responded without any hesitation.

Her life was saved by Fang Yuan. If he wanted to harm her, there was no need to save her.

"My life was saved by Master Chu, if he wants to harm me, so be it, I will just return this life to him!"

Thinking like this, Xia Lin responded in her mind: "Master Chu, tell me what to do, I will follow your instructions."

Chapter 1660: Mastermind

Rock gambling was truly a matter of luck, nobody could deny it. Be they Gu Master or Gu Immortal.

But the yellow scaled merman was very confident in himself.

Because he was prepared.

All these years, he had gambled with the rocks in his own Golden Jade House. He had observed, analyzed, and chosen some rocks with great precision, he was very confident in this gamble.

These rocks naturally did not contain valuable things, otherwise, he would have taken them himself, he would not leave them in the shop.

He had to maintain his business.

Most of these rocks would have Gu worms, even though they were not valuable, they were a form of excitement for the customers. This was like fish bait, they would want to continue gambling and investing.

The yellow scaled merman knew the locations of where these rocks were placed, sometimes, he even showed off his rock gambling skills in front of customers, opening Gu worms and showing that he was a great expert in this rock gambling activity.

Now, the yellow scaled merman was using these rocks to gamble against Xia Lin, he was very confident in himself.

But in the first round, he tasted defeat.

Xia Lin opened a rank three Gu worm, it was superior to his.

This was a good start!

The surrounding Gu Masters were shocked.

The yellow scaled merman was also suspicious and uncertain, was this mermaid girl a hidden expert?

He had suggested a two out of three format earlier, but Xia Lin requested to change it to five contests, the bet was higher now, he staked the entire Golden Jade House. At the same time, if she lost once, she would have to hand over the gather oil Gu.

But now, Xia Lin won, not only did she keep gather oil Gu, she even won twenty percent of Golden Jade House.

"What a joke, I lost?!" The yellow scaled merman could not believe it.

He stared at the mermaid girl, his suspicions fading slowly.

The yellow scaled merman was very experienced, he could tell that Xia Lin was a newbie, her expression of joy after getting a Gu worm was not fake, she was genuine.

Furthermore, Xia Lin did not know how to dissect rocks. She had asked the rock dissecting Gu Master in Golden Jade House to open her rock.

"Damn it, she had some dog shit luck!"

"Thankfully, we changed the rules from three rounds to five rounds, I have a lot of chances left, I am not in a passive spot."

Thinking of this, the yellow scaled merman looked at the rock dissecting Gu Master behind Xia Lin with a subtle gaze.

The rock dissecting Gu Master nodded mildly.

The yellow scaled merman smiled to himself secretly, in this situation, no matter what rock Xia Lin got, even if there was a Gu, it would be destroyed, how could she possibly win against him!

The second round.

"I will choose first." Xia Lin said.

"Go ahead." The yellow scaled merman smiled and replied.

Xia Lin walked around for a while and was dazzled.

"I will choose this." Suddenly, she stopped as she pointed at a weird rock.

This rock was very strange, it had multiple holes and was distorted in shape, it was not very compact and felt like a pile of sand.

Normally speaking, such a sandy rock would not have any Gu worm.

Seeing Xia Lin's choice, the yellow scaled merman laughed.

He pretended to walk around, touching and knocking the rocks, after a while, he chose a huge rock and said: "This is my choice."

The rock dissection started.

The yellow scaled merman did it himself while Xia Lin asked the rock dissecting Gu Master.

This was an open gamble, they dissected the rocks in the hall. More and more spectators came, they talked among themselves as the newcomers learned of this gamble and gained interest, they chose to stay and watch.

For Gu Masters, this was a huge gamble.

One was the entire Golden Jade House, it had a lot of funds after years of operation.

The other was a superb rank five gather oil Gu.

The bet was almost equal on both sides, gather oil Gu was just too amazing, it generated immense profits by collecting black oil.

The yellow scaled merman chose a huge rock, he needed some time to dissect it.

For Xia Lin, it was very rapid. The sandy rock was just too rough and coarse.

Xia Lin's rock dissecting Gu Master was very casual in his actions, he had no pressure. If he destroyed the Gu worm in the process, the yellow scaled merman would be very happy after all.

But at this time, Xia Lin said: "Use the grey soil method."

The rock dissecting Gu Master stopped his action, he said: "Are you sure? This method has limited effect on sandy rocks."

"Yes." Xia Lin responded.

The rock dissecting Gu Master shook his head: "Little lady, I am not lying, I will not lie since I am the one dissecting this. Why don't you ask around, everyone knows that the grey soil method has little effect on sandy rocks."

"I do not need that, just do as you are told, this is in the agreement." Xia Lin insisted.

"Alright, alright." The rock dissecting Gu Master nodded.

Once he used the grey soil method, the sandy rock's dissection became painfully slow.

The rock dissecting Gu Master was very annoyed, earlier it was like he was using a knife to cut tofu, but now, he was stabbing it with a needle while expending even more primeval essence.

"Use the flame smoking method." A moment later, Xia Lin added.

The surrounding Gu Masters gasped, they wanted to stop her.

The rock dissecting Gu Master said as well: "The flame smoking method will penetrate the rock, if there is a Gu inside, it will die before it is excavated."

"Just do as you are told." Xia Lin said expressionlessly.

The surrounding Gu Masters sighed, someone said: "Is this girl really gambling? She cannot even be considered a newbie, she is just toying around!"

But Xia Lin had a firm expression that was somewhat relaxed.

The rock dissecting Gu Master shook his head: "Since you want that, let's do it, everyone can tell that I am not sabotaging you, this is your request."

"Use the dripping method."

"Blue mark method."

"Planting qi method."

Next, Xia Lin gave several precise instructions.

The sandy rock was already fist sized, but no Gu worms came out yet.

The rock dissecting Gu Master had an ugly expression, he felt that Xia Lin was purposely toying with him, she said those names that she knew randomly.

"Alright, give it to me, I will dissect it myself." Xia Lin added.

"What?" The rock dissecting Gu Master was stunned but quickly reacted as he let out a breath of air, passing the rock to Xia Lin.

Xia Lin bit her tongue and spat out blood at the rock, before using gather oil Gu to apply suction force on the rock.

Crack.

The rock cracked, a rank three Gu worm was exposed.

"There was a Gu?"

"What Gu is this? I have never seen it before."

"It is asleep, by the looks of it, it is complete and uninjured."

The surrounding Gu Masters went into a commotion.

The rock dissecting Gu Master was stunned completely, he looked at Xia Lin with a dumbfounded expression, thinking suspiciously: "Is this girl really tricking us all?"

The yellow scaled merman also stopped his dissection with a dark expression.

Even if he opened it, his rock only had a rank two Gu, but the other party had a living rank three Gu!

"There was a Gu! Master Chu was not wrong after all!" Xia Lin was overjoyed.

Among the crowd, Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

There was no Gu in this sandy rock, there was only a Gu material.

Fang Yuan instructed Xia Lin to indirectly manipulate this rock dissecting Gu Master and refine the Gu material. Eventually, when Xia Lin dripped her blood and used gather oil Gu, the final step was completed.

Normally, newly refined Gu worms would be active, but Fang Yuan used a unique Gu refinement method that made the Gu worm hibernate. This allowed him to trick everybody that was around, nobody saw through this or found any flaws.

Quasi-supreme refinement path attainment level, it was not a joke!

Everyone was not calm, they looked with Xia Lin with a different gaze now.

"Who sent you here?!" The yellow scaled merman shouted, his composure was gone.

He realized something wrong, thoughts surged in his mind.

He had offended many people over these years, he felt that Xia Lin was a bait, he had fallen into a trap. This rank five Gu was used to trap him, it was truly a huge gamble!

"Calm down, calm down."

"I cannot take any more risks, the other party came prepared."

The yellow scaled merman wiped off his cold sweat as he focused his gaze.

He had a trump card.

There was a special batch of rocks in this Golden Jade House.

These rocks were not natural, the yellow scaled merman had created them artificially.

He first made living or dead Gu worms look like they were in a hibernating state, he then added rock fragments around them and eventually created artificial 'rocks'.

Rocks that contained Gu worms often had some observable traits, making them different from ordinary rocks.

These kinds of rocks were not easy to find.

Sometimes, in order to resolve the lack of supply of gambling rocks, the yellow scaled merman would create fake rocks himself. Of course, not all of these rocks would contain Gu worms, some only had these observable traits.

The third round, defeat.

The fourth round, defeat again!

The Gu Masters watching this gasped, nobody had expected this to happen.

Everyone looked at Xia Lin with wariness and solemness.

The yellow scaled merman turned pale, he gritted his teeth, ruthless light flashed in his eyes, he was like a jackal forced to the end of a cliff.

"The final round, I cannot afford to lose! I need to use my strongest trump card."

The yellow scaled merman's trump card was naturally overpowering, he hid the carcass of a rank five Gu in a fake rock, according to the gambling rules, only a living rank five Gu could beat him.

Both sides chose their rocks and dissected them.

Snap.

Fang Yuan suddenly snapped his fingers, using a time path immortal killer move[1]!

The entire Golden Jade House and even the island became still, anything and everything became motionless.

Fang Yuan walked out of the crowd, coming in front of the yellow scaled merman who was focusing on the flame and dissecting his rock carefully.

Fang Yuan squeezed the rock lightly, he saw the carcass of a rank five Gu.

Next, he placed this carcass into Xia Lin's rock and returned to the crowd.

At the next moment, time resumed.

[1] ZA WARUDO Back

Chapter 1661: Repaying a Debt of Gratitude

The result of the fifth round made the yellow scaled merman dazed on the spot.

His eyes were about to pop out.

If he was not witnessing this personally, he would not believe it!

He remembered clearly that this was the Gu worm carcass that he had put in the fake rock, but why? Why!

Why was this Gu worm carcass not in his hands but in his opponent's hands?

The yellow scaled merman could not understand.

"Is this all an illusion?" He was going crazy, his pale face surged with redness.

He suddenly pointed at Xia Lin as he screamed in a shrill voice: "You cheated!"

The mermaid girl Xia Lin heard this and became enraged.

She was also kept in the dark, not knowing of Fang Yuan's methods, she shouted: "You lost fair and square, are you going to deny that in front of everyone?"

The yellow scaled merman looked at Xia Lin and the surrounding Gu Masters, his gaze became hollow as he muttered: "No, this is not real, everything is fake, this is an illusion."

He stumbled back and wanted to run away from this cruel reality.

Looking at his pitiful demeanor, the surrounding Gu Masters had complex expressions, they looked at Xia Lin with trepidation and wariness.

The yellow scaled merman was almost mentally broken by Fang Yuan!

Xia Lin pursued: "Let's transact, you did not win a single round, this Golden Jade House is mine."

The yellow scaled merman shuddered like he was shocked with lightning, he screamed in response: "No, this is mine, this is my foundation, I will not give it to anyone! Don't even think about it, you can have it over my dead body!!"

"Sir, we can force them to go down with us!" The scarred merman came up and said with a sinister expression.

The yellow scaled merman shook again.

He wanted to do that, but hearing these words, he realized something.

"No matter who it is, this mermaid girl is just a pawn. The other party could manipulate this situation remotely, setting up a trap against me that I could not deal with. How can I face someone of such a magnitude? If I fight now, wouldn't I be courting death?"

The yellow scaled merman did not want to give up his Golden Jade House, but compared to his life, the latter was more important.

The yellow scaled merman looked around him, instincts told him that the enemy was among this crowd.

He felt suspicious of everyone, but he could not confirm their identity.

"I admit my loss, I lose!" Suddenly, he stopped his methods as he sprawled on the ground like a dying fish, shouting loudly.

He prostrated on the ground, admitting: "No matter who you are, I admit my defeat, is that enough? You can do anything with me, but before that, may you please enlighten me, when did I offend you?"

Everyone went into a clamor.

The yellow scaled merman's actions were unexpected, some people snorted in disdain, some felt that he was able to put down his pride and was quite a formidable person.

An unscrupulous merchant that had been in power for decades was naturally not so simple.

Xia Lin was also dazed, at the same time, she felt deep admiration towards Master Chu.

She understood clearly that this was all due to Master Chu, without his guidance, Xia Lin would be in even deeper trouble than the yellow scaled merman. But looking at the prostrating yellow scaled merman, Xia Lin felt joyful and also relieved.

"It is time." Fang Yuan smiled, guiding Xia Lin.

Xia Lin spoke to the yellow scaled merman: "Do you know why you lost?"

Seeing her speak, the crowd went silent.

The yellow scaled merman raised his head, looking at Xia Lin: "I do not know, please enlighten me."

"Because someone wanted you to lose." Xia Lin stated an obvious fact.

The yellow scaled merman's heart jumped, he lowered his head: "I understand, I understand."

Xia Lin added: "Do you want this Golden Jade House back?"

"What?" The yellow scaled merman was stunned, what did she mean? Of course he wanted it back, but he did not know about the other party, what did they mean by that? Were they toying with him or had ulterior motives?"

Xia Lin continued: "I have a condition before I return it to you."

The yellow scaled merman started to kowtow: "Revered lady, please tell me."

Xia Lin looked at the yellow scaled merman as she said slowly: "The reason why you ended up like this was because of just desserts, you committed too many sins. From now on, you have to commit acts of kindness, do good deeds and turn over a new leaf, I will let you off and return this Golden Jade House. But remember, if you return to your old ways, we will take not just this Golden Jade House next time."

Once she said that, all the Gu Masters showed perplexed expressions.

After so much talk, Xia Lin and her backer actually had such intentions?

They were promoting kindness?

This was not a common thing.

The yellow scaled merman was also surprised but he did not dare to show anything on the surface, he quickly thanked her profusely: "I will change, I will definitely turn over a new leaf. Revered lady, you are the benefactor of my life, you changed my ways. You are like a saintess guiding people towards kindness and away from evil. I was wrong, I was really wrong, thank you, Saintess, for giving me this chance, from now on, I will be a good person and dedicate my life to doing good deeds!"

The yellow scaled merman lowered his head and apologized sincerely, he was like a pitiful child.

Xia Lin's face flushed: "I am not the saintess, I have no qualification to be one, don't spout nonsense. Remember your promise, we will be watching you. If we find out or anyone reports you in the future, you will regret it."

Saying so, Xia Lin turned around and left.

The surrounding Gu Masters left a path for her.

Xia Lin had just left the Golden Jade House when she suddenly vanished without a trace.

At the next moment, she appeared at the edge of the island through Fang Yuan's teleportation.

"It's safe here, you can go back now." Fang Yuan did not show up, he only transmitted his voice.

"Master Chu, you saved me again, how can I repay you?" Xia Lin called out in her mind: "Master Chu? Master Chu…"

"We will meet again if we are fated to." Fang Yuan said as he smiled, memories emerging in his mind again.

On the beach, Fang Yuan chased after Xie Han Mo and the rest who were leaving: "Please wait!"

Xie Han Mo and the rest stopped walking, while the two guards stared at Fang Yuan in annoyance.

"Lad, stop following us."

"If you want to repay the debt of gratitude, you should get away from us. Do you know that Saintess could have stayed hidden this time, but to save you, she showed up. Now, we failed to find any evidence and even made the other party alert."

"I know!" Fang Yuan was panting.

"You know nothing." The blue scaled guard rolled his eyes.

Fang Yuan chuckled, raising his head and looking at Xie Han Mo and the guards: "I was too rash, but after that, I understand now. You are the Merman Imperial Court's current generation saintess, you came here to find evidence of Frost Tide tribe's corruption. I can help you in this matter. Because I operated gambling dens before, I know about their workings. The main avenue for this Frost Tide tribe's money laundering has to be that gambling den earlier."

"Please give me a chance saintess, let me repay the debt of saving my life."

Both guards hesitated, they looked at Xie Han Mo.

Xie Han Mo's thick eyelashes drooped down, before she opened her eyes and looked at Fang Yuan with a crystal clear gaze, after three breaths of time, she nodded: "Then I will thank you in advance, human Gu Master. What is your name?"

"My name is Gu Yue Fang Yuan. You can call me Fang Yuan." Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

Chapter 1662: Competition for Saintess

Time passed quickly, more than twenty days passed again.

Before the Merit Obelisk, Fang Yuan looked at the rankings with his arms behind his back. His position had fallen to fifth already.

Initially, he was at the front, but changes started to occur.

Gu Immortals realized that as long as they looked into this Merit Obelisk, they would be able to find many options.

These options had price tags, one could use their accumulated merits to exchange for them. Immortal materials, Immortal Gu, Immortal Gu recipes, immortal killer moves, and even Immortal Gu House, they were all available.

With the merits that Miao Ming Shen and the rest had, they could only exchange for the stuff at the bottom of the list. Those expensive options were like carrots dangling above the donkey, they made these Gu Immortals very proactive.

Competition was getting more intense.

Fang Yuan's focus was not that, his only goal was regret Gu.

Regret Gu was very important to Fang Yuan. Even though the items in the Merit Obelisk were very valuable, they were merely icing on the cake for Fang Yuan, regret Gu could help Fang Yuan gain a qualitative change.

But among these rewards, there was neither regret Gu nor the exchange of Merit Obelisk itself.

This meant that the rewards listed were not fully comprehensive.

Regret Gu was not part of the rewards, but that did not mean that regret Gu was not inside this paradise.

Fang Yuan did not waste his time, he looked for clues and chose specific missions, after using wisdom path methods to deduce, many of his suspicions were lifted. Eventually, his focus was completely on Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea.

There were many rumors regarding this sea area.

Through Fang Yuan's deductions, there was a high possibility of regret Gu being in there.

However, even though Fang Yuan knew the location, he could not get close.

The mission of punishing the unscrupulous merchant twenty days ago was the closest Fang Yuan had ever gotten to Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea. But he had tried, after just thirty li away from the island, he could not move closer.

"How can I get into Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea?"

This was a problem that gave Fang Yuan a headache.

Paradise Earth's arrangements were too powerful, Fang Yuan could not act freely. His space path attainment was also not impressive, he had tried to use Fixed Immortal Travel earlier but it could not activate, even with an immortal killer move that Fang Yuan thought of. This meant that once Fang Yuan left the paradise, Fixed Immortal Travel would not allow him to re-enter again.

"As for these people…" Fang Yuan looked at the names of the Gu Immortals on the merit board, he squinted.

He wanted to keep these people around.

On one hand, killing the Gu Immortals in this paradise was risky.

On the other hand, these Gu Immortals were now earning merits and getting rewards, they were like livestock getting fattened. Fang Yuan could slaughter them when everyone went out, it would give him much greater benefits.

Thus, not only did Fang Yuan not harm them, he even helped them with more detailed information.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest were competing more intensely. Especially since mission rewards were observable and limited, everyone could exchange for them, once someone got something, others could not.

Thus, even though they did not try to kill each other, they schemed and purposely gave out false information in increasing frequency.

In this situation, the 'honest and truthful' Chu Ying was like an outlier, he became very prominent. Even though Miao Ming Shen and the rest did not say anything, they became increasingly friendlier towards Fang Yuan.

A change occurred three days later.

A new mission appeared on the Merit Obelisk: Head to the Sacred City of the mermen, attend the Sea God Ceremony, and defend the city from the assault of sea beasts.

Once this mission appeared, Fang Yuan selected it.

"The chance I have been waiting for is finally here!" Fang Yuan was very excited.

The Sea God Ceremony was unique to the mermen, in this ceremony, males and females would gather and form new families, they would also elect the new Saintess.

The saintess had an incredibly high status in merman society.

And Fang Yuan had already gotten crucial information, in this paradise, the saintess had an incredible role. Every time a new saintess was elected, their main mission would be to enter Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea, using their singing to soothe the killing intent of the demon and stabilize the sea area.

"This Merit Obelisk's missions are meant to benefit the humans and mermen, bringing prosperity to the people and punishing evil while promoting kindness. After the saintess is elected, she would have to enter Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea, by then, a relevant mission might appear. But no matter what, I need to accept this mission and meet the saintess in advance."

"After so long, the Sea God Ceremony is finally here!" Xia Lin pushed open the window of her inn room, the noise of the crowd outside could be heard.

Her room was on the second floor, Xia Lin looked down and saw people moving in the streets while closely packed together. All sorts of flags were waving, there were temporary shops selling Gu, snacks, and even gambling dens, all of the businesses were doing well.

Xia Lin's mood was quickly affected, she became quite happy.

Splat.

Suddenly, with a soft sound, a pearl landed on Xia Lin's window frame.

Xia Lin was dazed before she flushed rapidly.

Pearls had a special significance in the Sea God Ceremony, it meant a proposal. If someone tossed Xia Lin a pearl, it meant that they liked her and wanted to marry her.

"Who is it?" Xia Lin did not dare to pick up the pearl because that action had deep meaning behind it, she looked down and saw that dozens of men were looking in her direction, tossing the pearls in their hands.

"Su Yi!"

"Su Yi!" "I love you!"

"Accept my love, Su Yi!"

The men tossed their pearls while shouting.

"Hey miss!" Someone called out to Xia Lin.

Xia Lin turned her gaze towards a young man on the street, he was a merman in tattered clothes, he was clearly poor.

The merman youngster flushed as he said: "Miss, I tossed that pearl to you, I had too little strength, I can't throw it high enough, can you please toss it back to me."

Xia Lin instantly understood, this youngster wanted to toss his pearl to Su Yi but had too little strength, it ended up going to Xia Lin instead.

"Lady Su Yi is truly a famous beauty, her charm is too great, be it young boys or mature men, they are all in love with her."

Xia Lin breathed out slowly, next, waves splashed as the pearl was lifted from the ground, going into the youngster's hands.

"Thank you, thank you!" The youngster was overjoyed, he tossed the pearl with all his strength.

The pearl got higher and higher, it was in the right direction now, but Su Yi frowned as she closed her window.

The youngster's pearl landed on the window and fell down, over a dozen pearls suffered the same fate. But these pearls were different, they were huge and shiny, they were not common.

On the street, the men did not disperse after this, they got even more excited, more and more people came to Su Yi's area and wanted to see her beautiful face. Some still had hope and wanted to toss their pearls, after all, what if they got lucky?

"A bunch of commoners with nothing better to do." Su Yi frowned, a pink cloud cushioned her tail as she floated downstairs.

She had incredible beauty and arrogance on her face, but the most attractive part were her snow-white scales.

Merman scales varied in different colors, white scales were extremely rare, it was considered the purest color and was extremely idolized in the merman society.

Two mermaid nannies followed after her as they muttered.

"These fellows should look at themselves in the mirror, they want to be Lady Su Yi's husband? Simply laughable!"

"Our Lady Su Yi is a contestant for the saintess position, she would not accept any man's pearl."

The merman saintess was pure and flawless, once she obtains the position, she would not be able to marry for life, she had to keep her virginity.

Xia Lin walked out of her room, lowering her head: "Sister Su Yi."

"Little sister Xia Lin." Su Yi showed a faint smile, hiding the arrogance deeply as she spoke: "How was your rest? Have you thought it through?"

"Thank you for the hospitality, right now, all the inns are fully booked, without you, I would not have had a place to rest." Xia Lin immediately thanked.

A mermaid nanny smiled: "It was fate that you met with our Missy. In this vast sea, the meeting of two mermen is not easy, you two are fated to meet. I will say this bluntly, ordinary mermaids would die to be acquainted with our Missy."

Su Yi was not just a white scaled mermaid, she had a high status, and was the doted daughter of a strong tribe leader.

"Nanny Rong, what are you saying? I met with Xia Lin because we liked each other. Xia Lin, don't have any worries, go ahead if you have any busy matters. If you follow me to this Sea God Ceremony, the risks are high." Su Yi walked towards Xia Lin as she held her hand, saying sincerely.

Xia Lin was moved: "Sister Su Yi, you have helped me too much, since you want to become the saintess, I will definitely support you. But I am afraid that I am too weak, there are only four follower quotas after all."

Su Yi's eyes shined brightly, she held Xia Lin's hands as she said excitedly: "Xia Lin, thank you, with your help, I will have a higher chance of becoming the saintess."

Xia Lin had low cultivation level, she was only rank two but she had a rank five Gu worm.

Gather oil Gu, a top tier rank five Gu!

Of course, this Gu worm had no offensive might, but Su Yi had already found out about the details of the saintess test, the gather oil Gu would be very helpful in one of the rounds.

Chapter 1663: Fang Yuan, You Are A Good Person

Fang Yuan walked in the merman Sacred City, he did not disguise himself, he was in Chu Ying's appearance. But his aura was completely concealed, he was like a mortal.

On the street, people moved about fluidly, those who brushed past Fang Yuan would never imagine that a rank eight Gu Immortal was walking so closely beside them.

On the two sides of the street, there were shops and houses arranged in an orderly scale-like manner, the houses of mermen had their unique style, most had seashell or conch designs. Most were huge seashells and conchs, or modified shells of giant crabs and turtles. There were also few Gu houses that were a symbol of wealth and authority, they had great defensive properties. Other than personal estates, Gu houses used as shops were also booming with business.

As he walked, the people walking in front of Fang Yuan started to move away, they were cheering loudly.

Walking closer to take a look, Fang Yuan saw that a mermaid was receiving a jade pearl from a male Gu Master with teary eyes.

This pearl was quite rare, it was like glowing jade and had the shape of an eyeball.

This was not something valuable in the eyes of experts, as for Fang Yuan, it was a mortal material that he had no use for. But it was owned by the rank two male Gu Master, it was not easy for him to obtain this rank four Gu material jade eye pearl.

The mermaid might have noticed his feelings, she received the jade eye pearl in public as it signified her acceptance of his love.

Next, the mermaid placed the pearl into her mouth, everyone started to cheer and shout, the couple started to blush and turn red.

This action was not so simple, it meant she had accepted the young Gu Master's proposal!

"This paradise does not discriminate between races, merman and human can freely fall in love and have children without obstruction."

"But in the five regions, it was forbidden for merman and human to get together, not only would they be discouraged, their children would also be ostracized by both sides or even killed."

Fang Yuan had an eerie gaze.

The Sea God Ceremony was around the corner, the entire Sacred City was oozing with a joyful and festive atmosphere.

This couple was not the first that Fang Yuan saw, they might be very simple and insignificant figures in the Sacred City, but being ordinary did not mean one could not be blissful, this beautiful moment would become a cherished memory etched in their minds.

The memories of the five hundred years of his previous life started to surface again.

A group of mermen were looking at Xie Han Mo, Fang Yuan, and the rest with an imposing aura.

"I am Investigator Wu De, there have been many reports by different clansmen that our current generation saintess Xie Han Mo has an affair with the human Gu Master Gu Yue Fang Yuan, I am here to investigate it!" The leader was a jade-scaled merman who spoke in an icy tone.

"What?"

"I dare you to say that again!"

The two guards behind Xie Han Mo were furious, they wanted to attack in anger.

Xie Han Mo had a calm expression, while Fang Yuan had a dark expression as he clenched his fists.

He helped Xie Han Mo investigate the gambling den, they found a lot of corruption evidence, the saintess' mission had a qualitative breakthrough.

But the other party was not going to wait for the end, they schemed and spread vicious rumors, saying that the saintess was impure and had an affair with a human Gu Master.

These rumors had no evidence and were merely made up, Xie Han Mo and Fang Yuan did not care about them. But to think that the investigator from the Merman Sacred Court would actually come!

"Mobilizing the investigator without any evidence, I am afraid that Frost Tide tribe leader was not the only corrupted person, there is a higher-up involved here!" Fang Yuan transmitted to Xie Han Mo.

Xie Han Mo frowned, with slight hesitation, she spoke: "I am the saintess, you are a mere investigator, do you have the elder assembly's token?"

The jade-scaled merman smiled, taking out an information path Gu worm.

Xie Han Mo was calm: "Just this?"

The jade-scaled merman smiled again: "This cannot allow me to investigate the Saintess, but Fang Yuan is different, he is a human Gu Master. Forget about the token, I can investigate him even without one!"

Even though Fang Yuan was a human and humans were the rulers of the five regions, Eastern Sea's Merman Sacred Court was a super force, Fang Yuan had no background himself, the jade-scaled merman was not lying.

"Too vicious, I cannot believe that Frost Tide tribe's leader is such a person!"

"He is afraid, he knows how amazing Fang Yuan is, he is afraid that we will find out more evidence as time passes."

The two guards stood in front of Fang Yuan.

After this period of time, they had already acknowledged Fang Yuan.

"Wait, if both sides clash, that will be what the enemy wants to see, we will not be able to explain ourselves. I will go with them, we have a lot of progress in the gambling den, even without me, you can still win if you continue on that trail!" Fang Yuan transmitted.

"No way!"

"Fang Yuan, you are too naive, if you end up in their hands, you will live a fate worse than death."

The two guards shook their heads.

Fang Yuan smiled: "What is there to fear? I will die at worst. You saved my life before, in that case, I will repay it now. Do not look down on their schemes, this was targeted at me on the surface, but the true goal is Saintess. Once her reputation is hit and rumors spread, her status might be affected. Sacrificing me is a small issue, but we must defend Saintess' position, without this, how can you investigate and punish those corrupted people?"

The two guards hesitated.

Xie Han Mo was still composed, she said to the jade-scaled merman: "Go back, I will not hand him to you."

The jade-scaled merman was slightly stunned before he laughed: "Saintess, you want to defend this human Gu Master? Even at the cost of conflicting with us investigators?"

Xie Han Mo nodded: "Go back."

The jade-scaled merman looked at Fang Yuan before turning to Xie Han Mo, he showed a smile as if his scheme succeeded: "Good! We are not Saintess' match, we can only return in defeat. Hahaha!"

Saying so, he waved his hand and left with the mermen.

"Saintess, why did you do that?" Fang Yuan was anxious: "Like this, you…"

For the first time, Xie Han Mo interrupted him: "Fang Yuan, you are a good person."

"Hmm?"

"You are not afraid of death, other than courage, the biggest reason is that life is boring right? You seem to be disappointed in this world and in your own life, there is deep fatigue hidden in your eyes. But undeniably, you are a good person." Xie Han Mo said softly.

Fang Yuan: "…"

Xie Han Mo continued: "And I am also a good person. How can a good person sacrifice another good person?"

Saying so, she winked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a little dazed, this was the first time he had seen such lively expressions from Xie Han Mo, she was quite cute and cheeky.

"Then… what about the rumors?"

"Indeed, that damned investigator is going to make up stories when he returns!"

The two guards were very worried.

Xie Han Mo's expression went back to normal, she said aloofly: "Then let them."

…

Several days later, the Sea God Ceremony started.

The male mermen wore their shell armors, they carried long spears, javelins and blades. According to traditions, these shells and weapons were made by them personally using locally sourced materials.

The female mermen, the mermaids, wore seaweed strips of various colors on them. Pink seaweed strips were used by young unmarried girls, widows wore black seaweed strips, while noble ladies wore gold, silver, and crystal colored ones. Ordinary mermaids wore brown, dark blue, and grey seaweed strips.

This was the traditional costume of the mermen, it was quite unique.

Long long ago, before mermen learned how to use Gu worms, they lived a primitive lifestyle. Males hunted while females foraged.

At the center of Sacred City, people gathered, singing and dancing.

A large number of merman warriors were waving their spears, their armors clashed and created loud sounds.

The mermaids' seaweed strips were like rainbow ribbons fluttering in the water, they waved in sync with the singing, experiencing no tiredness.

This moment was reserved for the mermen, all the human Gu Masters were watching outside.

The singing and dancing lasted for hours, mermen, male and female alike, continued to walk out of the area with shattered armors or fatigued bodies.

Gradually, several mermaid girls emerged, they were the contestants for this year's saintess competition.

But what surprised Fang Yuan was that out of the nine competitors, not all of them had white scales. it seemed like in this paradise, it was not only white-scaled mermaids who could vie for the saintess position, mermaids with different scale colors could also compete.

And among everyone, mermaid Su Yi was the most dazzling one.

Chapter 1664: Saintess Test

During the Sea God Ceremony, Sacred City was flooded with people.

The surrounding spectators were clamoring loudly.

Fang Yuan was in this crowd, he observed the prospective saintesses with an eerie gaze.

His plan was to choose one of them and assist her in becoming the saintess.

…

"They are assisting her to become the saintess?"

"That's right, Frost Tide tribe leader invested a lot into this to help Lady Qiu Shuang."

Xie Han Mo's two blue scaled and red scaled guards looked at each other after hearing this, feeling each others' worry.

In the hall, Fang Yuan sat at one side, he gritted his teeth as his expression turned unsightly.

Earlier, Xie Han Mo rejected the investigator and protected Fang Yuan, this escalated the rumors, eventually, the Merman Sacred Court decided to hold the Sea God Ceremony again to decide on the saintess once more.

"This is a scheme, they made use of your kindness and knew you would not abandon me, thus, this situation arose." Fang Yuan sighed deeply, feeling like he had implicated Xie Han Mo.

Xie Han Mo glanced at him, smiling: "Fang Yuan, no need to feel responsible. If we abandoned you earlier, they would spread rumors that I am old and callous, it would still affect my reputation."

"Saintess, no need to console me at this point." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "The effect and severity of both cases are vastly different, we have already worked together for so long, how would I not know?"

Xie Han Mo smiled: "Alright, forget about this, it does not help the situation."

Fang Yuan and both guards quickly adjusted their mindsets as their expressions changed.

Xie Han Mo added: "The saintess position is not easy to hold onto, the moment I started to investigate the corruption, someone tried to drag me down. This means that the issue of corruption among the Sacred Court's elders has gotten very severe! Don't be too pessimistic, even though a new Sea God Ceremony is held, I have not lost my qualifications, right? It is not so easy to nurture a new saintess."

Places with people will have competition for benefits.

This saying was appropriate for the mermen as well.

Mermen also had schemes and conflict of interests.

The saintess had high status, if the forces in the merman tribe can nurture their own saintess, for the following period of time, they would have some political advantage and would be able to gain more benefits.

Normally speaking, mermaid girls who could compete for the saintess position had deep backgrounds or were backed by one or two large forces.

…

In the underwater Sacred City, the singing gradually stopped, as intense sounds of drumming could be heard.

In the square, only a few mermaid girls were left, they danced without showing fatigue, they were extremely determined to become the saintess.

Fang Yuan stood outside the square, looking in, these seven mermaid girls were all beautiful, some were enchanting, some were youthful, some were cute, and some were elegant.

There was a huge spirit spring at the center of the square, it was called the Sea God's Spring, water sprayed upwards and carried an elderly mermaid granny, she was the grand elder of this merman tribe.

The grand elder looked at the seven mermaid girls as she nodded, saying: "The first round of the saintess test, golden needle in black oil."

Saying so, more than ten strength path Gu Masters carried huge vats into the square.

Thud thud thud…

After placing down the vats with loud sounds, each of the mermaid girls had one in front of them. The vats were larger than their bodies by several times, they could only see the inside after floating upwards.

The vats were filled with thick black oil, the first test was to find a tiny golden needle in the designated time.

"I request for my follower to take my stage." The white-scaled mermaid Su Yi looked at the huge water vat as she said calmly.

"Approved." The grand elder looked at Su Yi deeply.

"Don't be nervous, don't be nervous." Xia Lin encouraged herself continuously as she walked into the square while feeling uneasy.

"What's going on? The great Lady Su Yi has a rank two Gu Master as her follower?"

"Calm down, Su Yi's decision means that this mermaid is more than she seems."

Everyone talked among themselves.

"It's her?" Fang Yuan saw Xia Lin and his brows rose, he did not expect this girl to become the follower of the most favored saintess candidate.

Gather oil Gu!

Xia Lin floated to the water vat and used this rank five Gu worm.

Instantly, the black oil in the vat started to move, it was drawn out by Xia Lin and gathered in her hands.

The crowd went into a commotion.

"The aura of a rank five Gu!"

"She is clearly a rank two Gu Master, but she can use rank five Gu? Did I see wrongly?"

"I understand, this must be the rank five gather oil Gu that has been the hot topic recently."

"So this mermaid has such a quality Gu worm, no wonder Su Yi allowed her to become her follower!"

Gather oil Gu's effect was no joke, after a while, the vat became empty, only a golden needle was left sparkling at the bottom of the vat.

The crowd was roused.

Countless heated gazes landed on Xia Lin.

Xia Lin was even more nervous now, she flushed red and showed a cute expression of not knowing what to do.

Su Yi looked at her and smiled, thinking: "I was right to recruit her into my group."

In the first test, Su Yi relied on Xia Lin's stellar performance to gain a huge boost in reputation.

Fang Yuan's eyes were dark like the abyss, looking at the crowd leaving, he thought: "Six out of seven passed the first test, they came prepared for this. Evidently, the test content was leaked prior to this."

…

Pale green flames burned in front of Xie Han Mo, forming a path of flames.

Qiu Shuang, who was also a white-scaled mermaid walked in calmly, standing at the other end of the flame road as she looked at Xie Han Mo mockingly: "Former saintess, your turn."

"Damn it! This eerie fire burns the soul, special Gu worms are needed to resist it. We were already amply prepared, but to think that this first test would be so specific!"

"And the worst thing is, Qiu Shuang came prepared with the proper Gu worms, she can resist the eerie fire. Is this luck? Hmph! She clearly knows the test content, this is Frost Tide tribe's scheme, they are colluding and cheating openly!"

Both guards were very angry.

"Let me." Fang Yuan walked towards the frowning Xie Han Mo.

"You?" Xie Han Mo looked at Fang Yuan with crystal clear eyes.

"Trust me, I am confident in this." Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with bright light, looking at Xie Han Mo directly.

The two looked at each other for a moment, before Xie Han Mo turned away.

"Be careful, this eerie fire is not simple… if you cannot endure it, you can just step down." Xie Han Mo said.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, turning around and taking huge strides into the eerie fire.

Pain!

An intense pain originating from his soul assaulted Fang Yuan's entire body in an instant.

Fang Yuan shuddered as he walked with great difficulty.

He gritted his teeth until they bled.

His eyes were wide opened, they were also tearing apart.

His soul was burned by the flame as it melted, thankfully, he had two lifetime's accumulation, and was an otherworldly demon, the eerie fire was less effective on him than on others.

He would not give up midway, because he knew that by taking Xie Han Mo's place, if he failed, Xie Han Mo would fail too.

When he finally walked through the eerie fire road, everyone went wild, countless shocked gazes gathered on him.

Many mermen were moved.

Fang Yuan tried to smile but at the next moment, he fainted.

But right when he was about to land on the ground, Xie Han Mo arrived and held him in her arms.

"Don't worry, I will not waste your effort." Xie Han Mo looked at Fang Yuan deeply before turning to look at Qiu Shuang. For the first time, her gentle eyes revealed a cold and sharp light.

Thanks to Fang Yuan's desperate attempt, Xie Han Mo passed the difficult trap set specially for her.

The second, third, and fourth test…

She performed perfectly, the other competitors soon fell short, eventually, only mermaid Qiu Shuang was left.

"It seems that Lady Xie Han Mo will very likely retain her position as saintess." Outside the square, Fang Yuan was still pale as he sat down weakly, expressing joy on his face.

"It was all thanks to you Fang Yuan, without your performance in the first round, we would not have gotten this far."

"Hahaha, you got past the flame road, it was shocking to everyone. A few days later, you woke up, do you know that news of your survival shocked countless mermen in the Sacred City!"

Both guards laughed loudly.

Fang Yuan stopped his joyful expression as she said: "Be careful, the situation is in our favor, the other party will not stand by."

Fang Yuan had expected Frost Tide tribe leader to act, but he did not expect that it would be so vicious.

In the house, the red scaled guard knelt on the ground, his face was red: "Saintess, please let me battle, I need to clear up the accusation and humiliation that they have dealt to me. How could I possibly bully a widow?!"

Xie Han Mo sighed: "Get up, I know you well, but this is clearly the enemy's plot. If you charge out like this, their schemes will succeed."

The blue scaled guard was worried: "This is not an ordinary widow, she is Bu Su Lian, the wife of the former third elder of the Sacred Court. They are simply too vicious, the investigator will come soon to arrest him for trial. In that case, he would not be able to join the test, our strength will fall greatly!"

Fang Yuan added: "This wife of the former third elder of the Sacred Court was willing to sacrifice her reputation to accuse him. She must have a close relationship with Frost Tide tribe leader, this corruption is extremely severe, otherwise, she would not have to act personally. Since they set this trap, they must be amply prepared, if we try to clear up the situation, we would fall into their scheme. We can only play along with this and find a way out."

"How do we do that?"

"Very simple, I will take the blame." Fang Yuan said plainly.

Both guards stared with wide opened eyes as they started at Fang Yuan.

"No way." Xie Han Mo rejected this instantly.

Chapter 1665: The Story of the Sea God and Mermaid

Even though Xie Han Mo understood that if Fang Yuan took the blame, the situation would be resolved, she still rejected him without hesitation.

But this way, Xie Han Mo and the rest would be in a passive spot.

The turning point happened three days later, Xie Han Mo received some information.

Xie Han Mo looked at the information as she became stunned before sighing: "Qiu Shuang is no longer pure."

She gave the intel to her guards and Fang Yuan to see.

After looking at it, their expressions changed.

Qiu Shuang was the saintess candidate that Frost Tide tribe leader supported, she was extremely popular during this Sea God Ceremony, she was the most likely person to take the position of saintess from Xie Han Mo.

But to think that she had lost her virginity.

Only mermaids who were virgins could compete for the saintess position, this was the first condition.

The red scaled guard was extremely happy: "Great, to think that this Qiu Shuang is not a virgin, with this information, they are history!"

The blue scaled guard was very calm: "The Sea God Ceremony is the most important ceremony of our tribe, it has always been inspected strictly, how did Qiu Shuang get through the inspection? Unless our tribe's corruption has already extended to the priest? Then the situation is too severe."

Fang Yuan frowned: "We need to remember something, if we announce this now, everyone might think that we are trying to protect red scale and this is just our accusation. How reliable is the information? If this is part of their plan, we would be in trouble…"

Xie Han Mo shook her head: "This is definitely reliable, Qiu Shuang is supported by Frost Tide tribe's leader, we are supported by the grand elder, this was given to me by her. Even though we do not have evidence, I believe that as long as we inspect Qiu Shuang's background, we would be able to find out if she is a virgin by asking another priest."

Fang Yuan understood now that Xie Han Mo was able to become the saintess because she was supported by the grand elder of the Merman Sacred Court.

Among all the higher-ups, grand elder was the fairest and most lenient one, she had great authority. But because she was too lenient, everyone became corrupted, her support towards Xie Han Mo was also an attempt to correct her mistakes.

Everything that followed went as Xie Han Mo predicted.

After Qiu Shuang was reported, she was investigated upon and her story was exposed, she had really lost her virginity.

This information was too shocking, the Merman Sacred Court could not keep it secret. As news spread, the entire Sacred City was in a commotion, countless Gu Masters gasped.

"This is likely the biggest scandal in our Merman Sacred Court for the last thousand years!"

"Qiu Shuang was truly disrespectful, such a desecration towards the Sea God, she has to be punished."

"Killing her will not soothe our rage!"

Anger was not just in the commoners, the higher-ups of the Merman Sacred Court were furious too, the punishment towards Qiu Shuang was rapidly decided.

A few days later, Qiu Shuang's head fell off her head and onto the ground, she died.

Bam!

A high quality cup was smashed onto the ground by Frost Tide tribe's leader, it broke into pieces.

"Xie Han Mo, you were too much!" Frost Tide tribe's leader growled, his eyes were bloodshot.

"I told you long ago to control yourself when drinking. After Qiu Shuang's matter, as the person who supported her, the higher-ups will no longer give you their attention." In the room, there was a mermaid noble lady, she drank tea slowly, she showed no fear towards the angry Frost Tide tribe leader.

Frost Tide tribe leader gritted his teeth, he said to the mermaid noble lady: "Bu Su Lian, I do not need your reminder. Our allies will not turn on us after just this small issue. If Xie Han Mo retains her saintess position, they will also suffer and die. So even if they hate me, even if they do not want to see me, they will have to force themselves to work with me!"

Bu Su Lian said plainly: "You are right, but now that Qiu Shuang is dead, how will you defeat Xie Han Mo? Our best pawn has already been destroyed."

"No, no." Frost Tide tribe leader laughed sinisterly: "You can rest assured, I still have methods left."

"Oh? I am listening." Bu Su Lian sat up straight.

Frost Tide tribe leader kept it a secret: "You will know in a few days."

A few days later.

On the square of Sacred City, mermaid Dong Lei said under everyone's watchful eyes: "I am willing to take Qiu Shuang's place and continue with the Sea God Ceremony."

"Who is Dong Lei?"

"She was one of Qiu Shuang's followers."

"To think that Frost Tide tribe's leader had this pawn prepared."

"According to our tribe rules, sisters can take each others' place, Dong Lei can totally replace Qiu Shuang and attend the Sea God Ceremony to contest for the saintess position."

Everyone discussed.

The origin of the Sea God Ceremony was a legendary story among the mermen.

In the story, the first batch of mermen lived in Eastern Sea, they created a small fishing village.

One day, a huge sea beast attacked the island, it created a tsunami around the island, the fishing village was almost about to be destroyed.

To save the villagers in the fishing village, mermaid Ah Qing knelt at the cliff and prayed to the Sea God.

The Sea God heard her prayer and said: "Oh Ah Qing, I love to hear beautiful singing. If you can sing three satisfactory songs for me, I will chase the sea beast away and calm the sea, defending the fishing village."

Ah Qing was overjoyed, she quickly agreed.

She started to sing the first song by the cliff, it was enchanting. After she finished, the Sea God savored the melody as he calmed the sea.

Ah Qing sang the second song, her beautiful voice mesmerized the Sea God, seaweed danced to her singing, prawns and fish gathered by her side as they listened.

Ah Qing wanted to sing the third song but at that point, she no longer had any strength. After singing for two days and two nights, she was too tired.

After returning home, she called her sister Ah Ya and told her everything before dying from exhaustion.

Ah Ya was very upset but she listened to her sister Ah Qing's wish, she came to the cliff and said to the Sea God: "Oh Sea God, I will take my sister's place and sing the third song for you."

Sea God said: "Go ahead."

Ah Ya started to sing, her voice was filled with agony and misery, but also firm determination. After she finished, the Sea God was pleased and the sea beast left, the fishing village was safe once again.

When choosing the saintess, mermen would set up many tests during the Sea God Ceremony.

These tests had varying contents, but the final round would always be the same, since the start of the ceremony's history.

That was a singing competition among mermaids.

They would get on the stage and sing on the specially made altar-like Gu house.

Everyone would get to sing three times, from the results, they would choose the sole saintess.

All the tests before this were just elimination rounds.

If during the Sea God Ceremony, all of the contestants got eliminated, then the saintess position would remain empty.

Chapter 1666: Intercept

The sea at night was turbulent with vicious waves, wild winds were howling.

From the black depths of the sea, a chain made of pearls of light started to shine. Next, intense drumming and zither music could be heard reverberating in the waves.

The tens of merman warriors wore ancient armor made from seashells, they held up a huge white shell shield. Behind them, mermen danced and sang, surrounding Xie Han Mo and Dong Lei. Behind them, countless mermen were watching this final test with high spirits.

The seashell floated to the surface of the sea, waves landed on the huge shell and caused waves to splash.

Surrounding the seashell, merman warriors did their best to stabilize it.

The huge shell slowly opened up, this was a natural stage.

The seashell had a great origin, it was left behind by the desolate beast giant music shell, there was a vast number of sound path dao marks on the seashell, even if a mortal stood inside, their voice would be spread far and wide.

Dong Lei was the first to ascend the shell.

Countless mermen floated to the surface of the sea, watching in anticipation.

At a corner, in a boat-like Gu house, Bu Su Lian watched as she said to Frost Tide tribe's leader: "Are you so confident in Dong Lei? The first person to perform has a natural disadvantage."

Frost Tide tribe's leader smiled: "Just watch, I cannot explain it in words."

Bu Su Lian looked at Frost Tide tribe's leader deeply before turning towards the giant music shell.

Dong Lei started to sing.

Her voice was clear and elegant, it was quite mesmerizing, all of the mermen started to indulge in this beautiful song.

At once, due to the giant music shell's effect, in the radius of a thousand li, Dong Lei's beautiful singing could be heard. Even the torrential tides were suppressed.

Mermen were born with a throat that could sing better than other species, they could produce incredibly beautiful singing.

According to human standards, each merman was a natural born singer.

This was because each merman's body had abundant water path dao marks. And in their throats, there was a particular cartilage that was filled with sound path dao marks.

There was a point in history where humans slaughtered mermen to take away the sound path cartilage in their throats, it was an excellent sound path Gu material.

And the mermaids competing to become saintess had even better singing than most mermen.

Those who live near the sea would often hear similar rumors about sailors who would get mesmerized by the singing of mermaids, they would forget time, forget their direction, they would not notice even if their ship hit a reef.

This was not an exaggeration, it was the truth.

Dong Lei's singing was superb, most of the people were listening in enjoyment, only Fang Yuan and the rest became furious, their expressions were ugly and they frowned tightly. Even Xie Han Mo, who was usually calm, had a change of expression, sadness and shock was expressed in her eyes.

"What is going on?"

"Why is Dong Lei singing the song that we prepared?!"

The red scaled and blue scaled guards were furious with wide opened eyes.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim, he gritted his teeth: "Isn't this obvious? There is a spy among us, he informed the enemy of our song!"

Both guards looked at each other before turning to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked at them fearlessly: "Only the four of us know what songs we prepared, the traitor must be one of you. Who is it?"

Xie Han Mo could not be the traitor, so among Fang Yuan, blue scale and red scale, one of them had to be the traitor.

"Bullshit!"

"You are the traitor!"

Both guards were furious with red faces as they denied it.

Xie Han Mo sighed, shaking her head: "There might not be a spy, they might have found out about our preparations through special information path methods."

"Hahaha." Far away, Frost Tide tribe's leader laughed loudly in his Gu house.

Bu Su Lian had been observing Xie Han Mo and the rest long ago, seeing their expressions, she understood as her eyes shined: "You planted a spy near her?"

Frost Tide tribe's leader laughed continuously: "Of course! Xie Han Mo is too young and too naive to compete with me. Do you know the huge price I paid in order to get a spy this close to her?"

Bu Su Lian's eyes flickered with bright light: "As expected and befitting of Frost Tide tribe's leader, the price you paid is worth it. Now that Dong Lei has sang her song, Xie Han Mo cannot use it again, she is almost helpless now that she has no song to sing."

Xie Han Mo had truly fallen deeply into the plot of Frost Tide tribe's leader!

The final round of the saintess competition was to sing three songs. These three songs needed special preparation, sound path Gu worms were needed for them, including lots of practice.

Each song needed to produce a different effect.

The first song was to calm the sea waves. The second song was to attract living beings, and the third song was to repel sea beasts.

Thus, even though Xie Han Mo prepared three songs, after Dong Lei stole the first song, her remaining two songs were different and could not be used in its place.

"What do we do?" Both guards were extremely flustered and anxious.

"Damn it, damn it, we got so far but still fell for a trap at this moment."

"It is no use, it is too late to prepare now!"

"This must be the scheme of Frost Tide tribe's leader, we will expose it and ruin his reputation!" Red scale screamed.

Fang Yuan looked at him like he was an idiot: "Do you have proof? Who would believe us? They would use this chance to counterattack and accuse you instead, what do we do then?"

"Oh." Red-scaled guard was stunned.

Xie Han Mo sighed deeply: "In that case, forget it."

"Saintess?" Both guards were stunned.

Xie Han Mo smiled bitterly: "You can still leave now, hurry. While there is still some time, leave this place."

Xie Han Mo would lose the competition for the saintess position, she would no longer be the saintess. This way, she would face the attack of the new saintess Dong Lei and Frost Tide tribe's leader, she would have a terrible end.

To not implicate her three followers, even if there was a possible spy among them, Xie Han Mo wanted to fight for some time.

"Saintess…" Understanding Xie Han Mo's intention, both of her guards started to choke with tears.

This situation had attracted everyone's attention.

"What happened to Xie Han Mo?"

"Something bad seems to have happened!"

"They are panicking, haha, it seems that Lady Dong Lei's singing has sent them into despair!"

"Xie Han Mo is finished." Inside the Gu house, Bu Su Lian sighed deeply.

Frost Tide tribe's leader smiled sinisterly: "Even though I can't deal with that foolish old grand elder, I will definitely torture that Xie Han Mo after this to vent my anger and hatred!"

Dong Lei stepped down the stage as she raised her eyebrows: "I have already calmed the sea by five feet, I will anticipate sister Xie Han Mo's performance next."

Chapter 1667: White Moonlight

Xie Han Mo looked at her deeply in the eye as she ascended the stage.

She had just entered the stage when she got stunned.

"Why are you…" She looked at Fang Yuan who was beside her with deep shock.

Fang Yuan interrupted her: "As your follower, I am of course qualified to be your accompaniment."

"Quickly leave…" Xie Han Mo swiftly said, but anxiety was all over her face for once.

"You want to sing the same song? Even if you sing better than Dong Lei, the rules will disqualify you. Trust me, I have a song for this." Fang Yuan interrupted Xie Han Mo as he transmitted.

Xie Han Mo's heart wavered.

Songs could not be changed easily, because they needed to be paired with Gu worms and needed lots of practice.

By changing the song, the Gu worms used also needed to be modified.

In this situation, Xie Han Mo could no longer change her Gu worms, this meant that the new song and the original song needed to have the same rhythm and melody.

It might be possible given a hundred days of preparation, but in this rushed situation, the chances were close to zero.

"The song is not the same of course, but don't forget that I had participated in our song composition. I have a similar song here, but I need you to adapt to it on the spot, take note of the cooperation between my song and the Gu worms." Fang Yuan transmitted: "And these are the lyrics and tune."

Xie Han Mo was stunned before nodding: "Okay."

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply: "Then let's start."

Xie Han Mo breathed in deeply, she shut her eyes, this was her usual habit before singing.

Everyone became quiet.

They waited quietly…

And waited…

"Why is she not singing yet?" Gradually, some people became impatient.

"Hahaha, how can they sing? They have no songs to sing!" Frost Tide tribe's leader laughed loudly with a face flushed red.

"Oh, sorry, can anyone lend me a zither Gu?" Fang Yuan broke the silence.

Everyone: "…"

You are the accompaniment but in this important Sea God Ceremony, you did not even prepare a zither Gu?"

Is it really okay to be so lax?

"I need a rank three zither Gu, can anyone lend me one?" Fang Yuan added, looking towards the grand elder.

The grand elder understood his words, Xie Han Mo met with an accident, she had anticipated this and quickly asked someone to send a zither Gu.

Fang Yuan obtained the zither Gu and said: "This is too important, let me refine the Gu on the spot."

Everyone: "…"

What? At the last round of the Sea God Ceremony, you want to refine Gu?

Are you serious?

What was this human Gu Master thinking? He was toying with everyone!

The mood of all the mermen turned bad.

Frost Tide tribe's leader quickly instructed his lackeys, a voice suddenly resounded: "You are purposely stalling for time!"

Everyone was about to clamor when Fang Yuan shouted loudly: "Are you saying that the Sea God Ceremony has a rule against refining Gu? This is for the sake of the song, we will start after the Gu is refined."

Grand elder quickly added: "There are no such rules indeed, I will allow it. Quickly refine the Gu and start, what does everyone think?"

The other elders looked at each other, some wanted to speak while others stayed silent.

Lackeys of Frost Tide tribe's leader shouted again: "The Sea God Ceremony is such an important ceremony, you want all of us mermen to wait for your Gu refinement?"

Fang Yuan quickly rebuked: "I am refining Gu for the Sea God Ceremony, are you all unable to wait a little bit for this important ceremony? Whoever has no patience can stand up now! You can leave right away."

Everyone went silent.

"You have a sharp tongue! But when you end up in my hands, I will make sure I smash all your teeth and pull out your tongue." Frost Tide tribe's leader snickered.

On the giant shell that was floating on the sea's surface, the merman warriors were exerting themselves while stabilizing it.

Some of the mermen floated to the surface, some only had their heads above the water, but all of them were looking at Fang Yuan refine his zither Gu.

Xie Han Mo was instead ignored.

She stood beside Fang Yuan feeling very strange. She had attended the Sea God Ceremony once before and became the saintess. She had seen countless Sea God Ceremonies, but never had such a thing ever happened!

Fang Yuan's refinement speed became faster and faster, this was because the zither Gu's owner cooperated with him.

After getting the zither Gu, Fang Yuan stood up and went behind Xie Han Mo, saying confidently: "Alright, the real show starts now."

"Finally." The mermen let out breaths of air, feeling resentful.

"Go ahead and sing, I want to see what song you can come up with!" Frost Tide tribe's leader snickered.

Below the stage, the grand elder and both guards had worried expressions.

Xie Han Mo shut her eyes.

At this moment, the zither started playing.

Fang Yuan had activated the zither Gu, it let out a long and deep melody, the tune was extremely beautiful to listen to.

Xie Han Mo shut her eyes, she started to sing[1] —

The white moonlight is somewhere in my heart.

It is so bright, yet so icy cold.

Everyone has their own sadness.

Wanting to conceal it, but it just became more obvious.

…

Everyone was silent, only the sound of waves could be heard.

Her beautiful voice intoxicated everyone, they could not stop savoring it.

…

The white moonlight lightens the horizons of the world.

It's in my heart, but not by my side.

I could not wipe the tears off your face back then.

The road is too long, I could not seek forgiveness.

…

The tune was sorrowful but simple and elegant, it progressed smoothly with each verse, a feeling of intense sadness and agony filled everyone's hearts.

Xie Han Mo had a pure and penetrating voice, she was gentle and warm, just like the pale white moonlight that seemed cold and also a little warm on the inside.

The giant shell started to emit a white light, the waves did not seem to want to disturb her beautiful singing, they became weaker.

…

The white moonlight lightens the horizons of the world.

The fuller it is, the more loneliness I feel.

Unable to wipe the tears in my recollection.

The road is too long, how can I make amendments to you?

…

Xie Han Mo was also engrossed in it, her gaze shifted towards Fang Yuan, who was standing there activating the zither Gu with his full concentration.

She thought to herself: "Is there sorrow in your heart as well?"

Countless mermen shed tears.

The pain of love and affection, these tears were hidden deep in their hearts.

Was there true fulfillment in this world?

Loneliness always existed.

…

The white moonlight is somewhere in my heart.

It is so bright, yet so icy cold.

Everyone has their own sadness.

Wanting to conceal it but it just keeps growing.

…

As the song ended, the crowd remained silent.

In the Gu house, Frost Tide tribe's leader was stiff like a statue, shock expressed all over his face.

The sea was calm and the dark clouds scattered, pure moonlight shone down on the giant seashell, enveloping Xie Han Mo and Fang Yuan.

The two turned around slightly, looking at each other.

[1] Search Youtube: White Moonlight, Jeff Chang Back

Chapter 1668: Too Naive

As the music ended, the mermen started to converse among themselves.

"What song is this? This is the first time I have heard it, it is simply too amazing."

"Did you all notice, the song was superb but Xie Han Mo was not skillful, her Gu worm manipulation had lots of errors." Many mermen talked about it with strange expressions.

The true reason was that Fang Yuan and Xie Han Mo did not practise this earlier. If they had even one practice, they would not make such mistakes.

But even so, reaching such a level of cooperation in their first attempt, Xie Han Mo's personal attainment was truly profound.

"Right now, the sea is calm and the weather has changed, the dark clouds scattered and the moonlight reappeared. Regardless of Xie Han Mo's mistakes, the results are evident."

"This should be a draw, in fact, Xie Han Mo should have a slight lead."

"It will depend on the next two songs."

The mermen were getting more excited about the rest of the Sea God Ceremony.

The grand elder could notice many things, she let out a breath of air as the worry in her heart lifted.

"What is going on?!" In the Gu house, Frost Tide tribe's leader screamed.

"It seems that although your scheme succeeded, an accident occurred." Bu Su Lian squinted her eyes, focusing her gaze on Fang Yuan, she sighed in amazement: "This man is not so simple, no wonder Xie Han Mo took interest in him. I am a song expert, this is likely his own creation, this shows that this human has very high attainment in sound path."

Frost Tide tribe's leader expressed his suspicions: "There are countless songs in this world, how can you be sure that this was his creation?"

Bu Su Lian smiled lightly, looking at Frost Tide tribe's leader with an expression of disdain in her eyes: "You don't understand."

Frost Tide tribe's leader's face became even darker: "Bu Su Lian, can you speak clearly?!"

Bu Su Lian chuckled coldly, ignoring Frost Tide tribe's leader as she looked towards Fang Yuan with glistening eyes.

Others would fear Frost Tide tribe's leader's political power but Bu Su Lian was an exception.

This was not only because she was the spouse of a former tribe elder, but also because of her own talent and schemes.

But Bu Su Lian guessed wrongly in the end, Fang Yuan was not the creator, this song was originally from Earth.

"This song is unique and unheard of, it has to be a new creation by you. To think that you would have such high attainment in sound path, Fang Yuan." Xie Han Mo walked down the stage and transmitted to Fang Yuan, showing appreciation and praise in her tone.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "I am flattered, you saw for yourself, I even had to borrow a zither Gu, I do not have such a high sound path attainment."

"No need to be humble, being able to create such a song means that your sound path attainment is beyond ordinary, you might have a future if you change to cultivating sound path." Xie Han Mo looked at Fang Yuan with a sincere and bright gaze.

Fang Yuan had already anticipated this.

He did not want to explain it, because that was not important and he could not explain it clearly either.

"The important thing now are the next two songs, if I am not wrong…" Fang Yuan hesitated.

They walked down the stage as Dong Lei went up.

Fang Yuan and Xie Han Mo might have had an impressive performance, but she was not flustered, she remained calm and composed.

She started to sing, her moving voice attracted lots of fish groups to her.

"As expected." Fang Yuan snickered.

Xie Han Mo's gaze also became increasingly cold.

Both guards looked at each other with bright red faces: "This bitch stole our song again!"

"Don't worry, I have a song prepared." Fang Yuan smiled with deep confidence.

After Dong Lei went down the stage, the two of them went up again.

Fang Yuan played the music[1] while Xie Han Mo sang and danced.

…

When did the bright moon first appear? One raises a cup and asks the blue sky.

One does not know in the celestial palace, what year it is this evening.

…

Once the song started, the atmosphere changed, all of the mermen shut their eyes in enjoyment.

…

I wish to ride the wind and return there, yet I fear the jade towers; in a high dwelling, one cannot bear the cold.

Starting to dance with one's own shadow, how can it compare to life in the mortal world?

The moon revolves around the red pavilion, hanging upon the silk windows, the light shines upon the sleepless.

…

Xie Han Mo thought about about the time she was saintess, even though she had high authority, she was all alone, she became filled with deep emotions at this moment.

I wish to return by riding the winds, but the position of saintess is like the jade tower that locks me in. The cold atmosphere is chilling, I cannot sleep, who is here to dance with me?

…

I should not have resentment; but why is the moon always full at times of separation?

People feel sorrow and joy upon partings and reunions, the moon can be dark or bright, full or crescent.

These problems have existed since ancient times. Yet one hopes for longevity, a thousand miles apart, seeing the moon's beauty together.

…

As the song ended, the world went silent.

Fish, prawns, turtles, crabs, all of the aquatic animals floated on the surface of the sea, scattered all over the place.

Birds were fluttering in the sky, many were birds that flew in the day, they were drawn over from their slumber by this beautiful song.

Beautiful lyrics and an enchanting tune, it pierced deep into everyone's hearts, the mermen could not help themselves but listen.

Xie Han Mo looked at Fang Yuan, she thought: "Was this a song he made for me?"

She could feel resonance in the lyrics, she felt consolation and warmth from it. She was pure like the icy jade, but was maligned by outsiders, right now, all of the sadness and annoyance in her heart had faded, none of the rumors from before could affect her heart anymore.

"He is someone who knows me." At once, Xie Han Mo felt an indescribable feeling in her heart, she was truly moved.

The results were clear, Fang Yuan and Xie Han Mo won by a margin again.

Dong Lei's face turned pale below the stage, she understood that if not for Xie Han Mo and Fang Yuan's imperfect cooperation that led to certain mistakes, she would not even be able to sing the third song.

"This person is a huge threat!" Frost Tide tribe's leader gritted his teeth, slamming his fist onto the window of the Gu house.

"You finally realized?" Bu Su Lian said plainly, mockery was in her words.

Frost Tide tribe's leader snorted, he did not want to argue with Bu Su Lian.

He needed to resolve this problem now, because at this rate, after the third song, Xie Han Mo was bound to win.

"Fang Yuan is it? To think he is such a problem!"

"I need to get rid of him!"

Frost Tide tribe's leader was determined to do this, but felt a huge headache. In normal times, he had countless methods against Fang Yuan, but now during the Sea God Ceremony, under everyone's watchful eyes, he could do close to nothing.

"What do I do?" Frost Tide tribe's leader thought about it rapidly, his forehead was covered in sweat.

After a long period of consideration, Frost Tide tribe's leader finally acted.

"Fang Yuan, I am Frost Tide tribe's leader!" He directly transmitted to Fang Yuan, this was the most useful choice of action.

Fang Yuan's expression changed but he did not reply.

Frost Tide tribe's leader chuckled: "You can just listen to me, I know you are a smart guy but you are too young, you have aspirations that are too unrealistic and naive."

Fang Yuan laughed coldly as he replied: "I am not naive, this is my ideal, you won't understand."

"That's why I said you are foolish, lad, don't think that you two are basking in fame now by standing there, you are just pawns. Look at the flag fluttering in the wind, its foundation is the pole. Think about it, what are you relying on?"

"The grand elder? Just go ask around, what kind of person is she? She had the political power to suppress our faction but she chose to let you people be the vanguard. When Xie Han Mo investigated the corruption case, did she help you? She might have given you some clues or what not, but trust me, it was really not much of an effort."

Frost Tide tribe's leader was quite eloquent, he added: "Or rather, even if you win and defend the title of saintess, so what? Do you think I will die? No, Frost Tide tribe is the largest faction in the Sacred Court, if I die, the entire Sacred Court will be in turmoil or even break apart. The grand elder does not have the guts or determination to do that, she only wants to keep me in check and prevent me from acting out of line."

"So in the end, no matter what you find out, I will still continue to live as Frost Tide tribe's leader, at worst, I will sacrifice a few scapegoats and stop my overbearing actions."

"In the Sea God Ceremony, almost every saintess candidate is backed by their own force. Do you think this is simply a competition for the saintess position? No, this is a game, this is a way for the higher-ups to distribute resources for the next few decades without internal conflict. The force that has a saintess will get a bigger share of the pie, those who don't will receive less."

"Fang Yuan, you might hate or detest these games that we play in the dark, but you must understand that in this sea, darkness is the true ruler. The so-called light merely shines at the surface of the sea, ordinary people might enjoy or indulge in its dazzling beauty, thinking that light is the truth of the sea, but they are just… too naive."

Fang Yuan was silent.

[1] Faye Wong - Wishing We Last Forever Back

Chapter 1669: Rejection

Inside the blue dragon whale grotto-heaven, the Merman Sacred City.

The atmosphere in the inn was heavy.

"What do we do?"

"In the next test, Zhao Lu's follower will be taking part. That person is famous in the seas, with him around, we have no chance of winning."

The two nannies had grim expressions.

White-scaled merman Su Yi sat at the center as she held a cup in her hand, she was in a daze while looking at the tea inside.

"Missy, you cannot hesitate anymore."

"That's right, the Sea God Ceremony has already gone on for so long, only us and Zhao Lu are left, the rest have been eliminated. After the next round is the final test, once we get past this hurdle, we will be able to vie for the saintess position."

The two nannies urged anxiously.

Su Yi sighed: "But what can we do now?"

The nannies quickly came forward to Su Yi's side.

"Missy, didn't our tribe find a strong expert that can fight against the enemy?"

"That's right, as long as we get him to fight, even if we cannot win, we will not get eliminated at least."

Su Yi's gaze was lingering on the cup, she said in a long sigh: "I understand your suggestion, but did you forget something, I can only have four followers in this competition, these spots are all used up now. Even if the tribe invites an expert, we cannot use him."

The two nannies looked at each other with bright gazes.

"So that's it, Missy had such plans already but she could not say it personally." They understood the reason now.

Among them, one nanny said in a soft voice: "Missy, this matter can be easy or difficult depending on us. We just need to abandon one follower!"

"That's right." The other nanny added: "According to the Sea God Ceremony's rules, we cannot abandon followers easily, but if they are corrupted or have committed crimes, for the purity of the Sea God Ceremony and the saintess, we can expel them with proper reason. With that freed follower position, we can then invite the expert into our group, right?"

Su Yi's expression changed as she rejected: "This is not appropriate. The Sea God Ceremony is such a huge event, if a scandal occurs, that person's reputation would be tarnished for life, they would never be able to clear their name. All of my followers have helped me greatly, how can I repay gratitude with enmity?"

"Oh Missy, a great person would not mind small sacrifices, so what if we have to give up someone?"

"I would suggest we target that Xia Lin. She has no background and is a mermaid that nobody will care about, who knows what luck she had to be able to obtain that gather oil Gu." Seeing Su Yi's displeasure, Nanny Rong added: "Of course, we are not framing her, we are trying to move her with logic, Xia Lin looks like an understanding young lady after all. Missy, leave this to me, I will negotiate with her, it is okay if we pay a small price. Compared to the saintess position, it is evident which is more important!"

"This…" Su Yi hesitated.

The other nanny quickly added: "Missy, we are not forcing or harming Xia Lin. We are seeking her cooperation, in any case, so what if she loses some reputation? Xia Lin is a poor girl, she needs some materialistic gains more. It is very likely that after hearing our suggestion, she might become very happy and would want to deal with us, she is merely trading reputation for huge benefits!"

"Leave, let me consider it first…" Su Yi frowned as she asked them to leave.

The two nannies looked at each other before leaving.

Days later, rumors regarding Xia Lin spread throughout the city.

"That's her, the shameless mermaid who betrayed her benefactor Su Yi just to gain the favor of the rich and noble!"

"No wonder Lady Su Yi was always at a disadvantage, she had a traitor after all."

"I want nothing more than to tear the tendons and skin out of this scoundrel."

"She is truly shameless, I can't believe she is still coming to find Su Yi at this time!"

Xia Lin bit her lips, walking up the inn's stairs under everyone's accusations.

"Stand there." Halfway through, mermaid Nanny Rong blocked Xia Lin with a cold expression.

"I was framed, I want to see Sister Su Yi!" Xia Lin raised her head, looking at Nanny Rong with an anxious expression.

Nanny Rong laughed coldly: "Xia Lin, you still want to act? Missy was very upset after hearing the news, you still want to see her now during a crucial moment of the Sea God Ceremony? You are truly vicious, you want to annoy our Missy and cause her to make mistakes in the competition later?"

"That's not it, Nanny Rong, listen to me…"

"Listen to what? What is there to say! You are a shameless scum, we were blind to accept you into our group. Scram!" Nanny Rong lost her patience, she screamed in a shrill voice, being very overbearing.

"You don't believe me but I believe in Sister Su Yi, if I don't get to see her, I will not leave!" Xia Lin's eyes were red, a light of stubbornness flickered in them.

"You are forcing me to chase you away?" Nanny Rong said sinisterly.

"Stop." At this time, Su Yi appeared, walking down the stairs.

"Sister Su Yi!" Xia Lin was overjoyed, she wanted to move forward but Nanny Rong's arms blocked her path.

"Xia Lin…" Su Yi said to Xia Lin with a complex tone.

"Sister Su Yi, you need to believe me, I did not betray you!" Xia Lin shouted.

"Do you need us to investigate it?" At this moment, a group of mermen charged into the inn, they drew all the attention away.

This group of mermen walked towards Xia Lin as they said: "Xia Lin right? I am the Sacred City's investigator, someone reported you for corruption, you betrayed Su Yi and tried to ruin the sacred Sea God Ceremony, you tried to manipulate the saintess' competition. We are now arresting you, follow us and tell us everything that you did."

"No, I am innocent!" Xia Lin turned pale from fright, she shouted loudly in retaliation.

"We will investigate whether you are innocent or not." The investigator was very cold.

"No, I will not leave with you, I was framed, someone framed me!" Xia Lin was frightful, she continued to shake her head.

"You don't want to leave with us? Hmph, you don't have a choice! Come, arrest her!" The investigator ordered as the merman Gu Masters behind him acted.

"Wait." At this moment, Su Yi spoke.

"Sister Su Yi!" Xia Lin's eyes shined with a light of hope.

But Su Yi shook her head: "Sister Xia Lin, I do not believe that you betrayed me, but the investigator is here, we need to believe in Sacred City's justice! I believe that they will clear your name, go with them, as long as the results come out, your innocence will be proven, right?"

"Sister Su Yi…" Xia Lin's eyes turned dim.

"Go, go with them."

Xia Lin lowered her head, walking towards the investigator: "I was framed, but I will go with you."

The investigator nodded in satisfaction: "That's right, come with us."

Xia Lin was quickly brought into the interrogation room.

"These information path Gu worms are all evidence, take a good look, I will give you some advice, don't think you can get out of this!" The investigator smiled sinisterly, pointing at the information path mortal Gu on the table.

Xia Lin looked into them one by one.

Soon, shock was expressed all over her face: "These videos and voices are all fake, I have never said such things!"

"That is your explanation against all this evidence? Who would believe you?!" The investigator chuckled.

"I have never said such things! I…" Xia Lin was anxious.

The investigator raised his arm, stopping Xia Lin from talking, he smiled: "I know you were framed."

Xia Lin was stunned: "What, what did you say?"

"You were framed." The investigator repeated himself.

Xia Lin was stunned, she blinked before saying: "In that case, why did you…"

"Because this was Lady Su Yi's request." The investigator laughed again.

"What do you mean? Don't try to sow discord between us!" Xia Lin was enraged.

"You are truly a naive little girl. Let me explain it to you then. You know who Lady Su Yi's father is right? Do you know the current situation of the Sea God Ceremony…"

The investigator spoke as Xia Lin went into deep shock upon hearing his words.

After a long while, she reacted: "I do not believe that this is sister Su Yi's plot! If she wants me to step down, I can leave. If she told me herself, I would not have rejected her."

The investigator looked at Xia Lin with a mocking expression, rebuking mercilessly: "Is the Sea God Ceremony an event where you can just leave like that? If anyone could just step down, this competition would just be a pure contest between forces. The only way to step down is by force, at the same time, that position left behind could be filled again."

Xia Lin said in a daze: "A situation like this…"

The investigator smiled: "Indeed, you've grown smarter. Alright, you have two choices now, the first choice is to deny this evidence and fight for your innocence. But this evidence is concrete, nobody will believe your words."

"The second choice is to cooperate with us, admit to the crime and even though you will lose reputation, we will repay you with abundant resources. Choose now."

Xia Lin smiled bitterly, lowering her head.

Did she have a choice?

The other party tricked her into this interrogation room, at this point, she could no longer reject them.

Even if she tried to, she would still be framed and trialled as guilty.

She did not have the strength to resist them, she did not have the right to reject them!

Silence.

After a long silence.

The investigator spoke: "Xia Lin, if you keep silent any longer, I will take it that you accept our proposition. The facts are simple and clear, I believe a smart person will make a wise choice. This benefits both of us, isn't that right?"

"I reject the offer." Xia Lin suddenly raised her head as she spoke.

Chapter 1670: Racing Heart

"Reject?" The investigator frowned, a cold light flickered in his eyes and his tone became much tougher: "Young lady, think properly. You are young, you should not be impulsive, you need to know the weak cannot contend with the strong, let alone that you can't even be considered weak."

"I know I have no one to rely on, I am just a small character, which was why you all targeted me, isn't that so?" Xia Lin looked straight at the investigator, her tone was filled with mockery but also bitterness and helplessness: "But you don't have to worry, I won't make a useless retaliation or file a complaint. I accept your false accusation, I will consider it as paying back Sister Su Yi's kindness. I don't want any compensation, from now on, we no longer have any debt to each other, we will just be strangers."

The investigator revealed a surprised expression as he looked at Xia Lin firmly. In the dim room, Xia Lin's eyes seemed to shine brightly. This pair of bright eyes directly shined on the investigator's heart, making him unable to match her gaze!

He quickly moved his gaze: "You can leave, I hope you can uphold what you said."

"I will." Xia Lin stood up and left with a calm expression that contained no anxiety.

Several days later.

"Lady Xia Lin, it is not that our inn does not want to do business with you but that the public sentiment is too fierce and many people have made reports. If we continue to let you stay here, they will…" The innkeeper said with a bitter expression.

Xia Lin stopped him from continuing the story: "I understand your situation, I will leave then."

"I thank you for the understanding, Lady Xia Lin, you truly are a good person." The innkeeper said as he thanked profusely and gratefully.

Xia Lin packed up her luggage and left her room, walking down the stairs.

"Look, it is her!"

"This woman secretly betrayed Lady Su Yi for her own personal gains."

"This kind of person is simply tarnishing the Sea God Ceremony and our Sacred City."

The Gu Masters inside the hall saw Xia Lin and started discussing while pointing fingers at her.

Xia Lin heard them but walked out of the inn with a calm and composed expression.

When she arrived at the wide main street, a bustling tide of people was moving along the path.

"Today is the day of the second last test of the Sea God Ceremony."

"I can barely wait, today is sure to be spectacular!"

"Do you guys know? Su Yi had been in a disadvantageous position for so long because there was a spy by her side."

"Who does not know of it? It's Xia Lin! As the saying goes, no matter how vigilant one is, they cannot defend against an internal threat."

…

Most of the people did not recognize Xia Lin, their attention was on the Sea God Ceremony as they hurried towards the central square.

Even if some people recognized Xia Lin, they were not absolutely certain. The Sacred City was extremely crowded at this time, it was normal for there to be one or two people with similar appearances.

The atmosphere was bustling, the people were jostling through the street as joy filled everyone.

Xia Lin mixed in with the crowd, her expression was tranquil, a stark contrast with her surroundings.

She had felt happy before, but now, it was like layers of heavy mist had gathered in her nostrils, making her feel difficulty in breathing.

She could no longer feel happy in this Sacred City or satisfy her curiosity.

"Maybe, I will never come here again in my life." Xia Lin raised her head slightly, looking at the tall buildings.

These buildings seemed to be slanting down, the whole Sacred City seemed to be pressing towards her.

Xia Lin felt increasingly depressed and frustrated, she quickened her pace and left the crowd, walking into a dark alley.

The alley was dim and dark, trash was piled up in corners, spreading stench throughout the alley.

Xia Lin, however, felt her breathing become much smoother as if a huge weight had been lifted out of her heart.

Walking in this dark alley devoid of people, Xia Lin's raised head drooped slowly.

"How did I reach this state?" She asked herself but obtained no answer.

Her eyes reddened and she soon turned tearful.

She was still a young girl, her previous strong attitude was just a facade.

"Hello, young lady!" Three mermen suddenly walked out of a corner of the alley.

Xia Lin was dazed for a moment before turning vigilant.

These three mermen were hooligans, their ill intentions were clearly exposed by their gazes. More importantly, every one of them was a rank two Gu Master.

Xia Lin was also only rank two.

"What do you want?" Xia Lin took a step back.

"What do we want? Hehehe!" The three mermen looked at each other, laughing deviously at the same time.

"Young lady, our encounter was fated, why be in a hurry to leave?"

"Even if you want to leave now, it is too late."

At this moment, two rank two merman Gu Masters walked towards Xia Lin from behind.

Xia Lin's heart sank, not only was it five against one, both the front and rear paths were blocked. Although this alley was not far from the main street, these people were all Gu Masters and had clearly been lying in ambush; they definitely had methods to suppress the commotion.

The five mermen approached Xia Lin menacingly.

Xia Lin was panicking, she retreated again and again till her back touched the wall.

The cold wall made her feel even more helpless.

She gritted her teeth, her brows rose as she suddenly said: "Come, even if I die, I will drag you down with me."

"Oh dear, the little girl has guts!"

"Quite fiery, big brother likes such girls."

The five mermen giggled in amusement, they showed no fear but their footsteps had slowed down.

Bump.

Suddenly, Xia Lin felt an intense dizziness.

She was attacked!

Her mind was filled with fright as she turned to look back with difficulty, she saw the wall melt down from which the sixth merman Gu Master walked out.

"They got me!" The moment before she fell unconscious, Xia Lin's heart turned cold.

"She is down…"

"Hahaha, boss, your method is truly amazing!"

"Quickly clean up this place, the Sea God Ceremony is currently ongoing after all!"

The six mermen gathered around Xia Lin.

"Wake up, wake up…" A deep voice lingered in the darkness.

Xia Lin slowly opened her eyes, the alley was once again reflected in her eyes. The pain behind her head reminded her, she got a fright and quickly struggled to stand up.

She then saw the six mermen lying on the ground motionless in strange postures.

A human Gu Master was standing in the middle of the six mermen.

Xia Lin cried out with joy: "Master Chu, it's you!"

"It's me. I have been observing the Sea God Ceremony from the start, I heard of your matter as well, you were tossed aside by Su Yi, right?" Fang Yuan slightly smiled.

Xia Lin's tear immediately started to fall as she sobbed: "Master Chu, you…"

"I have good judgment of people, although I have only met you a few times, you are not that kind of person." Fang Yuan continued.

Xia Lin could not hold it in anymore as she covered her face and started crying, like a wronged child finally getting vindicated.

Fang Yuan quietly watched her cry for sometime before patting her shoulder: "Let's go."

"To where?" Xia Lin was slightly dazed.

"I am also slightly responsible for your current situation." Fang Yuan sighed: "If I did not give you gather oil Gu, you would not have been targeted by Su Yi and participated in this Sea God Ceremony. So, I am taking you with me, follow me and leave."

"Okay." Xia Lin nodded, she no longer had no interest in Sacred City.

Fang Yuan led the way while Xia Lin obediently followed behind him.

At the end of the alley, there was another branch of the main street, it was also crowded with the stores at the sides enjoying bustling business. At the center of the street, there was a lion dance team.

Facing the crowd again, Xia Lin immediately felt some fear and disgust, but Fang Yuan had already walked ahead so she could only follow.

Snap.

The moment they walked out of the alley, Fang Yuan snapped his fingers.

The next scene stupefied Xia Lin, her mouth opened so wide that it could swallow an egg. She shockingly saw the whole street coming to a standstill.

"This, this…" She was unable to speak.

"Just a small trick, come." Fang Yuan waved towards her before entering the crowd.

Xia Lin quickened her pace, following behind closely.

This was a wondrous situation that she had never experienced before!

She walked right past two mermen who looked like they were having a close conversation and seemed to be lovers. She looked at a store where a customer seemed to be haggling price with the clerk, spittle flew out of the clerk's mouth and was suspended in the air, almost landing on the customer's face.

There was a dog which was moving past the tightly packed legs and merman tails. Its body was bent as it was moving around a blue scaled merman, its three legs were raised high while one was on the ground.

Xia Lin stared widely at these people with various lives, the liveliness in them made her forget her depression and frustration.

Fang Yuan was extremely agile and walked quite quickly, it was quite tiring for Xia Lin to follow him.

Bump.

In a moment of carelessness, she bumped into a sturdy human Gu Master.

The human Gu Master swayed, his posture was still the same walking posture from before but his feet had almost left the ground, he started tilting to the side.

"Sorry!" She was just about to prop up this human Gu Master when she was grabbed by Fang Yuan.

"Here." Fang Yuan gave her a mask.

"Master Chu, this…" Xia Lin was puzzled, Fang Yuan did not lead her away from the street but brought her in front of that lion dance team.

The mask that Fang Yuan gave her was colorful and made from fish scales and bird feathers.

Fang Yuan pointed to the lion dance team: "Don't you think it lacks two key characters?"

Xia Lin nodded: "They are playing the sea lion winter spring opera, they are short of the male and female leading characters, a filial fisherman and a traveling mermaid princess. But I think this performance was a spontaneous idea, they are not a real opera team, it is normal for them to not have all the characters."

Likely at the start, one Gu Master put on the opera costume and makeup for his own entertainment. Later, along the way, more Gu Masters joined in.

These people were generally opera fans and loved such culture.

In fact, there were all kinds of traditional opera and plays that existed in the grotto-heaven, it was the trending entertainment of this paradise.

"My method can only last for a short while, put on the mask quickly, we will move with the crowd." Fang Yuan hurried Xia Lin, not giving her the chance to refuse.

"Oh, okay." Xia Lin subconsciously took the mask and when she wore it, her heart suddenly calmed down.

No one would recognize her like this.

The mental pressure on her had greatly reduced.

But shortly afterwards, her face blushed. Because she saw Fang Yuan wear a mask and it was the mask of the filial fisherman.

"Doesn't this mean that Master Chu and I are the main male and female characters?"

Xia Lin's heart started to race wildly!

Chapter 1671: Life and Mask

Snap.

Fang Yuan snapped his fingers once again.

The surroundings immediately started moving again from the motionless state.

That merman couple continued to walk forward while holding hands.

Amidst the haggling at the stall, the saliva spit landed on the customer's face but he did not realize it.

The small dog's three legs landed on the ground, it smoothly moved past the blue scaled merman and continued to pass nimbly through the crowd of legs.

Xia Lin took everything in with surprise and curiosity.

This was too magical!

"Master Chu's methods are truly powerful! This is probably a rank five time path killer move."

Xia Lin guessed.

Plop.

That male Gu Master, who Xia Lin had collided into, fell down to the ground and even affected the person behind, creating a small chaos.

"You are so big, don't you know how to walk?" Someone scolded.

"Sorry, sorry." The well-built male Gu Master politely apologized. This was, after all, the Sacred City of the mermen, meanwhile, the people in this paradise were less irritable than in the five regions.

"I was walking properly, how could I trip? Strange." The male Gu Master looked puzzled as he quickly stood up and moved with the crowd.

Xia Lin apologized softly while gazing at the receding figure of the male Gu Master.

However, she felt a bit of joy like that of a prankster. Just as she was about to criticize herself, her hand was grabbed by Fang Yuan.

"Follow me!" Fang Yuan dragged her to the lion dance team.

The lion dance team was stunned at first before dancing even more joyfully, the accompanying music was immediately raised.

"We have all the characters now, haha!" One dancer laughed heartily.

"You know how to dance, right?" Fang Yuan smiled and moved his legs, he was playing the role of the filial fisherman, his movements were subtle and natural, having their own beauty.

The surrounding people immediately cheered and hooted, Fang Yuan followed the crowd while dancing towards Xia Lin.

"Your turn." Fang Yuan's voice was secretly transmitted to Xia Lin's ears.

Xia Lin's heart was beating loudly from nervousness. Despite her practising this play often when she was a child, she had never performed before a large crowd.

She began to dance with stiff movements.

Fang Yuan laughed as he took her hands and led her.

He secretly used wisdom path methods, Xia Lin immediately started feeling nimble, all kinds of dance postures of this play surfaced in her mind with extreme clarity.

The two sang and danced and moved along with the crowd.

The lion dance team was wearing colorful costumes and strange-looking masks. There were also some who jointly acted as an enormous golden sea lion. They attracted attention wherever they moved.

And as the male and female protagonists of the team, even more eyes were focused on Fang Yuan and Xia Lin.

Xia Lin was extremely tense at the start but the more she danced, the better and more confident she felt. She was immersed in the joyful atmosphere, forgetting about the injustice she suffered as cheers, shouts, and whistling filled her ears.

Even when Xia Lin made some mistakes in her movements, there was only kind laughter.

The crowd continued to move, some left the lion dance team while some joined.

Unknowingly, Xia Lin started laughing brightly.

An unprecedented level of happiness which she had never felt before in the Sacred City filled her heart.

She was immersed in this happiness, unable to extricate herself from it. At the same time, she felt fear that this was not real.

"It truly is like I am dreaming!" Xia Lin's heart was filled with emotions, her gaze never leaving Fang Yuan.

"Time to leave." Suddenly, Fang Yuan's movements changed, he dragged Xia Lin away from the opera team and walked to the side of the street.

Xia Lin was caught unprepared and got pulled directly into Fang Yuan's embrace.

She bumped into Fang Yuan's chest, a strong manly smell entered her nose. She quickly held the mask that had almost fallen down, hiding her reddened face.

"Here." Fang Yuan moved quickly while pulling her, walking into an alley.

It was another lonely alley with dim lighting and the stench of garbage.

Fang Yuan released Xia Lin's hand and quickly walked ahead.

Xia Lin immediately felt an empty feeling as she followed behind.

The two moved in the long alley, one in front and another in back. Fang Yuan did not utter a sound, the alley echoing his monotonous footsteps.

The sounds from the rowdy street became softer and softer as they moved further into the alley.

A lonely and cold feeling pervaded Xia Lin's body and heart.

The previous happiness and joyful feelings started disappearing from Xia Lin's heart. Gradually, worries began to find her once again, and her previous depression began to surge.

Xia Lin wanted to find some topics to talk with Fang Yuan, but Fang Yuan had been moving ahead without even turning his head back. The oppressive atmosphere made Xia Lin not dare to casually speak.

Finally, they reached the exit of the alley.

The street here, although not as lively as the previous, was also filled with crowds and was boisterous.

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped and turned towards Xia Lin: "Have you thought it through?"

Xia Lin was stunned: "Thought… thought what through?"

Fang Yuan smiled, pointing at the mask Xia Lin was wearing: "Do you want to wear it to cross the street or do you want to walk in the crowd showing your own face?"

Xia Lin was stunned again.

Fang Yuan continued: "I took off my mask when I entered the alley, but you are still wearing it. Why? Do you feel ashamed? Do you feel afraid of looking at people with your face? Worried that if you confront life, you will lose the happiness from earlier?"

A series of questions caught Xia Lin unprepared and unable to reply.

After a while of silence, she seemed to have understood something as she took down the mask, revealing her face: "Master Chu, I understand your intentions, thank you, I truly thank you. I am only an ordinary mermaid…"

Fang Yuan stretched out his hand, interrupting her: "I have said it before, your current situation is largely because of me, I need to compensate you for this."

"Master, what are you saying? You have shown enormous kindness to me by gifting me gather oil Gu. You don't owe me anything at all, in fact, it is I who owes you everything!" Xia Lin quickly said.

"That is how you interpret it, not me." Fang Yuan shook his head, his expression turning solemn: "Look back on it, you were previously taunted and jeered by others, but just earlier, you were showered with welcomes and cheers, what is the reason for such a big difference? Could it because of this mask? But in fact, you had been yourself all along, isn't that so?"

Xia Lin nodded.

Fang Yuan looked at the street outside the alley and pointed at the passing crowd: "Take a look now, these people don't want to inspect your true self and who Xia Lin truly is. When we were dancing and singing, they also did not want to know our names. They are only expressing their attitude, the true situation is not important to them. Ordinary people chase after the truth because they are usually angry and indignant about being made a fool of."

"So to them, we are not important at all, and to us, their attitude should similarly not be important."

Xia Lin took a deep breath: "Master Chu, thank you for comforting me, I truly can't thank you enough…"

"I have not finished speaking. Since the attitude of outsiders is not important, what is truly important in our lives?" Fang Yuan asked with a smile.

Xia Lin was stunned for the third time: "Master, forgive my ignorance…"

Fang Yuan pointed at Xia Lin and then pointed at himself: "It is us, ourselves. It is our truest feelings. Ask yourself, listen to the voice in the depths of your heart. What do you want to do, what kind of person you want to become, where do you want to go? You will obtain the answer in the depths of your heart."

"If you want to travel, then travel around the world. If you want to treat others well, then treat them properly. If you want to attempt flying, then collect money and resources to purchase and practice flying Gu worms."

Fang Yuan pointed at the alley then at the street: "If you want to remain in the alley, you can stay. If you want to walk into the street and enjoy the event with others, then walk out. Don't mistreat your own feelings because of their attitude. If you mistreat yourself frequently, then you will end up with regrets, you will constantly wear a mask to act as another person, you will no longer be yourself."

The moment she heard that, Xia Lin felt that her mind had cleared up, it was as if she received enlightenment, all her previous worries and distress were swept away entirely.

Chapter 1672: Stop Being So Naive

"Master, I will never forget your guidance in my life!" The mermaid took a step back and bowed solemnly towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "My efforts were not in vain. But sometimes, it is easier said than done, I'll ask you now, what is it that you want to do the most at this moment?"

Xia Lin hesitated.

"I want to follow you!" This was the first thing that popped up in her mind.

But before she spoke, she saw Fang Yuan shaking his head: "You still haven't thought properly, you have time to think about it later. Actually, I am not concerned about what you want to do. Do you know what I want to do?"

Xia Lin shook her head, but at the next moment, her eyes opened wide and her body stiffened.

Because Fang Yuan had slowly stretched out his hand and stroked her face.

Thump thump thump thump thump!

Xia Lin's face blushed red, her heart thumped wildly, and watery ripples appeared in her eyes.

She felt Fang Yuan's wide palm and the warmth from it, this feeling was like a slight electric shock that transmitted to her body and mind. It was clearly an ordinary action but Xia Lin was unable to even budge.

Fang Yuan took back his hand: "You still have a mask on."

Xia Lin was puzzled but she heard Fang Yuan speak: "Sometimes, we wear a mask of our own initiative, sometimes, others force us to wear a mask. Right now, I want to take away the mask on your face, cooperate with me, okay?"

"Mas… master, you don't need…" Xia Lin vaguely knew what Fang Yuan wanted to do as she stuttered.

Fang Yuan shook his hand: "I will not be happy unless I take this mask off. I don't want to betray my feelings, since you feel that you owe me, then cooperate with me as compensation, okay?"

How could Xia Lin refuse after hearing this?

She knelt on the ground and made three kowtows to Fang Yuan before quietly standing up: "Master Chu, I will do whatever you want me to do!"

"Okay, then become the saintess."

"What?!"

Several days later.

The Sea God Ceremony's final test had gathered the attention of everyone.

Su Yi was looking at Xia Lin with shock as if she had seen a ghost.

The two nannies were also stunned.

Following the grand elder's explanation, the crowd went into a commotion.

Su Yi was very confident of victory because her competitor had suffered heavy injuries in the previous round and was unable to step up to compete in such a short duration.

But who could have thought that a surprise would occur.

The competitor's younger sister who had been separated for many years was found, it was this mermaid, Xia Lin!

"Isn't this too melodramatic?"

"Unbelievable!"

"Xia Lin… isn't she the person who betrayed Su Yi for her own gains?"

"That is a lie that Su Yi's supporters spread intentionally. The true reason is that Su Yi wanted to free up a follower quota. I heard that investigator pleaded guilty, his conversation where he pressured Xia Lin was recorded and is ironclad evidence!"

"This is more dramatic than an opera play."

The discussions among the audience became more heated.

The two nannies conversed secretly:

"What is going on?"

"How did the public sentiment change all of a sudden?"

"Also, we never arranged for the investigator, why did he admit guilt for no reason?"

Su Yi's expression was extremely unsightly, while Xia Lin was calmly looking at the crowd. Fang Yuan's guidance had elevated her mind and spirit to another level.

Su Yi felt even more stifled when she saw that Xia Lin did not even look at her, she snorted coldly: "Xia Lin, I truly didn't think we would meet again and in this way."

"I also didn't expect this." Xia Lin looked at Su Yi and said honestly. The huge setbacks and gains that she experienced over these days felt like a dream.

Su Yi snorted once again: "No matter what scheme you have, this last test is not something a casually selected mermaid can pass. This Sea God Ceremony's saintess position is mine."

"Oh." Xia Lin lightly replied.

Su Yi felt like her provocation had ended up hitting air, she felt terribly irritated.

Xia Lin scanned through the surrounding crowd once again, there were too many people.

"Master Chu said he will watch me from the crowd. But where is he? I am not able to find him at all. Could he have disguised his appearance? He has vast mystical prowess, if he wants to hide, I will never be able to find him."

"After this matter is over, I will tell him I want to follow him. I wonder if he will agree?"

Xia Lin's mind lingered on this question, compared to the answer to this question, the saintess position did not have any attraction to her.

In the first round, Xia Lin was slightly better than Su Yi.

In the second round, Xia Lin won against Su Yi by a little.

This result greatly surpassed expectations, causing the audience to be in a commotion, everyone revealed shock.

Fang Yuan, who was hiding among the audience, looked shocked like the surrounding people, but his heart was tranquil.

He had trained Xia Lin over these days, using immortal level time path methods to gain a large amount of time to train her to a certain level.

Along with Fang Yuan's personally chosen songs, which were unique, and the sound path Gu worms he prepared specially for Xia Lin.

Moreover, when Su Yi and Xia Lin stepped on the stage to sing, Fang Yuan had even secretly tampered and influenced their performances. The former's performance became choppy while the latter's performance became increasingly better due to his support.

"Besides us outsiders, there is probably no Gu Immortal in this grotto-heaven. Now that I am using immortal level methods, is there any worry that I can't control this grand ceremony of mortal Gu Masters?"

"What should we do? The third round is about to start." The two nannies were sweating from anxiety, they were sent by the clan to specially assist Su Yi. If Su Yi did not get the saintess position, they would have to suffer the punishment.

Su Yi was pale as she looked at Xia Lin.

Everything felt like a dream!

As far as Su Yi was concerned, Xia Lin was a dull and ordinary girl. It was only because she possessed gather oil Gu and was a mermaid that Su Yi had used her.

Although she had not felt comfortable doing this to Xia Lin, she did not feel like it was a huge deal.

Even if Xia Lin wanted to take revenge, what revenge could she take? She, a person with no background and only rank two cultivation, wasn't she asking for others to use her?

If not for the saintess position being in sight and Su Yi not wanting to divert her attention, she would have taken the chance to scheme for Xia Lin's rank five Gu worm.

This was not considered repaying kindness with enmity!

Could a rank two Gu Master protect a rank five Gu worm?

A person's wealth is their own ruin by causing another's greed.

So, to Su Yi, rather than Xia Lin being killed by others in the future, it was better to persuade Xia Lin to offer gather oil Gu to the clan of her own initiative. Like this, her own side would obtain benefits and she would also not die, it could also be considered as Su Yi helping her.

This was a small plan in Su Yi's mind. But, as the saintess position was too important, Su Yi did not dare to split her attention and also did not want to attract criticism, so she could only spare Xia Lin for the moment.

If it were before and someone told her Xia Lin would be her biggest obstacle in becoming the saintess, Su Yi would have replied with only a chuckle: Hehe.

Now though, Su Yi wanted to say 'hehe' to herself, life was truly too cruel.

With Fang Yuan personally forging a fake identity for Xia Lin, who would be able to see through it?

Nobody in this huge Sacred City could!

So this evidence which proved Xia Lin's identity was irrefutable and ironclad. Even Su Yi believed Xia Lin's identity was truly like so.

"Oh destiny, this is truly too big of a joke." Su Yi heaved a deep sigh.

"Young miss, what should we do?" The two nannies were out of ideas.

"We cannot do anything in front of such a large crowd, we also don't have the time. There is only one option left, I will personally persuade her." Su Yi remained silent for a while before uttering through clenched teeth.

She transmitted her voice to Xia Lin: "Xia Lin, I am Su Yi."

Xia Lin was surprised, but her expression calmed down quickly as she replied: "What's the matter?"

Su Yi organized her thoughts and said: "I want to make a deal with you, lose the next round and let me be the saintess. I swear in the name of the Sea God that I will pay a price that will satisfy you completely. Even if my power is not enough, my family will be able to satisfy you."

Xia Lin remained silent for a moment before saying: "Sorry but I…."

"Don't be in a hurry to reject me, Xia Lin. You are too young, maybe you still don't recognize the significance of the saintess position. What do you think the saintess is? Just a belief? Or a superficial selection? Both are wrong! It involves benefits, it involves the interests of the whole Sacred City's higher-ups, this is a political game."

"I know you want to take revenge against me, but do you know your situation is extremely dangerous right now. Once you become the saintess, you will be in an even bigger danger. Your elder sister's side pushed you to the stage because they did not have other candidates, so they are only putting up a front. Once you become the saintess, they will use all their strength to make you into their puppet, they will make you do things that match their benefits."

"Although I have not been in much contact with you, I understand you. You are pure and kind, if you become the saintess, you will probably try to fight for benefits of the mermen and mermaids. But you definitely won't succeed because you are not a person of any political force, you are just an outsider. Unless you join one of the forces and become the representative of their benefits, or else you will be excluded by everyone and will become the most powerless saintess in history."

"But if you choose to transact with me, the benefits you will obtain will surpass your imagination. It will be much more than the benefits you can obtain from your elder sister's side. Please believe in my sincerity!"

Su Yi had an amazingly eloquent tongue, even Xia Lin felt moved.

But she replied: "Lady Su Yi, I understand your sincerity, but I cannot agree to you in this matter."

"Why?" Su Yi's tone was hurried: "You think I am deceiving you? Although it is cruel, what I have said are all truthful. Stop being so… so naive, okay?"

Xia Lin remained silent.

Chapter 1673: Gu Yue Fang Yuan

Fang Yuan's first life of five hundred years.

Sea God Ceremony.

Naive?

Facing Frost Tide tribe's leader's long-winded speech, Fang Yuan fell into silence.

But he only fell silent for a short period before he chuckled and transmitted his voice: "You think I am not aware of what you said? You think I am an inexperienced youngster? No, I understand all these tricks, clearly in fact. I know these truths and have accepted them."

Fang Yuan was forced to leave Qing Mao Mountain, wandering about in Southern Border before going to Western Desert and then to Eastern Sea. He struggled at the border of death, he had to worry about one or two primeval stones. He had to bow down and grovel before the strong and this destitute life. He had also once gained a high status, listening to reports from his subordinates while drinking tea.

He had been lowly, he had been glorious, he had been lofty, he had been ordinary.

Considering his life on Earth and the experiences after crossing over to this world, his vision was already beyond normal people, his experiences were plentiful, and he was very knowledgeable.

How could such a person not understand these worldly affairs?

Frost Tide tribe's leader was frustrated, replying quickly: "Since you know these truths, then you should know you are taking great risks now! This is our merman internal political battle, what are you, a weak human Gu Master, doing by meddling? You like Xie Han Mo? I can guarantee that after this matter is finished, I will gift you many more beautiful mermaids! Don't doubt my sincerity, I can swear an oath to the Sea God!"

"There is indeed no need to doubt the sincerity of a merman who swears an oath to the Sea God. But…" Fang Yuan continued: "Although I accept these truths, it does not mean I like them. You think I like Xie Han Mo? No, no, I only want to help her. Why am I taking such risks to help her? Because I have my own principle, favors must be repaid, hatred must be returned."

"I have used lifespan Gu, I have lived much longer than you can imagine. I used to wish for a long life before, but now, I am tired of this thought. Life has become increasingly boring. Sometimes, the final destination of the journey is not important, the important thing is the process of the journey and how you feel during the journey."

Frost Tide tribe's leader involuntarily opened his eyes wide at these words, it was hard for him to understand Fang Yuan's way of life: "You are saying the position of saintess is not important, the important thing is helping Xie Han Mo in this competition?"

"Correct, but there is still more. You talked of the dark side of politics and promised to gift me mermaid beauties, both have no importance to me. Let me put it this way so you might understand a little, I have lived long enough that I am already sick of wearing a mask to live. Death is not scary to me at all. Right now, I only want to live using my truest emotions and feelings, I will achieve my goals in my own way. Only by living like this can I feel the excitement of life and the desire towards living!"

Frost Tide tribe's leader was dumbstruck and stupefied, he finally understood as he shouted: "So that's it, you are a lunatic! You have said so much but they are nothing more than saying you have lived long enough and don't want to live anymore! So be it you were a Gu Immortal, but you, a mere rank three Gu Master, want to live life your own way? You are dreaming!"

Fang Yuan smiled: "You think becoming a Gu Immortal can allow people to live according to their will? Live without wearing a mask? A place with people has society and conflict. Survival and living are two different things. The way you want to live does not have to depend on your strength and cultivation level, but your own heart."

After a brief pause, Fang Yuan continued: "Actually, low strength is also quite interesting. When you live without a mask, low strength will allow you to face more difficulties and challenges of reality; surpass these difficulties, face these challenges, and life becomes much more wonderful."

Frost Tide tribe's leader stood stupefied, his eyes and mouth were wide open as he was unable to say anything!

His sight moved across the crowd of people, landing on Fang Yuan, he saw a slight smile. A chill rose in his heart: This person has such strange and deviant thoughts that differ from common logic, he has an inclination towards self destruction. He has likely turned demonic!

It would not matter if he did not play by the rules, the more terrifying thing was he did not think according to the rules. His thought process was completely different from ordinary people, he was already too far away from the norm!

This was a demon!

"This is a true demon!" Frost Tide tribe's leader felt a chill. He felt this was Fang Yuan's true nature, even though Fang Yuan did not wantonly slaughter lives, even though Fang Yuan currently still committed acts of kindness like repaying favors!

Frost Tide tribe's leader felt a deep powerlessness at the same time.

If it were an inexperienced youngster, he could have disguised himself as a senior to guide him and let him know the complexities and some dark truths of society.

But Fang Yuan understood them well, he almost knew everything way too clearly. What made him even more helpless was that Fang Yuan's thoughts completely differed from others!

"He is too strong-minded and stubborn. He clearly only has rank three cultivation, how dare he? Unreasonable, unreasonable! A lunatic, a madman! He is too arrogant, he actually shows contempt for life and death!! Right… he does not even fear death, what would he not dare to do? All the wealth, beauties and status in the world might be useless when compared to his own true feelings! What else do I have to entice him?"

Frost Tide tribe's leader was going crazy.

The more he thought, the more he realized, the more he knew Fang Yuan had no fear and would not be enticed. There might be a day when he is enticed, but it would be because he himself wanted to be enticed and it would be his genuine intention.

It was not easy for people to live in this world!

That was the case for mermen as well.

Frost Tide tribe's leader had high authority and status, but it was even harder for him.

The elders of merman Sacred City were pressuring him from above, while many of his subordinates were scheming against each other or coveting his position. He had a lot of children who were looking for power and authority, and there were deep conflicts between his many wives. Everything required his supervision and arrangements.

Was it wrong for him to be corrupt?

No!

What was corruption?

Corruption was no more than obtaining more benefits and these benefits made other benefit holders feel unfair.

It was similar to dividing a cake, in normal cases, you take a piece and I take a piece. Now, I secretly took another piece which made you jealous. You complain: "You broke our distribution agreement, what gives you the rights to take so much?"

This was corruption.

Did you think the grand elder's side which supports the saintess was not corrupt?

There would be more or less some corruption. Even if the grand elder herself was not corrupt, what about her subordinates? Her children? It was just that they were not as heavily corrupt as Frost Tide tribe's leader.

Even if the grand elder's side was completely free from corruption, they were still higher-ups, people who enjoyed the cake and also people who exploited others.

From this aspect, everyone was an exploiter, what difference was there?

They were all the same!

So, Frost Tide tribe's leader had never felt his corruption was wrong, he only wanted to obtain more wealth, beauties, and authority.

As his corruption increased, he was gradually pushing beyond the distribution agreement. But he did not want to stop, the greed in him did not allow him to stop.

"No, it is not greed. It is my aspiration!" Many times, Frost Tide tribe's leader would shout this inwardly.

There was a joke which was not a joke —

The father asked his son: What is your aspiration when you grow up?

The son replied: I want wealth and beauties.

The father slapped his son!

The son replied again: I want career and love.

The father smiled and nodded his head lightly!

Therefore, while career and love were aspirations, wealth and beauties were also aspirations.

So, Frost Tide tribe's leader was confident in himself, was there anything wrong with him chasing wealth, beauties, authority, and fame?

Did you think it was crude?

These were all aspirations!

Which person's life was not filled with such aspirations?!

Frost Tide tribe's leader liked this aspiration from deep down because this aspiration spurred him on, and also enticed others to pay and sacrifice for their aspirations and help him, Frost Tide tribe's leader, to achieve his aspiration!

There was nothing wrong with his corruption, this was his aspiration!

Aspirations should be practical and required effort to reach.

When Frost Tide tribe's leader fell into corruption for the first time, he knew there would be a time when he would be opposed and blamed by others.

But so what?

These were natural and were difficulties and pains that he must experience in realizing his aspiration!

As long as he passed these difficulties and subdued this suffering, Frost Tide tribe's leader could realize his aspiration.

As long as he used a series of political techniques like secret manipulation, indirect approaches, threats and so on, he could realize his aspiration.

Frost Tide tribe's leader, who had an authoritative status for a long time, was confident in this aspect. He indeed had the capital to be confident, if not for Fang Yuan appearing out of nowhere, he would have already pushed down Xie Han Mo and promoted his own pawn to the saintess position.

Once he accomplishes this, he would have defeated the grand elder and successfully defended the fruits of success from his corruption.

He would then use the puppet saintess to issue several policies which would be for a good future of the mermen and also for Sacred City. He would be able to turn his corrupted history into legal events that would clear his reputation for good.

At that time, who could say he was corrupted?!

But right when Frost Tide tribe's leader was about to succeed, he failed, he completely failed.

Because he ran into Fang Yuan.

This person had no 'aspirations'!

No, that was not exactly right. Frost Tide tribe's leader believed Fang Yuan liked wealth, beauties, power and fame too, but he liked to live by his own feelings even more! That was his aspiration.

What was the point of having such a grand aspiration?

With such an aspiration, wouldn't the majority of other people end up looking crude and ordinary?

He was really courting death!

Frost Tide tribe's leader gritted his teeth with hatred, this hatred was intensified because of an unknown fear in the depths of his heart.

Frost Tide tribe's leader wished he could flay Fang Yuan, he wished Fang Yuan would immediately die!

But he could not do so right now as this was the Sea God Ceremony.

The final song.

Xie Han Mo and Fang Yuan walked to the stage together.

Fang Yuan played the accompaniment while Xie Han Mo's song spread to the surroundings[1].

…

The blue sea is laughing, the tidal waves are surging.

Drifting with the waves, only caring about today.

Heaven laughs, at this hectic mortal world.

Who will win, who will lose, only heaven knows.

…

Human lives have ups and downs like the waves, sometimes high, sometimes low. Why do we have to be always concerned about victory or defeat?

The natural romanticism intoxicated the crowd.

…

The rivers and mountains laugh, the misty rain is far away.

How many great men and heroes, have the tides washed away?

Smiling at the breeze wind, lost in quiet solitude.

Heroic feelings remain, reflected in the cold night.

…

Bold and lofty, free and unrestrained, all kinds of 'aspirations' would be washed away by the waves. Even life itself will perish. But what is the big deal?

A noble man is not a slave to external matters, aloof from the world, forgetting gains and losses.

Destiny is fickle, so why uphold your disposition, throw away your mask and find your true self.

True self is unyielding, true self is lonely. Even if my life is the setting sun, I will live my own splendor.

The audience was entranced.

Frost Tide tribe's leader was pale, his body shivered as he understood his loss was certain!

…

The blue sea is laughing, the tidal waves are surging.

Drifting with the waves, only caring about today.

Heaven laughs, at this hectic mortal world.

Who will win, who will lose, only heaven knows.

The rivers and mountains laugh, the misty rain is far away.

How many great men and heroes, have the tides washed away?

Common people laugh, there is no more loneliness.

Yet the unyielding spirit in me is still laughing crazily.

…

I struggle to survive in the mortal world, I came to life and I joined the world. I lived my own life, I lived according to my own feelings, even if the waves toss me up and down, sending me to the border of death, I will never grieve, lament, fear, or worry; I will savor these flavor thoroughly, I will still laugh crazily until the end.

I am true to my nature.

I am a true person[2]!

On the stage, Fang Yuan was wholeheartedly activating the Gu worm with his eyes closed, the sound of the zither spreading throughout the area.

Frost Tide tribe's leader looked at him blankly, involuntarily mumbling: "This, this demon…"

Xie Han Mo was also entranced as she sang. She looked at Fang Yuan, an extraordinary brightness shining in her eyes as she thought: "Such a free and unrestrained life, isn't this what I yearn for? Fang Yuan is able to create such a song, he has the disposition of an immortal!"

…

Back to the present.

Dragon Whale grotto-heaven, Merman Sacred City.

Sea God Ceremony.

Xia Lin went on stage for the third song.

The blue sea is laughing, the tidal waves are surging. Drifting with the waves, only caring about today.

Heaven laughs, at this hectic mortal world. Who will win, who will lose, only heaven knows…

The entire place was shocked, Su Yi turned pale. The outcome was already certain.

Xia Lin was already entranced in singing.

At this moment, Master Chu's image was elevated infinitely in her heart, there was a moon and slight breeze in the background along with faint fog.

The familiar melody rang once again in Fang Yuan's ears and intertwined with his memory.

He had once stood on the stage as an accompanist, closing his eyes and slightly smiling.

Now, he stood outside of the stage as a spectator, his eyes hiding dark light.

After living for several hundred years, the vast power of time had changed him, but it also seemed like nothing had changed.

He had always been Gu Yue Fang Yuan.

[1] The song is Cang hai yi sheng xiao (沧海一声笑) by Sam Hui Back

[2] True person is 真人, which is in the pen name that the author goes by as well as RI's Chinese title, in daoist terms, it means transcendent person, but here it can also mean someone who lives truthfully by their own desires. Back

Chapter 1674: Sudden Change, Regret Gu

The Sea God Ceremony ended, the result was astonishing; the person who became the saintess was completely unexpected by anyone — Xia Lin.

Saintess Palace shined with bright and gorgeous lights, a group of servants were running around.

Xia Lin had already changed into her saintess attire, she was dressed in a white garment while her tail rested on a lump of clouds.

She opened the window and gazed at the large courtyard, those colorful corals could not attract her gaze.

She looked dazed and unfocused: "Several days have passed since the Sea God Ceremony concluded, Master Chu has not appeared again after transmitting his message that day. When will he return?"

"Saintess, your elder sister has come to pay a visit." At this moment, a maid lightly walked towards Xia Lin and reported.

Xia Lin's brows slightly furrowed as she sighed: "Please bring her in."

Xia Lin's elder sister Zhao Lu walked into Saintess Palace.

She was only Xia Lin's elder sister in name, but after Fang Yuan tampered with her memories, this elder sister did not doubt Xia Lin's identity.

"Little sister, have you considered what I said to you a few days ago?" Zhao Lu said directly.

Xia Lin shook her head lightly: "I am really sorry, I don't want to get involved in other affairs. The saintess position was never my goal, if possible, I do not want to be the saintess."

Zhao Lu laughed.

Her laughter carried a sense of ridicule and jealousy.

She was narrowly defeated by Su Yi in the final stage, then Xia Lin came out of nowhere and was supported by her backers just to give it a try. They had not thought Xia Lin would truly succeed!

The political force behind Zhao Lu, naturally, would not let go of Xia Lin and wanted to make her their representative for benefits.

But before Fang Yuan left, he had instructed Xia Lin to not agree to any person or side with any political force.

So Xia Lin had already refused Zhao Lu a few days ago.

Naturally, Zhao Lu's mood would not be so good.

First of all, her long lost little sister had suddenly appeared, besides the connection of blood, she did not feel any affection for this sister.

Secondly, she had worked hard for so long, but in the end, Xia Lin - who had cut in line - snatched the position of saintess. This was the same as snatching her lifelong dream!

Lastly, the force behind her still made her come out to persuade and rope in her younger sister Xia Lin, but Xia Lin still refused!

With all these reasons, Zhao Lu's mood naturally could not be good.

"Xia Lin, if you truly didn't want to become saintess, why did you take part? Don't say such things to me, we both understand the situation here, tell me whatever requests you have, this deal will make you fully satisfied!" Zhao Lu spoke frankly.

Xia Lin's brows furrowed deeper, she knew Zhao Lu was not her elder sister. This was just Master Chu's doing.

And now that she heard such words from Zhao Lu, Xia Lin's impression of her worsened greatly.

"Elder sister." Xia Lin spoke softly: "I am truly sorry, I really don't want to get involved in these matters. But you can rest assured that I won't collaborate with other forces as well."

Zhao Lu's eyes opened wide: "Xia Lin, you are truly naive, you actually have such thoughts? I had thought you were waiting for the right price, sigh, I overestimated you. Since it is so, I will make it clear for you, you will die if you don't have our support, understand?"

Xia Lin was stunned as she stared at Zhao Lu: "Don't tell me…"

Zhao Lu shook her head: "Don't think wildly, we never had the intention to conspire against you even if you ended up not collaborating with us. You are the saintess, a person who has received the Sea God's recognition, which merman force dares to make a move against you? Once the deed is exposed, they will face a terrible death!"

"Every selected saintess has an important task. That is to go to Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea and sing for three days and three nights, using her song to eliminate the increasingly dense demonic aura in Regret Crying Sea! This is an extremely dangerous task and has a very low survival rate. Many saintesses have passed away in Regret Crying Sea, some who came back alive turned crazy. Although the saintess position is good, it carries enormous risks and danger. If not for this task, there would be at least ten times more mermaids competing for the position of saintess!"

"There is such a thing?" Xia Lin was astonished.

Zhao Lu laughed: "You think I am deceiving you? This information might be hidden but it is not any important secret. You can easily inquire about it with your current identity and position. You can casually find anyone to ask, but of course, ordinary mermen are in the dark about it."

"Among the sea areas controlled by the Sacred Court, the most dangerous is Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea. It is an absolute forbidden area! According to legends, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable suppressed a peerless demonic Gu Immortal in this sea area. The Immortal Venerable was too benevolent to take away the demonic Gu Immortal's life, so he sealed the demonic Gu Immortal to make him repent. This demonic Gu Immortal had no choice but to repent, so there are often sounds of crying in that sea area. But his sins are truly too heavy and his demonic nature is too strong, the demonic aura will accumulate after a period of time and start influencing the living organisms in the sea area, making them stronger, ferocious and crueler."

"The saintess' task is to go the center of Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea and sing with all her strength, using her song to dispel the demonic aura, otherwise, as time goes on, the demonic aura in Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea will keep on getting stronger, making the living beings in the sea area become more tyrannical and invasive. This demonic aura is infectious as well, which will expand the area of Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea."

Xia Lin showed a surprised expression as it was the first time she heard this secret: "Even with support and ample preparations, the previous saintesses had to face extreme danger. If I go in alone without your help, it is almost like seeking death?"

"Not almost, but definitely!" Zhao Lu's tone was firm.

She expected this could persuade Xia Lin but did not expect Xia Lin to still reject: "Even so, I won't collaborate."

"Even if it will result in your death?" Zhao Lu's expression was cold.

It was not that Xia Lin did not have hesitation, but the image of Fang Yuan in her mind made her insist on abiding by the agreement she made with Fang Yuan.

"Yes, I am sure, even if I die."

Zhao Lu was so furious that she laughed: "If so… I only wish you good luck!"

The sisters parted on a bad note.

"Haha, it finally appeared!" In front of Merit Obelisk, Fang Yuan's eyes emitted bright light.

A new task had appeared on Merit Obelisk — help the new saintess complete her most important mission!

The task did not provide any details, by only looking at this task, outsiders would have no idea what the mission was.

But Fang Yuan had already inquired about it. In the Merman Sacred Court, the selected saintess had one important mission - to purify Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea!

Fang Yuan could only enter Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea if there was such a task.

But the issue was: Fang Yuan was not sure if this task would appear on the Merit Obelisk. So he needed to support a saintess and this saintess should have low strength with no one to rely on.

If so, the saintess would have no way to complete her mission and would require the help of outsiders.

In this grotto-heaven, there were no local Gu Immortals besides the suppressed demonic immortal. Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea was extremely dangerous, accumulating demonic aura at set intervals. The restraining method of the grotto-heaven was to select a saintess to quell it without regarding the sacrifices.

The saintess' mission was extremely important, if there was no successor to the saintess position for too long of a time, the demonic aura might even pervade the whole grotto-heaven. But naturally, there might also be some backup methods left by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

What Fang Yuan did was to hasten the appearance of this task as far as possible.

And from the results, his plan worked perfectly.

Without any hesitation, Fang Yuan accepted the task and was once again teleported to Sacred City.

Several days later.

Saintess Xia Lin stood on a giant tortoise that was slowly advancing towards Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea.

Behind her stood Fang Yuan.

The journey was tranquil and calm, but all of a sudden, a gale blew towards them carrying with it crying sounds: "I really regret it! Why did I have to provoke Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, I regret it so much!"

Xia Lin jolted, quickly looking at Fang Yuan: "Master Chu…."

"No worries." Fang Yuan smiled while secretly using wisdom path methods to calm Xia Lin and the giant tortoise.

The crying sounds seemed like an immortal killer move that could disturb an ordinary being's emotions and mind.

The nearer they reached Demon Suppression Regret Crying Sea, the louder and more concentrated the crying sound became.

"I regret it! I should not have killed so many people."

"I painfully regret it! I should not have chased after power, it would have been much better if I had stayed behind to look after my parents as a filial son!"

"I truly repent! I deceived everyone and concealed Immortal Gu, I let a friend, who trusted me the most, carry the blame so I could get benefits!"

…

The mournful cries made Xia Lin's face pale, while Fang Yuan instead became more excited because he already felt the large immortal formation in this place.

"I am now almost certain regret Gu is here! But if I take regret Gu, will it destroy Paradise Earth's arrangements and trigger his backup methods?" Fang Yuan was doubtful.

Regret Gu was very important, it was used to suppress the giant demon in the sea and was clearly not included in Paradise Earth's true inheritance.

But as far as Fang Yuan was concerned, it was a crucial Gu worm he had to take and he had decided to take the risk.

He focused his mind, activating investigative methods with all his strength, this demon suppression regret crying formation gradually appeared in his mind, becoming increasingly clearer.

This time, it was Fang Yuan who became pale.

"Such a powerful formation, it is as vast as the sky! My formation path attainment level is high and I also have extremely powerful wisdom path methods, but I would need at least dozens of years to comprehend all the profundities of this large formation!"

Cold sweat started seeping out of Fang Yuan's forehead when his mind suddenly jolted: "Regret Gu!"

He discovered regret Gu.

Although regret Gu was hidden, Fang Yuan had already determined regret Gu was hiding somewhere in the center of the sea area through all kinds of clues and arrangements.

"How should I take regret Gu? If I move rashly and trigger the formation's backlash, it would end up badly!"

"Maybe I can rely on reverse flow protection seal to resist it one time?"

"Or borrow the strength of the suppressed demon?"

Fang Yuan analyzed continuously in his mind.

If the demon was released, all the living beings of this small world might face extreme misery and suffering, but Fang Yuan had no misgivings or pity.

Just as Fang Yuan was thinking, a change occurred.

The large formation suddenly activated, regret Gu shot out directly towards Fang Yuan.

At the same time, an extremely boundless force emerged and pressed on Fang Yuan's body.

"What happened?!" At the next moment, Fang Yuan disappeared, directly leaving this grotto-heaven of Paradise Earth.

Chapter 1675: Birth of Red Lotus

Dark clouds covered the sky and heavy rain was pouring down.

Rumble!

Lightning flashed and thunder rumbled.

In Central Continent, inside the city lord's manor in Maple Leaf City, the Maple Leaf City Lord was pacing back and forth outside a room.

He had a square face and a dignified temperament. Right now, however, his brows were tightly furrowed and his mood was like this weather, erratic and uneasy, feeling extremely worried.

Suddenly, he stopped in his tracks and leaned in with his ear pressing on the door.

Besides the torrential rainstorm and thunder, he could hear painful groans from his wife as well as several midwives' voices: "Madam, push, push harder!"

Maple Leaf City Lord was already over fifty years old, he loved his wife deeply. He was a rank five Gu Master with the highest battle strength in all the surroundings, he had high authority as well as a leader's charisma, he was well supported by the people. The only imperfection was he had no children.

Nine months ago, he had been ecstatic because his wife had finally gotten pregnant.

He was going to have a child in his old age, his greatest regret was finally resolved.

But despite him requesting for three famous midwives, two were rank three and one was rank four, his wife's labor still encountered unexpected difficulty.

"How could this be?!" Maple Leaf City Lord wanted to get angry but had nothing to vent on.

He clenched his fists, the battle strength, which he had been proud of in the past, was of no use at this moment.

He had many healing Gu worms but none of them was good at helping in childbirth.

"Oh!" He could only restrain his mood, lowering his head as he once again paced back and forth in the corridor.

"Wa! Wawa…." Suddenly, he heard an infant's cry.

He then heard joyous laughter from the midwives: "The child is born, it is a boy! Madam, you have succeeded!!"

"I, I have a child! My… son!" Maple Leaf City Lord was stunned for a moment before turning ecstatic, he opened the door impatiently and charged in to take a look.

Right at this time, a peculiar fragrance spread within the room.

This peculiar fragrance was refreshing and gentle. The fragrance started to become denser, condensing into rays of colorful lights, they were like streams of water that floated in the air, covering the whole manor as well as the surrounding hundreds of li.

"What is this?!" Maple Leaf City Lord stopped his steps in astonishment.

But the real shock came next. These colorful flowing lights continued to increase in numbers and the fragrance also became increasingly intense.

The rainstorm stopped abruptly, dark clouds slowly dissipated; sunlight pierced through the gaps between the dark clouds and shined down, the grandest ray of light among them shining on the delivery room of the City Lord's wife.

Then, the flowing lights started to condense into a manor-sized red lotus flower that floated in the air. It was vivid and did not dissipate for a long time.

"Born with a natural phenomenon!" Maple Leaf City Lord was shocked, his wife and the three midwives were also frozen from shock.

At the same time, in the sky, three rank eight Gu Immortals were standing on clouds and watching the city lord's manor in Maple Leaf City. They had seen the phenomenon when the baby was born.

"He has finally been born." The Gu Immortal in the middle, Duke Mei, heaved a long sigh. He was an old man with a benevolent countenance, his brows were particularly peculiar, they were like two exquisite dark brown roots that extended down from his forehead to his chest.

"This child is extraordinary indeed, he is blessed by the destined luck of humanity, his innate blessing is so dense that it actually condensed into a grand red lotus observable to the naked eye! He is absolutely an Immortal Venerable seed! It was worth it that our Heavenly Court used three wisdom path Gu Immortals to deduce him." Standing on the left, Gu Immortal Duke Tong sighed.

He was a middle-aged man with a very robust physique, his face and muscles seemed to be made from brass as they let out cold metallic glister. Standing on the clouds, he looked deep like a pool and lofty like a mountain, as if he was a vajra tower that could not be moved even if heaven and earth shook, an absolute spirit that disregarded the storms.

Duke Mei nodded: "Among all the Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables in history, they share a common characteristic, they all possess the destined luck of humanity[1]. It is just that in some cases, the luck is not conspicuous at the early stage and is deeply concealed. Only by a certain period would the luck activate. This child caused such a phenomenon when he is just born, no wonder heaven and earth cannot tolerate him and sent down calamities and tribulations to eliminate him. This is rare even in venerable history. If this child is nurtured properly, he will definitely become the most talented and outstanding existence among the venerables!"

Suddenly, Duke Mei's body shook as he coughed out a mouthful of blood.

"Duke Mei." Duke Tong frowned: "We suffered heavy injuries to block the calamities and tribulations."

"Duke Mei!" The Gu Immortal standing at the right also revealed a concerned expression. He was a young man with a head full of purple hair, a dragon shaped qi aura moved around his body continuously.

Duke Mei looked at the young Gu Immortal: "Duke Long, fate Gu has given us the revelation, you share an extremely deep affinity with this child. This child will become a venerable and you are his Dao Guardian! Go, take him as your disciple, guide him and nurture him. You will be the cause of his achievements as he will be the cause of yours. You two are destined to shine brightly in the history of humanity for all eternity!"

"Yes, I shall go now." Young Duke Long nodded.

"Go." Duke Tong's brows were furrowed: "When we return to Heavenly Court, Duke Mei and I shall enter a very long hibernation to recuperate. The era of the Three Dukes of Heavenly Court is over, Duke Long, you will lead Heavenly Court, continue to bring prosperity to this world."

"I will!" Duke Long restrained his excited emotions and slowly descended.

His sleeves were fluttering with the wind, he waved his hand and boundless wind surged. Endless dragon roars were heard, attracting attention and shock from everyone.

In this boundless wind, he slowly flew down and landed on the manor of Maple Leaf City Lord.

Including Maple Leaf City Lord, all the guards were kneeling on the ground, many of them shivering like leaves.

Maple Leaf City Lord was a knowledgeable man, knowing about Gu Immortals' existence as well as knowing his strength could not even resist one finger of a Gu Immortal. He forcibly calmed himself before paying respects: "I, Hong Zhu, pay respects to lord immortal. I wonder what matter lord immortal has descended to the mortal world for?"

Duke Long smiled: "Hong Zhu, your son is the blessed child of the world, a peerless genius that appears once in a million years with extremely rare innate talents. If he is nurtured well, he will definitely be outstanding. But if he lacks guidance, there will be huge danger to countless beings of this world, chaos would ensue. I was happy to see such a rare talent, and for the sake of humanity, I came here to take this child as my disciple. I will carefully raise and guide him, making him into a leader of the righteous path, a Gu Immortal who seeks prosperity for the whole of humanity."

"Ah…" Maple Leaf City Lord was both stunned and joyous at these words.

He was shaken by Duke Long's words, but he had personally seen the natural phenomenon just before, and was actually somewhat mentally prepared.

The joy was naturally because his son received a Gu Immortal master and had boundless future prospects, he would definitely surpass his parents.

Although he was a city lord with high authority, he was nothing compared to this Gu Immortal.

But besides the shock and joy, Hong Zhu felt somewhat dejected. He got a child in his old age, it was not easy, but who could have thought that before he even got a chance to look at his son, his son would be taken as a disciple by lord immortal. They would probably get very few chances to meet each other in the future.

Duke Long immediately knew what Hong Zhu was thinking, consoling: "Rest assured, I came today only to explain this matter and not to take away your son immediately. I will only bring him away when he is ten years old which is the correct time to start teaching him."

Hong Zhu immediately felt endless excitement and expressed his thanks repeatedly.

At this time, the door opened, the city lord's wife had already cleaned herself up, she came out while holding the newly born baby along with the three midwives and knelt on the ground, paying respects to Duke Long.

Duke Long's gaze was immediately attracted towards the baby. He laughed happily as he took a step forward, immediately arriving in front of the city lord's wife.

He carefully held the baby and inspected him.

This baby did not have any ugliness that a newly born baby had. His head was filled with dark hair and had a very attractive and cute face. His eyes shined brightly like stars, his skin was white and tender and his cheeks were chubby.

At this time, the red lotus that was hovering in the air slowly descended while shrinking and condensing continuously, in Duke Long's vision, the red lotus eventually landed on the baby's forehead, condensing into a nine petaled red lotus birthmark.

A trace of shock flashed past Duke Long's eyes as he thought: "This destined luck condensed into a birthmark, imprinted on his forehead, this phenomenon has not been seen in any venerable before. When my disciple becomes a venerable, he will probably be an extremely unique one!"

As he thought of this, Duke Long felt like the light baby he was holding had become as heavy as a mountain. A strong sense of mission and responsibility filled Duke Long's mind.

"You don't need to kneel, please stand." After inspecting for a while more, Duke Long solemnly handed the baby back to the city lord's wife.

He exhaled, three gusts of qi flashed by, one fell on the baby while the other two merged inside the city lord couple.

The baby immediately fell asleep with a smile on his face.

The city lord couple felt boundless strength filling their limbs and bones.

The city lord's wife gave a cry of shock, the weakness from giving birth was gone instantly, she burst with energy as her body condition returned to when she was young.

City Lord Hong Zhu astonishingly discovered his old injuries were completely gone and his primeval essence had broken common sense, carrying a trace of green luster. His strength that was already at a level where it could not be raised further seemed to have been elevated by a large degree!

Without immediately inspecting his changes, Hong Zhu first gave thanks to Duke Long along with his wife.

Duke Long waved his hand: "You don't need to thank me because I still need your help. The parents and the master are not interchangeable with each other. I wish that you can love each other dearly and give your son deep care, let him feel the love and warmth of the world, this will be extremely helpful to his growth. Ten years later, I will come again."

Duke Long then slowly rose to the sky. Air currents surged around him and dragon roars were heard unceasingly, as if there was a formless wave of dragons.

Mortals gazed towards the sky and saw Duke Long flying away until his figure was blocked by the clouds.

After a while of deep silence, the whole city went into an uproar.

[1] This is not Giant Sun's luck path, this is more like your MC aura's luck, or rather, they have immense fortune and blessing. Back

Chapter 1676: What is Fate?

It was a clear sky with no clouds anywhere.

Maple Leaf City was bustling with people moving here and there.

Six years had passed since the City Lord's son, Hong Ting, was born.

In these six years, Maple Leaf City enjoyed a peaceful time with no calamities. Its size continued to expand unceasingly, already surpassing the original size by over ten times, it had become the number one human city in the surrounding plains.

Chirp, chirp…

A group of spiritual sparrows flew over from somewhere. Their whole bodies shined with golden light and were flying like they were dancing.

They displayed extraordinary liveliness until they arrived at the top of the City Lord's manor when suddenly, they imploded one after the other, bursting into specks of golden lights that sprinkled down.

Inside the City Lord's manor, Hong Ting was currently brandishing a short decorative sword. He was moving some ornamental mounds back and forth while skillfully swinging his sword.

In an instant, Hong Ting's figure disappeared, sword lights formed into spheres which shined brightly everywhere.

"Great!"

"Amazing!"

"Young master truly has unrivaled talents, he has completely perfected this sword technique after just learning it for three months. Such a density of sword lights is simply unbelievable."

The surrounding guards praised with sincerity from the depths of their hearts.

City Lord Hong Zhu stroked his beard and nodded with a smile. He was very proud of his son, as for the feeling of surprise, he had lost it a long time ago.

Over these years, Hong Ting's aptitude and performance had changed his view and understanding multiple times, he now knew how shallow his comprehension of the word 'genius' was.

Because of the endless surprises throughout these years, Hong Zhu had already become numb to them long ago. Now, everything involving his son was natural and a matter of fact.

Clang!

Right at this time, a crisp sound echoed.

Silver sword lights suddenly disappeared and Hong Ting's figure appeared once again, his short decorative sword had slashed apart a boulder.

Cheers and praises immediately resounded.

"Father, I feel like this sword technique has not reached its limit, there is room for improvement." Hong Ting walked out from the group of ornamental mounds and said with a smile.

Hong Zhu laughed heartily: "This sword technique belongs to the secret manual of a famous sword cultivator, Zhao San Si, I used a lot of treasures to exchange for it. You have only practiced for three months and already feel that it is not good enough?"

Hong Ting blinked with a cute slyness in his eyes: "Father, I only said that out of momentary inspiration. To tell the truth, this sword technique is only so-so, I have already learned all of its essence after practicing for three months."

Hong Zhu coughed, feeling a bit of headache again. His son's talent was too great, he was fast at learning anything, he even went as far as to comprehend the deepest essence of those moves. This was good but also bad as well. Hong Zhu's accumulations were already used up several years ago by Hong Ting. He went through all kinds of avenues to search for secret manuals to teach Hong Ting, but it still could not match Hong Ting's ability to absorb knowledge like a black hole.

If this continued for a long time, what could he do?

Right at this time, a group of spiritual sparrows flew over their heads and suddenly imploded into golden light specks.

The light specks fell and got absorbed into everyone's head; but most of the light specks were absorbed by Hong Ting alone.

Instantly, everyone had joyous expressions. They had received inheritances and all sorts of peculiar secret manuals.

"This is the gift of yet another immortal!"

"I wonder which immortal this is?"

"We should thank young master, we are all enjoying his fortune."

The guards looked at Hong Ting passionately, even Hong Zhu's gaze carried a trace of complex feelings.

Hong Ting had closed his eyes, immersed completely in the newly obtained sea of knowledge.

Hong Zhu and the rest were already not surprised at this scene, even the commoners outside the City Lord's manor were only slightly surprised before returning to their business.

Unusual phenomena and immortal miracles were fascinating, but when they happened too many times, they would start feeling bland and ordinary.

The immortal miracles appearing around Hong Ting could not be said to be 'a lot', it was at a mind numbing level that was simply overflowing with such incidents.

Since he was born and taken as a disciple by Duke Long, immortal phenomena would frequently occur around him.

Duke Long was the leader of Heavenly Court, not mentioning the rank eight Gu Immortals in Heavenly Court, just the ten great ancient sects under Heavenly Court were colossal forces with extremely robust foundations.

Duke Long had taken in this disciple with great publicity, he did not conceal anything. Everyone understood his intentions, so whether it was Central Continent's righteous path, demonic path, or lone immortals, they all paid extreme attention to Hong Ting's growth.

Hong Ting was the blessed child of the world, a future Immortal Venerable who would be cultivated by Heavenly Court, this was not a secret. So, every so often, Gu Immortals or descendants of Gu Immortals would secretly help Hong Ting, to build a good affinity and relationship with him in advance.

As a result, the golden sparrow inheritance gift was not strange, there were also spiritual cranes imparting scrolls, auspicious clouds sending fruits, sacred wind marrow cleansing, and all sorts of unusual immortal level phenomena that appeared endlessly.

After a long while, Hong Ting completely absorbed the knowledge in his brain but his brows furrowed into a frown: "There are eighteen types of weapon training methods, each one is exquisite and unique, but there is still no mention of any advanced aperture awakening method. Father, when can I awaken my aperture and control Gu worms? No matter how excellent these fighting techniques are, they are only mortal techniques. Controlling Gu worms is the only true way."

"Son, don't be in a hurry. You have once again forgotten what your master instructed in his letter." Hong Zhu said with a pleasant smile.

Hong Ting waved his hand impatiently: "Father, I know, I know. Master said that although I can awaken my aperture in advance, I must do it only when I am twelve. Before the timing and opportunity is right, I cannot do it in advance. I am really curious, master has such vast powers, why can't he awaken my aperture now?"

Hong Zhu's expression became slightly grave: "Son, your master is an immortal, you cannot understand what he is thinking but you have to obey. You need to understand that he absolutely won't harm you, he cherishes you just like how father and mother treasure you."

"Yes, father. I was wrong, please don't get angry." Hong Ting quickly cupped his fists, he was very filial to his parents.

Time passed, years passed in an instant.

Duke Long appeared once again and formally took Hong Ting as his disciple. He took Hong Ting to roam all over the world while personally guiding him.

When Hong Ting was twelve, Duke Long awakened his aperture. Hong Ting officially stepped on the path of Gu cultivation, and because of his peerless talent and robust foundation, his cultivation progress was shockingly fast.

Not only in his cultivation, his experiences also richened constantly on this journey. He met many people, mortals and immortals, kind people and evil people. His knowledge of human life and heaven and earth was constantly deepening.

He had a strong sense of justice and loathed evil, he looked handsome and kind but was crafty and resourceful as well.

"Master, I have found that evil Xue Tu Dao who slaughtered an entire village, he is staying at a nearby mountain!" On this day, Hong Ting returned to the cave from hunting and spoke to Duke Long with excitement.

Duke Long nodded with a smile: "Take a seat first, the soup is almost ready. This soup is made from the bones of an ancient desolate beast, it will be very helpful to your growth."

Hong Ting threw down the prey he hunted, saying with clenched teeth: "Master, I have been wanting to take action on Xue Tu Dao for over a year and get rid of this evil, but you said I only had rank three cultivation while he had rank five, I was not his match so you didn't allow me to go. Half a year ago, I already had rank four cultivation and eight killer moves, I had an extremely high chance of taking Xue Tu Dao's life but you said that it was not one hundred percent so you didn't let me make a move. Three months ago, I already reached rank five and could easily deal with Xue Tu Dao in two to three moves, but you said it was not time to take his life. Master, if we let such an evil person run amok, who knows how many more innocent lives would be lost. Let me strike now!"

Duke Long put down the ladle and let the bone soup simmer as he said with a sigh: "Disciple, the opportunity has not arrived."

"I don't care about any opportunity, I only know that if I don't make a move now, I would lose a good opportunity!" Hong Ting was extremely firm.

Duke Long shook his head: "Now is not the time for Xue Tu Dao to die. If you forcibly kill him, not only will it be futile and fruitless, you will even create certain aftermath which will lead to tragedy."

"I don't believe it! I only need one move to take his life!!" Hong Ting raised one finger, staring right into Duke Long's eyes with a burning gaze.

Duke Long went silent for a while: "Then go, young man, give it a try."

"Thank you master!" Hong Ting was exulted.

"I just hope that you will not be disappointed when the time comes."

"Why will I be disappointed? Master, please wait a moment, disciple will return with Xue Tu Dao's head within fifteen minutes."

Hong Ting turned around and left.

But fifteen minutes passed, thirty minutes went by and soon it reached forty-five minutes, Hong Ting still did not appear.

Duke Long saw everything, he knew the timing was right as he left the cave and crossed a forest, arriving beside Hong Ting.

Hong Ting was kneeling on the ground, his face filled with shock, anger, and deep regret.

He was dazedly looking at the foot of the mountain, a small village had once been there where the villagers lived happily.

His eyes were red and filled with traces of blood. He saw Duke Long and raised his head, tear stains were still clear on his face.

"Master, I did not imagine there to be a Gu Immortal inheritance here. That Xue Tu Dao secretly came here to obtain this inheritance. After I destroyed his plan, he used the inheritance's power to stop me and although I fought with all my strength, I did not think the battle would cause the mountain to crumble, unexpectedly, unexpectedly… the small village was completely buried. Master! It was me, I caused the death of these villagers!" Hong Ting sobbed.

Duke Long did not console him, he was silent for a while before suddenly saying: "Disciple, do you want revenge? Do you want to get rid of Xue Tu Dao? The opportunity has arrived."

"Really? Where is he?" Hong Ting's body shook, asking immediately.

"At that mountain." Duke Long pointed.

Hong Ting immediately hurried off and easily killed Xue Tu Dao.

"I was so close, I already obtained the true inheritance and only had to absorb the gains. The moment I narrowly escaped death, you came after me! If I had some time, I would not be afraid, I could have become a Gu Immortal!" These were Xue Tu Dao's last words before he died.

Hong Ting was silently standing before Xue Tu Dao's corpse.

Duke Long appeared behind Hong Ting once again, remaining silent.

After a good while, Hong Ting stopped looking at Xue Tu Dao's corpse in a daze as he asked with an extremely hoarse voice: "Master, had I listened to your arrangements, I could have easily killed him and those villagers would not have been implicated, is that right?"

Duke Long did not reply, only softly patting Hong Ting's shoulder.

Hong Ting's body shook as he fell into a deep silence before asking: "Master, I want to ask you, what is… fate?"

Chapter 1677: I Regret It

"Fate…" Duke Long sighed with a deep and complex expression. He walked towards a rock and patted beside him, indicating Hong Ting to have a seat.

Hong Ting followed Duke Long and sat cross-legged.

"Look." Duke Long pointed at the rock he was sitting on.

Hong Ting quickly looked, he saw a small group of ants moving beside the rock. They were moving in an orderly fashion, returning to their nest with food.

"This is fate." Duke Long continued.

"…What?"

"Look again." Duke Long pointed at the sky.

Hong Ting gazed at the sky, clouds of all kinds of shapes were moving in the sky.

"This also is fate." Duke Long said.

Hong Ting's mind jolted as if he had comprehended something: "Master, you mean to say…"

He did not continue, he had gained some comprehension but was unable to express them in words at this time.

"Ants transporting food, bees collecting honey, wind blowing, clouds floating, everything in this world have their own paths to walk on. To us, they might look like they don't follow any rules, but they are actually moving according to the rules of the Great Dao."[1]

"Look at the moon and sun, every day, the sun rises and the moon falls, the moon rises and the sun falls. Look at a human's life and death, no matter who they are, be they an Immortal Venerable or a Demon Venerable, they will die in the end."

"Everything is fate."

"Every person, every living being, even every rock, every drop of water, every lump of fire, since they exist in this world, they will have value and meaning in their existence. Good and evil is also the same, without good, how would there be evil? Without evil, why talk about good?"

"You were in a hurry to kill Xue Tu Dao and did not see his value. Since heaven and earth let him exist, there is definitely a reason for his life. This is fate. Fate already has arrangements for everything in the world, it is just that we can only slightly feel this kind of arrangement and cannot see it clearly."

"Not being able to see clearly is normal. The laws of heaven and earth, the Great Dao of the universe, even if an immortal uses all their life, they would not be able to understand them thoroughly. We are too weak, too small, while heaven and earth is too vast. We should revere heaven and earth, follow the arrangements of the heavenly fate, and bring fortune to the world."

"Your parents' marriage was fate's arrangement, their greatest value was to bring you into this world."

"You will become an Immortal Venerable in the future, this is also fate's arrangement. You need to accept it, climb to the peak step by step, lead Heavenly Court and contribute your life to the righteous path."

"And my greatest value in life is to teach and guide you towards the proper path. I am your… Dao Guardian."

"Believe in fate, acknowledge fate, all its arrangements have their own reasons. If we forcibly interfere, it will lead to tragedy and regret. Just like how you tried to take Xue Tu Dao's life early, but were you able to kill him?"

Duke Long shook his head: "No. Although your strength surpassed his, you encountered all kinds of unexpected situations. In the end, not only did you fail to kill him, you even implicated innocent lives."

"Think back on it, if you had listened to fate's arrangements and attacked Xue Tu Dao at his weakest moments, would you still have encountered those accidents?"

"I will tell you, the value of Xue Tu Dao's existence was to activate this Gu Immortal inheritance, to open the way and hand this inheritance to you."

Hong Ting was dazed, he was motionless like a statue.

Two clear rows of tears fell from his eyes as he choked: "Master, I was wrong."

"It is good to know your mistakes and change them. Actually, your wrong choice was also fate's arrangement." Duke Long said.

"Master, what do you mean?"

"We are all under fate's arrangements, you thought you could defy fate, but your thought was also fate's arrangement. You don't need to feel guilty, you should comprehend fate's intention. You think your wrong choice was of no value? Wrong."

"Every mistake has an inestimable value to a youth's growth. If you can absorb the lesson from this mistake, acknowledge fate's existence and accept it, then this mistake would have shown its value. That village's destruction also has its value!"

Duke Long then took a deep look at Hong Ting: "My disciple, you are a talented and intelligent child, a good child, but I worry because you emphasize on feelings too much. You already have rank five cultivation now, among the paths to ascend to an immortal, you will probably choose wisdom path, right?"

"Master, your vision is unparalleled, I indeed have such thoughts, I feel like wisdom path is extremely suitable for me." Hong Ting said truthfully.

Duke Long shook his head: "Wisdom path focuses on thought, will, and emotion. You emphasize on feelings too much so studying emotions has more demerits than benefits to you. Listen to master, choose time path. When you can view the past and present, observe the rise and decline of history, all sorts of honor and disgrace, you will understand that all feelings and romance will be cleansed by time. I have received revelation from fate Gu, time path suits you the most."

Hong Ting opened his mouth slightly, wanting to say something, but he nodded in the end: "Disciple shall abide by master's teachings and choose time path."

Duke Long nodded in satisfaction: "That's good, master is your Dao Guardian, pointing you towards the correct path is the meaning behind my existence."

Time slowly moved forward.

Hong Ting chose time path, and under Duke Long's protection, successfully passed his immortal ascension tribulation, becoming a time path Gu Immortal.

…

"Lord immortal Hong Ting, that demon has proclaimed he is going to slaughter the whole city unless I give my daughter to him as a concubine. He is a great Gu Immortal, we are only mortals. We truly are unable to do anything, considering the friendship between me and your father, I implore you to eliminate this demon!" An old city lord paid a visit, kneeling to the ground as he made his request to Hong Ting.

Hong Ting recognized him, this city lord's city was close to Maple Leaf City. They had frequent dealings with each other, this city lord and his father indeed had a close friendship.

He had even seen this city lord's daughter and had played with her when they were young.

"Old senior, please get up. I will definitely help, it is just that…" Hong Ting paused for a moment: "The opportunity has not arrived."

The old city lord was exulted: "Since lord immortal has replied, this old man shall be rest assured. I believe lord immortal will not go back on his words!"

Hong Ting waited till it was the correct time to kill this demonic Gu Immortal.

He attacked resolutely and killed this demon easily.

However, the old city lord was kneeling on the ground, gazing at the city filled with ruins and corpses as he cried in sadness: "This accursed demon is finally dead! My good daughter, the inhabitants of my city, you can rest in peace now, your hatred has been avenged!!"

…

"Disciple pays respect to master. I wonder what matter master has called me for?" Hong Ting went up to Duke Long.

"Disciple, master has sensed fate. Floating flower river is about to flood, the river channel has diverged. I want you to go save people. Remember, don't make a move early, you can only do so after three days and three nights." Duke Long instructed carefully.

"Yes, master."

Hong Ting came to the floating flower riverbank and looked at the flooding river water, countless living beings were forced to be homeless, while many drowned corpses were floating on the surface.

He forcibly restrained his emotions and waited for three days and three nights. But at that time, he found that he did not even need to make a move, the river water retreated by itself, swamps appearing in many areas.

A wild Immortal Gu's aura emerged and was actually not far away from Hong Ting.

Hong Ting easily subdued this wild Immortal Gu: "Great Gu, it is actually a rank seven time path Gu which is perfect for me."

Howl!

The wild Immortal Gu's aura attracted two ancient desolate beasts.

Hong Ting's expression turned solemn as he concealed himself. He waited for these two ancient desolate beasts to kill each other. After one died and another was injured, he made his move, getting these two ancient desolate beast corpses easily.

"Wonderful, wonderful." Gazing at the traces of the battlefield, Hong Ting suddenly came to a realization.

"So it turns out this was fate's arrangement. With the battle of the two ancient desolate beasts, floating flower river has expanded by several times its width while its river channel has been dyed by the ancient desolate beasts' blood, becoming much thicker. From now on, floating flower river will probably not flood again."

"There are also these plots of land beside floating flower river which will become extremely fertile as they are soaked in the essence blood and corpses of countless beings. In the future, the mortals who live here will truly be fortunate."

…

"Bull-headed Demon Brute, let go of my parents now, otherwise, I will make you suffer a fate worse than death!" Hong Ting furiously glared at the bull-headed demonic immortal.

The bull-headed demonic immortal held Hong Ting's parents in each of his hands, laughing loudly: "Kid, you are very arrogant, you want to get rid of me? When I became a Gu Immortal, you were still suckling milk as a baby! Are you scared now?"

Hong Ting had to restrain himself and could only shout in anger.

Bull-headed Demon Brute quickly shouted: "Don't come over, don't be impulsive! Don't you want your parents' lives? If you come over, I will directly crush your parents' heads!"

"What do you want?!" Hong Ting shouted.

Bull-headed Demon Brute gave a malevolent smile: "Now we are talking. As long as you hand over my lifespan Gu, I will return your parents to you. If not, I only have a few days to live anyway, I will just die with your parents."

Hong Ting was immediately dazed.

According to fate's arrangements, those two wild lifespan Gu should indeed go to Bull-headed Demon Brute. But Hong Ting saw his parents getting old and reaching their life's limit, so he seized those two lifespan Gu without telling Duke Long. Who could have thought that Bull-headed Demon Brute would come and bring disaster to his parents!

In an instant, Hong Ting's face became deathly pale and his forehead was filled with cold sweat: "I have already used those two lifespan Gu."

"I know, you used them on your parents!" Bull Demon was not surprised: "But, you are Duke Long's disciple, a future Immortal Venerable who will lead Heavenly Court. I don't believe Heavenly Court's treasury does not have any lifespan Gu. Bring three hundred years, no, three thousand years lifespan Gu and I will release your parents!"

"This…" Hong Ting was now caught in a dilemma.

In the end, through twists and turns, he finally forced Bull-headed Demon Brute to retreat. But his parents were irrecoverably injured, even immortal methods could not heal them.

"Father, mother, I harmed you! If I had not taken lifespan Gu for you, you would still have several years left!" Hong Ting knelt down and cried.

Hong Zhu, however, smiled: "Son, life and death is up to fate, fortune is up to heaven. Humans have to die sooner or later, this world has long life but is there anyone who can live forever? No! We are fated to die, you don't need to feel sad for us. On the contrary, you should be happy for us. The two of us could have a son like you, a future Immortal Venerable, how great of an honor is this, we will definitely be noted down in history because of you."

Madam Hong also said: "My son, listen to your father, be a good person, you must be righteous."

The old couple grasped each other's hands and died at the same time.

"Father, mother—!" Hong Ting howled towards the sky.

…

Bright light accumulated in Hong Ting's eyes. Through the passing of time, experience and maturity made him full of manly charisma.

The setting sun illuminated the lush green hill.

Under the setting sun, he saw Liu Shu Xian for the first time.

Two pairs of eyes met each other, both felt their hearts pulsing, an indescribable atmosphere rapidly spread.

Love at first sight.

Liu Shu Xian revealed a strange expression, asking softly: "Who are you?"

Hong Ting, however, felt no surprise, he replied with a smile: "I am your fated husband, my name is Hong Ting."

Liu Shu Xian was astonished: "You are the future Immortal Venerable?"

"Don't be surprised, our encounter here was determined by fate."

Love gave Hong Ting a feeling of satisfaction and bliss that he had never experienced before!

He and Liu Shu Xian always kept each other's company and had a lot in common. It was like they were born for each other, like a key to a lock, they were a natural couple.

They roamed the world together, they conversed and dined under the moon. They had great chemistry, an eye signal to the other could express their inner heart and even convey all their intention to the other's mind. They were a true immortal couple, living together for hundreds of years. They supported each other in the path of cultivation, there was not even one fight or a moment where they were vexed at each other.

Liu Shu Xian accompanied Hong Ting all the way to rank eight, rank eight peak, and finally to rank nine venerable realm!

The tribulation was unimaginable, but Hong Ting still succeeded in the end.

Duke Long was heavily injured due to this, several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals perished, while Hong Ting held Liu Shu Xian's gradually freezing body with tears all over his face.

He tightly held Liu Shu Xian, repeatedly saying: "Don't leave me, don't leave me, I beg you, please live!"

"It's no use, I have been struck by the tribulation. Having a trace of my soul left to take a final look at you is already an enormous fortune. How could I possibly ask for more?" Liu Shu Xian smiled.

"I am useless, I am useless! I underwent tribulation but implicated you!" Hong Ting's head was lowered with tears rolling down his eyes.

"No, Hong Ting. That tribulation could only have been blocked by my special physique. Even if you all sacrificed your lives, you would only have failed. I was born with one of the ten extreme physiques and encountered you, it was all fate's arrangement. In your fatal moment, I suddenly understood the greatest meaning of my life, it was to protect you, to block the tribulation for you and help you ascend to the position of an Immortal Venerable! Now… I have accomplished it."

"No, No! Xian Er, I would rather not be an Immortal Venerable, I only want you to live, I only want you to live!" Hong Ting roared helplessly, his body was shaking and his tears were falling.

"Everything and everyone in this world has its own respective fate, it is fixed. Hong Ting, you cannot have such thoughts, you need to live on properly, your fate is to become an Immortal Venerable, lead Heavenly Court and spread the glory of the righteous path throughout the five regions… Do you know? I had always been wanting to see that scene, standing by your side and accompanying you as you bring fortune to the world with invincible might. Unfortunately, I won't be able to see it…"

Liu Shu Xian's life force gradually fell, until she died.

Hong Ting's head was lowered and his back was bent deeply like an old man, a heavy shadow shrouded his face.

At this moment, he seemed to have lost all signs of life.

He was motionless like a statue.

In his immortal aperture, the remaining heaven and earth qi gathered and merged, refining a rank eight Immortal Gu according to his current mental state.

This Gu had the form of a centipede, its whole body was pale white like paper. Unlike centipedes, its legs were replaced by one hundred feelers. Every feeler was translucent, gently floating in the air, agitating hearts and continuously raising the deepest regretful feelings.

Rank eight regret Gu!

"Cough, cough, cough." Duke Long coughed out several mouthfuls of blood, he forcibly stood up and walked to Hong Ting's side.

"Liu Shu Xian's death was not without meaning, it was worthy and valuable, there is no need for sadness, my dear disciple. This was all fate's arrangement. Now, you are already an Immortal Venerable, rank nine venerables are extremely rare even in the long history of humanity. You still have a long life ahead, your mission has just started. I will abdicate my position, Heavenly Court as well as the five regions and two heavens need you. Hong Ting, Hong Ting?" Duke Long softly called.

Hong Ting slowly raised his head, he did not look at Duke Long, his gaze was still on Liu Shu Xian's icy corpse.

He replied lightly: "I regret it."

[1] Dao is also read as road or path. Back

Chapter 1678: Immortal Venerable Regrets, But I Do Not!

"What did you say?" Duke Long did not hear clearly.

"I said, I regret it." Hong Ting said again.

Duke Long's brows immediately furrowed, using a stern gaze to look at his proudest disciple: "Regret? Oh Hong Ting, don't speak of such nonsense again. You are clear of it, how many people dedicated and sacrificed themselves to cultivate and support you until you reached your current cultivation level? If you say such things, would you be doing justice to those people who have helped you throughout your life? Would you be doing justice to your parents? Justice to your late wife Liu Shu Xian? Justice to the immortals who helped you pass the tribulation and sacrificed themselves?"

Duke Long berated Hong Ting sternly.

"Alright, Lord Duke Long, Liu Shu Xian's death is a great tragedy, we can understand Red Lotus Immortal Venerable's feelings. He is only in a temporarily agitated state." The other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals attempted to mediate.

"Red Lotus Immortal Venerable… hehe." Hong Ting laughed with disdain, he gazed at Duke Long with his bloodshot eyes: "If such sacrifices are required and there will be even more sacrifices in the future for this Immortal Venerable position, then I would rather not have it!"

"Enough!" Duke Long shouted in rage: "I will not allow you to speak anymore nonsense, Hong Ting! You think your Immortal Venerable position can be gained or abandoned at your will? This is all fate's arrangement, this is the mission of your life, you must accept it no matter what!"

Hong Ting laughed loudly, his hair was messy, he was in a miserable state. He lowered his head and looked at Duke Long: "A grand Immortal Venerable, invincible in the world, actually cannot do as he pleases, he cannot even reject this Immortal Venerable position?"

Duke Long snorted coldly: "Tell me, Hong Ting, who can do as they please in this world? Your thoughts are too childish, you think becoming an Immortal Venerable and leading the righteous path would not need sacrifices? What is there in this world that has no price to pay for? How shallow do you think the words 'righteous path' are? Wrong! Maintaining Heavenly Court's righteous path requires you to pay a price, it requires sacrifices. If you don't even have this sacrificial mentality, then I will tell you, you don't have the qualifications to enter Heavenly Court!"

Hong Ting's body shook.

"Lord Duke Long, Lord Immortal Venerable, please calm yourselves. We should recuperate and heal our injuries now instead of quarreling." The other Gu Immortals repeatedly tried persuading.

Hong Ting slowly lowered his head, but his fists were slowly clenched tight as he said with an incomparably firm tone: "I want to revive them."

Duke Long's brows raised, his face cold as ice: "Who do you want to revive?"

"Every person who sacrificed themselves for me. My parents, Liu Shu Xian, and many others."

"Presumptuous!" Duke Long suddenly shouted while pointing at Hong Ting: "How could you have such a heretical thought?! You know it clearly, I have also told you several times, life and death is determined by fate, life and death is the rule of the Great Dao, any living being's life and death is arranged by fate. You want to revive the dead? Are you trying to send the entire world into chaos? Have you not learned yet? The more you think like that, the more cruel tragedies will happen around you!"

"Even if there are crueler tragedies, I will accept them! Master, disciple always had a question. Why? Why must we accept fate's arrangements? If there was no fate, would the world truly fall into chaos? Is it not possible that the world will become a better place?" Hong Ting asked in an anxious tone.

Duke Long's body shook with anger, even the persuading Heavenly Court Gu Immortals slowly took a step back, looking at Hong Ting as if he was someone unfamiliar.

"Lord Immortal Venerable, your thought is too dangerous."

"Right, without fate, our human race would not be prosperous."

"Fate Gu is Heavenly Court's supreme treasure, Lord Immortal Venerable actually wants to destroy it? This, this, this…"

"All of you…" Hong Ting looked at the surrounding Gu Immortals, he felt an indescribably deep loneliness at this moment.

Time flowed, who knows how long had passed.

A lonely figure appeared in the River of Time.

His hair was messy, his face was filled with the vicissitudes of life, like a man who had roamed the world but had no place to call home.

His face still had the former Hong Ting's shadow, but his expression had already changed completely.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable looked at the endlessly flowing River of Time as he sighed: "It is time to leave behind my inheritance."

He slowly descended, his feet stopped right before he touched the River of Time: "This first stone lotus island will also be the most important stone lotus island, I will use regret Gu as its core and leave this behind for the otherworldly demon, for the person who has the greatest hope of destroying Fate!"

Thereupon, a stone lotus island gradually appeared in this world.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable left behind rank eight regret Gu here as well as a large amount of time path immortal materials, immortal killer moves, a portion of his true meaning that contained his true memories of a certain period of time, as well as an immortal killer move with an unparalleled effect.

After finishing the arrangement, Red Lotus Demon Venerable flew away slowly with his exhausted body.

Time flew by, who knows how long had passed.

An outsider charged into this stone lotus island.

He was dressed in rough clothing, he had a thin looking body and a bald head, he had an ordinary appearance. He was bare-footed, his legs were even stained with some mud, like a farmer who had returned from a day of work in the fields.

However, his face looked very young, his eyes were glistening brightly, filled with compassion and benevolence.

Red Lotus' true meaning appeared, condensing into an illusory image of Red Lotus Demon Venerable who smiled towards the bare-footed young looking man: "Welcome, my honorary guest."

"I am Paradise Earth, I finally found this place after immense effort."

This person was Paradise Earth, who had already become an Immortal Venerable!

Red Lotus' true meaning directly asked: "Immortal Venerable, what is the purpose for your visit?"

Paradise Earth smiled: "Senior Red Lotus, why ask when you already know?"

Red Lotus' true meaning also smiled: "You are right, Fate has only been damaged, not completely destroyed, so everything is still traceable and observable from the River of Time."

Pausing for a moment, Red Lotus' true meaning continued: "I can lend you regret Gu, as for your intention to steal my inheritor, that will depend on your ability."

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable looked solemn: "Although he is an otherworldly demon, he is not an emotionless person. Put down the blade to reach redemption, it is never too late to turn back. Who does not want to seek redemption? I am willing to give it a try!"

Red Lotus' true meaning laughed: "Alright. My main body still had some worries when constructing this island. After all, I am not entirely confident in defending against Heavenly Court. However, since you are taking action, then there is no worry. This is regret Gu, catch it properly."

Regret Gu flew over slowly, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable stretched his hands, which were covered in radiance, and carefully received it.

"It is indeed worthy of being regret Gu, it constantly draws out boundless regretful feelings. Only a person with not even a little bit of regret is immune to this greatest flaw. Otherwise, any Gu Immortal who approaches it will feel incomparable pain and regret!" Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable smiled bitterly: "If not for my rank nine cultivation level, I might not be able to suppress it."

"Looks like you also have regret in your heart." Red Lotus' true meaning sighed.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable smiled lightly: "Who in this world does not have any regrets in their life?"

Putting regret Gu into his immortal aperture, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable bowed towards Red Lotus' true meaning solemnly: "I take my leave, I will definitely send him here."

…

Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes, the dazed expression slowly dissipated from his eyes.

He went through this memory that Red Lotus Demon Venerable had left here and understood the cause and result of everything.

"I never expected to directly arrive at the stone lotus island. Red Lotus Demon Venerable and Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, even though both have already perished, their arrangements are still in effect."

Fang Yuan sighed before looking at Red Lotus' true meaning as well as rank eight regret Gu that was already floating before him.

Red Lotus' true meaning smiled: "Fang Yuan, you are finally here. There is no need to say anything else, I believe you will try your best to destroy fate Gu. So, accept my true inheritance, it has already waited for you for over a million years!"

Fang Yuan nodded and extended his hand, trying to grasp regret Gu.

Red Lotus' true meaning reminded him quickly: "Careful, regret Gu cannot be touched directly, otherwise even if you refine it, you will be drowned in endless regrets! I have already prepared a method for you, you only need…"

"There is no need for that." Fang Yuan's expression was indifferent as he grabbed regret Gu and instantly refined it.

Red Lotus' true meaning was stunned: "You…"

Chapter 1679: Red Lotus' True Inheritance

The surging river was always flowing from past to present to future.

Fang Yuan stood at the edge of Red Lotus' stone island, looking at the River of Time with a tranquil expression and a deep gaze.

The River of Time could be said to be the most special secluded domain of heaven and earth.

Because it traversed the entire world, without its existence and movement, the whole Gu Master world would become a still picture without any changes or vitality.

Fang Yuan had seized Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, these two secluded domains of heaven and earth belonged to him, but he absolutely could not seize the whole River of Time.

This secluded domain of heaven and earth belonged to all beings of this world.

Every beast, every grass, every rock, every drop of water, they all enjoyed the benefits derived from the River of Time.

Even Gu Immortals could at most only possess a tributary of the River of Time in their immortal aperture.

The River of Time was the collective wealth of the whole world.

Every drop of the water of time was a transparent pale white. A gazillion droplets of water crashed, intertwined, collided, and spun each time, giving off a brilliant light show. Thus, the surface of the River of Time was always covered in a thin layer of ever-changing radiance.

This was the area with the greatest amount of time path dao marks in the whole world, the largest congregation of time path.

Fang Yuan stood at the edge of the island and saw several year beasts, a one finger flow shark, and large numbers of time path wild Gu worms in just a short while of observation.

The River of Time was overflowing with vitality.

Several days had passed since Fang Yuan arrived at this Red Lotus stone island.

In this period of time, he had completely absorbed Red Lotus' true meaning, his time path attainment level soared rapidly, reaching an unimaginable height — time path quasi-supreme grandmaster!

With this attainment level, Fang Yuan had many new insights when he looked at the River of Time. These feelings were not superficial, instead it pierced into the essence of the River of Time, mesmerizing Fang Yuan the more he looked at it. Pinnacle profundities of the Great Dao were in front of his eyes, quietly lifting a corner of a mysterious veil, allowing him to begin understanding this world and the principle of its operation.

Although he gained refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment previously, his experience at that time had not been as deep as now. After all, Fang Yuan was currently in the secluded domain of heaven and earth, River of Time.

Time path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level gave Fang Yuan comprehensive growth in all aspects.

For instance, the mysterious immortal killer move time cutting edge, Fang Yuan now had the ability to completely understand its essence and change the Gu worms involved, restoring its original might.

Another example was Xia Cha's time path Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves, Fang Yuan could now modify them and make them suited for himself.

The greatest growth was in time path Immortal Gu recipes. With both time path and refinement path at quasi-supreme grandmaster level, Fang Yuan had a very high assurance in modifying any time path Immortal Gu recipes and refining time path Immortal Gu.

There was no doubt that Red Lotus' true meaning was the most valuable treasure. Below it was the rank eight Immortal Gu — Regret.

Not mentioning this Gu's legendary status, just based on its rank eight level, its value was extraordinary.

With this Gu worm, Fang Yuan now had five rank eight Gu worms: Attitude, Wisdom Sword, Years Flow Like Water, Soul Beast Token, and Regret.

Fang Yuan could now construct Regret Pool with no obstacles.

Of course, difficulty was still there, but the greatest hurdle had become non-existent because of regret Gu. Back when Red Lotus Demon Venerable arranged this true inheritance, he had deduced Fang Yuan's situation and thus prepared a large amount of time path immortal materials.

With regret Gu and time path immortal materials, Fang Yuan only needed to follow the procedures and spend some time to construct Regret Pool. He could even build an Immortal Gu House better than Regret Pool.

With all these, Fang Yuan could begin to refine Gu en masse. On one hand, he could refine a lot more time path Immortal Gu, on the other hand, he could advance the rank of the Immortal Gu he already had.

These time path immortal materials left behind by Red Lotus Demon Venerable were of high rank, the lowest was rank seven while there was a large amount of rank eight immortal materials.

Were Heavenly Court to see this, they would cough out a large mouthful of blood. They tried all methods to disturb Fang Yuan and obstruct him from purchasing time path immortal materials without hesitating on paying a huge price. This had indeed created huge trouble for Fang Yuan, but all their actions turned out to be of no use now.

Red Lotus' true meaning, rank eight Immortal Gu Regret, large amounts of time path immortal materials, as well as immortal killer moves.

Among the immortal killer moves, the greatest gains were immortal killer moves that used Spring Autumn Cicada as the core. The most important thing Fang Yuan cared about was the spring autumn success killer move, this move used several supplementary Immortal Gu and with the activation of Spring Autumn Cicada, its success rate would reach one hundred percent!

Simply using Spring Autumn Cicada had too low of a success rate, it also had the disadvantage of greatly decreasing luck. But although spring autumn success immortal killer move still had the disadvantage of reducing luck, the failure rate was lowered to zero.

With this move, Spring Autumn Cicada's practicality obtained an enormous boost! Fang Yuan had already decided to prepare this killer move.

Almost all the immortal killer moves were in the form of information and required Fang Yuan to personally prepare them. But one time path killer move had been specially activated by Red Lotus Demon Venerable and left for Fang Yuan. The former rank nine killer move, after over a million years, had its power greatly reduced but was still effective.

The name of this time path killer move — Future Self!

This move relied on the River of Time and Red Lotus' stone island, the Gu Immortal user could temporarily borrow the use of a certain future state of his life.

For instance, a Gu Master who had only rank five cultivation, but in the future, would successfully pass his ascension tribulation and become rank six. Under the use of future self, he could borrow the body of his future Gu Immortal self and temporarily gain a Gu Immortal's cultivation level.

Even Fang Yuan was speechless at the mysterious and terrifying powers of this move.

Unfortunately, this move had already weakened to rank seven level and was of no use to Fang Yuan.

In Red Lotus Demon Venerable's deduction, Fang Yuan would have rank seven cultivation when he found this stone island. But Red Lotus Demon Venerable was after all not a wisdom path Immortal Venerable, even if he were a wisdom path Immortal Venerable, there could still be flaws in the deductions. Especially in the situation when fate Gu was injured and luck path emerged, everything had become much more difficult to predict.

"My cultivation is already rank eight, I can only give this future self killer move to my subordinates."

"This can make up for their lack in strength and have the qualifications to participate in my battles."

"What a pity that I lost so much manpower before this."

The complete content of Red Lotus' true inheritance was extremely plentiful and indeed worthy of being Red Lotus Demon Venerable's true inheritance. But Fang Yuan was still slightly disappointed.

The thing he had most expected was some kind of method or a shortcut to pull a fast one and destroy fate Gu.

However, Red Lotus Demon Venerable did not leave behind such things.

Even in the memory left by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, it only portrayed his experiences of becoming an Immortal Venerable and his regretful life later on. As for how he refined Spring Autumn Cicada or how he invaded Heavenly Court and injured fate Gu, there were no memories of them.

The memories had directly skipped to Red Lotus Demon Venerable constructing the Red Lotus stone island after becoming a venerable. What was the deeper meaning behind such an arrangement?

Fang Yuan had inquired before he consumed Red Lotus' true meaning.

The reply of Red Lotus' true meaning was: There was no shortcut to destroying fate Gu. Even if Red Lotus Demon Venerable had exploited some kind of shortcut back then, that shortcut no longer existed now. Don't underestimate Heavenly Court. If there was any shortcut, be extra careful as it should be Heavenly Court's trap!

As for why Red Lotus Demon Venerable did not leave behind more memories, Red Lotus' true meaning did not have an answer. He only gave speculation: "He might not have wanted to point you towards a specific direction because it could easily lead to misunderstandings. Whether or not to destroy fate Gu is your own choice."

Fang Yuan asked: Where are the other Red Lotus stone islands?

Red Lotus' true meaning did not know.

However, this reply was within Fang Yuan's expectation.

If every Red Lotus stone island could mark the other islands' locations, they would have already been taken by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable or Heavenly Court. To prevent such a situation from happening, Red Lotus Demon Venerable specially constructed each Red Lotus stone island separately without the ability to sense the others' locations.

"Fate Gu must be destroyed!"

A Heavenly Court with or without fate Gu were two completely different concepts. If Heavenly Court successfully restored fate Gu, although Fang Yuan would not be bound by the shackles of fate, other people or beings in the world would be influenced or even manipulated by fate.

At that time, Fang Yuan's enemies would be everyone and everything besides him!

This was slightly exaggerated, but it was that serious.

Another more important reason was that fate Gu's existence was the greatest obstacle to Fang Yuan's pursuit of eternal life.

Fate Gu did not allow revival, it stated that all living beings must die.

Thus, no matter what, Fang Yuan would have to destroy fate Gu.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable might have already deduced this, so he was not worried about Fang Yuan's motivation.

Chapter 1680: Advancing Immortal Gu

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Central Continent.

Dark clouds covered the sky as thunder rumbled and lightning flashed.

Fang Yuan's time path clone was standing high in the sky, he was observing the Gu refinement process cautiously to prevent any accidents.

Under the dark clouds, the originally wide plain was now filled with deep craters.

Bolts of lightning struck the ground, smashing the earth and creating half-spherical craters. The soil inside the crater was refined into a ceramic-like structure with smoke rising up from them.

"The time is right, my main body should be making a move!" The time path clone just had this thought when countless lightning bolts converged together into one enormous lightning bolt!

Boom—!

The deep blue lightning bolt resembling a heavenly pillar struck a white boulder at the center of the plain fiercely.

Instantly, the white boulder was split into pieces by the lightning bolt, countless fragmented rocks flew out everywhere.

The lightning was incomparably fierce, it had suddenly converged together and vanished just as suddenly.

The white boulder that was the size of a hill exploded, but a small Gu worm floated in the air.

The Gu worm was in the form of a butterfly with various colors, it was man as before Immortal Gu.

"I finally succeeded after failing six times, not bad, not bad!" Fang Yuan's time path clone was exulted upon seeing this.

Man as Before came from Tai Bai Yun Sheng, its origin could be traced back to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

The original man as before Immortal Gu was only rank six, which was only effective in healing rank six Gu Immortals and had barely passable effects on rank seven, often failing in its activation. Its effect on rank eight was even more abysmal. Fang Yuan could use it effectively because of his sovereign immortal body's characteristic — different kinds of dao marks did not conflict with each other. But now that he was currently rank eight, rank six Man as Before was clearly too weak.

But now, man as before Immortal Gu was successfully advanced from rank six to rank seven!

Fang Yuan's time path clone inspected it carefully and soon discovered the difference between rank seven Man as Before and the rank six version.

They both had the shape of a butterfly, but the rank seven Man as Before was much more dazzling. Moreover, there was a change in the butterfly's body, it looked like a tiny naked and pale person.

Although rank eight Man as Before was more suitable for Fang Yuan, he was currently satisfied with advancing it to rank seven.

Refining rank eight Immortal Gu would need countless cultivation resources which Fang Yuan currently did not have the ability to bear.

Back then, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had almost emptied out his accumulation to refine rank eight Fortune Rivalling Heaven, every member of Snowy Mountain blessed land had complained about it. What's more, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had cultivated for much longer than Fang Yuan in this life.

This was unless Fang Yuan spent his entire fortune like selling Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, Reverse Flow River, or wisdom Gu to exchange for countless resources. But that was not worth the loss, Man as Before might be a superior Gu, but it was not a crucial Gu worm like Spring Autumn Cicada.

Fang Yuan did not have the extravagant hope of refining rank eight Immortal Gu. He intended to advance most of his rank six Immortal Gu to rank seven.

Because of the high quantity and the difficulty of Gu refinement along with high failure rate, even if Fang Yuan invested all his current resources, it would hardly be enough.

Fang Yuan had gained batches after batches of cultivation resources from the grotto-heaven of the Five Xiangs, Qi clan's grotto-heaven, the Blue Dragon Whale grotto-heaven as well as Red Lotus' stone island.

However, Gu refinement was a bottomless pit, no matter how much investment was done, it would never be high enough.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan obtained regret Gu, which he used to construct a refinement path Gu formation that allowed a small portion of the Gu refinement process to be done again if it failed.

When Fang Yuan's time path clone took the rank seven man as before Immortal Gu, the dark clouds had already vanished. The refinement path Gu formation slowly activated and along with the killer move self cleansing, they cleaned the dao mark traces left at the scene.

"Next is Landscape as Before." The time path clone thought.

In the list of Gu refinement plans, Man as Before and Landscape as Before were at the top but there were still a lot more left.

For example, day Gu, Self Strength, Pulling Mountain, Strength Qi, Vajra Thought, Star Eyes, Star Thought…

Unravel mystery Immortal Gu was also important, after its rank was advanced, it could greatly increase the power of unravel dream, which was extremely beneficial in Fang Yuan's dream path cultivation.

There were also Dog Shit Luck, Qi Luck, Luck Inspection, Connect Luck, and Time Luck, these luck path Immortal Gu would also be an enormous help after they were advanced.

Fang Yuan was lacking offensive methods in luck path, but its support function could not be neglected. Previously, Fang Yuan had used his luck path superiority to get rid of the pursuit of the multiple time path Immortal Gu Houses of Heavenly Court.

Advancing the ranks of Immortal Gu was all done by Fang Yuan's main body, the time path clone did not have enough qualifications because of low cultivation level.

After receiving Red Lotus' true inheritance, Fang Yuan continued to stay in Red Lotus' stone island.

Besides him repeatedly refining Gu, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan and so on were also moving around on the island. They exchanged pointers with each other and did their best to adapt to their future self.

Under the effect of future self, their battle strength climbed to first-rate or even the peak of rank seven.

This was already the limit of the killer move.

With his subordinates' strength rising to this level, there would no longer be awkward situations like before. Next time Fang Yuan battled, these people would have the minimum qualification to take part in the battle.

The regrettable thing was that Fairy Miao Yin, Lady White Rabbit, and Sixth Hair were dead. Although Fang Yuan still had several enslaved Gu Immortals like Qi clan's Gu Immortals, these people were far less reliable than the former. They were bound by a slave agreement which could very well dissipate under the power of their future self. So, Fang Yuan did not intend to elevate them even though the future self killer move could still be used on several more people.

Advancing Immortal Gu became Fang Yuan's most important project and occupied almost all of his time. Occasionally, he used Fixed Immortal Travel's killer move to teleport to the Five Xiangs grotto-heaven and continue refining the killer move heaven form.

Fang Yuan had already obtained the true inheritance and was the owner of this Red Lotus stone island, thus he could use Fixed Immortal Travel to travel back and forth.

Before this, this Red Lotus stone island had been protected by Red Lotus Demon Venerable's strength, which prevented methods like Fixed Immortal Travel.

This was the same situation as in the immortal aperture inside the blue dragon whale.

Fang Yuan had already tested it but unfortunately, he was unable to return to the dragon whale grotto-heaven with Fixed Immortal Travel.

Also, Spring Autumn Cicada might have reached rank seven, which expanded its detection range, but Fang Yuan did not go to look for other Red Lotus stone islands.

Firstly, his current strength had not increased a lot, he still needed to process his gains.

Secondly, Heavenly Court was also searching in the River of Time, Fang Yuan would have to avoid them if he ran into them.

Finally, Fang Yuan's rank eight immortal essence reserve was still accumulating because advancing Immortal Gu spent a lot of immortal essence.

Time passed, several months went by quickly.

Southern Border.

Boom—!

Earth tremored and mountains shook, rocks and stones flew in all directions as an Earth Trench appeared. The vast aura of a wild Immortal Gu spread everywhere.

"This wild Immortal Gu has finally appeared!" In the clouds, three Gu Immortals looked at the ground with smiles on their face.

"Alright, let's compete according to the agreement we set earlier."

"Yes. Earth veins are stirring more intensely and wild Immortal Gu appear from time to time. We need to finish our battle quickly."

The three Gu Immortals fought fairly, the atmosphere was harmonious.

The influence of Southern Border's righteous path super force alliance was becoming increasingly larger.

Previously, Wu Yong led the Southern Alliance but was unable to deal with Fang Yuan, instead Fang Yuan used the pretense of undergoing tribulation to plot a trap in five regional mountain range. But it was not like the Southern Alliance had no gains, they obtained Tao Zhu's true inheritance. After Lu Wei Yin rescued many Southern Border rank seven Gu Immortals from Fang Yuan's hands, he represented Paradise Earth's force and officially joined the Southern Alliance.

It was perhaps due to Fang Yuan that the Southern Alliance's righteous path Gu Immortals restrained themselves, as they had a common enemy.

They were inwardly apprehensive that as Southern Border's earth veins fluctuated repeatedly and cultivation resources appeared one after the other, Fang Yuan might suddenly come to fight over them. So, Southern Alliance Gu Immortals did not fight each other to death, instead their fights became controlled.

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei's brows rose up in joy when she heard the report.

"Dragon Palace has been found! This is good news, Lord Duke Long had all along been searching for it and now, our Heavenly Court has discovered the Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace."

Dragon Palace was an extremely powerful Immortal Gu House, even Heavenly Court placed great importance on it.

"This Immortal Gu House has a deep relationship with Lord Duke Long, I should tell him this news first."

When Duke Long obtained this news, he immediately brought Feng Jin Huang to Heavenly Court and handed her over to Fairy Zi Wei to look after.

Several days later, Duke Long returned without anything.

Fairy Zi Wei was surprised, Duke Long was extremely powerful, in this current world, what methods could actually obstruct him?

"Dragon Palace is actually surrounded by a layer of dream realm, I cannot enter it." Duke Long sighed.

Fairy Zi Wei immediately understood the reason after hearing this reply, she consoled Duke Long: "Lord Duke Long, you do not need to worry, the formation is already ready, it can use the strength of the whole of Heavenly Court's grotto-heaven to suppress Spectral Soul. We will soon obtain his dream path research results."

Duke Long laughed joyfully and said 'good' three times.

Spectral Soul's dream path research results naturally referred to the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique. With this method, Heavenly Court could condense dream realms into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, the dream realm surrounding Dragon Palace would be easily removed.

"That demon Fang Yuan has made no move recently?" Duke Long asked.

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head: "Ever since he escaped from the River of Time, there has been no news of him. Currently, all five regions are facing frequent movements of earth veins with Southern Border's situation being the greatest, countless cultivation resources are being churned out. I really hoped he tried to loot these resources and gave us the opportunity to track him. But unfortunately, it is like he has completely disappeared, I have been using wisdom path methods to analyze every bit of information but have not been able to find his traces."

Duke Long nodded: "Continue to pay attention to him, even though this demon has reached rank eight, he has to face stronger calamities and tribulations now. This will definitely give him a headache. Although he can annex apertures with the sovereign immortal body, he needs rank eight grotto-heavens to skip grand tribulations. Furthermore, there is still the even more terrifying myriad tribulation!"

Even Fairy Zi Wei felt her heart palpitate when she heard the mention of myriad tribulation, she nodded with a smile: "Lord Duke Long is right, Fang Yuan might have advanced to rank eight but how many rank eight grotto-heavens are there for him to annex? His cultivation won't change much within a short period of time."

"Currently, Fang Yuan lacks resources, especially time path resources. It will be almost impossible for him to face the arrangements we made in the River of Time, that means he will have no chance at getting Red Lotus' true inheritance."

"Although he escaped before, his immortal essence expenditure was extremely huge and nearly all his trump cards were exposed. He needs to quickly accumulate rank eight immortal essence, because relying on immortal essence stones has too low efficiency, he can only rely on his immortal aperture's self-production. But the immortal aperture's self-production requires time, if he quickens the rate of time of his immortal aperture, he will also accelerate the arrival of his calamities and tribulations as well."

"Once he has no more immortal apertures to annex, he will have to face tribulations."

"The time he undergoes his tribulation will be the time our Heavenly Court takes his life!"

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes glistened brightly when she said this.

Duke Long nodded, looking at Fairy Zi Wei with praise: "With you taking charge of Heavenly Court, I am at ease."

Chapter 1681: Progress

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Central Continent.

Fang Yuan's time path clone was slowly flying in the air as he planted the last flower bud.

The terrain here had already been modified by him into a marshland that was extremely fertile, a large amount of high quality silt was spread here. There was also a knee-deep clear river above the layer of silt.

The time path clone patted his hand and flew to the sky after giving a last glance at the flower bud.

Standing on a high altitude, the man-made marshland entered his sight. This marshland was vast, Fang Yuan's time path clone was unable to take in the whole marshland in his sight.

A flower bud, the size of a house, could be seen every few kilometers. These flower buds had quite an origin, they were the buds of a desolate plant, extreme marsh flower.

Fang Yuan had obtained a small portion of the extreme marsh flowers in the blue dragon whale's immortal aperture, while the rest were bought from treasure yellow heaven.

After taking in the view, Fang Yuan's time path clone breathed in deeply and activated summer Gu.

Summer Gu came from Southern Border's rank eight Gu Immortal Xia Cha, and was also at rank eight. Fang Yuan's time path clone was only at rank six and would not be able to use summer Gu by just himself. However, Fang Yuan's main body had white litchi immortal essence which he gave to his clone along with summer Gu. By lending his clone the necessary tools, Fang Yuan's time path clone could utilize almost all the Immortal Gu of his main body.

Summer Gu's activation was followed by other supplementary Gu worms which activated an immortal killer move.

Xia Cha had developed a set of time path killer moves to manage the immortal aperture: spring ploughing, summer hoeing, autumn harvest, and winter storage.

The killer move which Fang Yuan's time path clone activated was not one of them but was modified from summer hoeing, it was used specially to raise extreme marsh flowers.

Extreme marsh flowers bloomed at the height of summer and bore fruit in spring.

Fang Yuan's time path attainment was at quasi-supreme grandmaster, it was at the peak of the world. Along with the light of wisdom, it was simple for him to modify time path killer moves.

Following the continuous activation of the killer move, all the surroundings entered the height of summer, light rays became brighter, the temperature increased rapidly and the air became increasingly dry.

The peak of summer had arrived, the extremely vigorous extreme marsh flowers felt all these and began to absorb nutrition from the water and soil, growing at a visible rate and started to slowly bloom.

Every extreme marsh flower was huge and looked like a trumpet with its petals connected. They were primarily white with a few parts bearing slight hints of pink.

The knee-deep water was already emptying, the marshy soil had also become dryer. The fertility of the soil was being expended intensely.

Fang Yuan's time path clone looked calm, this was within his expectations.

Cultivation methods of extreme marsh flowers were mentioned in detail in both Red Lotus' true inheritance and Shadow Sect's true inheritance, all these changes were within Fang Yuan's arrangements.

Soon, strands of white mist started rising slowly from the pistil of the extreme marsh flowers.

These mist gradually spread and covered a large area. Fang Yuan's time path clone stopped the killer move, the air immediately became very moist.

The mist nurtured the soil, gradually transforming this man-made marshland.

"Let's name this marshland flower mist extreme marsh. The first step is finished." Fang Yuan's time path clone observed with joy.

"It won't be an issue to feed regret Gu with this scale of extreme marsh flower mist."

Rank eight regret Gu's appetite was huge, its food was the mist produced by extreme marsh flowers. The problem was that this mist needed to be fresh. So it was not practical or reliable to purchase them from outside.

"When the mist condenses to a certain extent and forms a layer of water on the ground, I can then plant water vegetation as well as bring in small lifeforms like ducks and flying fish."

"Then, I will continue to expand the scale of extreme marsh flowers. When regret Gu becomes hungry, the accumulated extreme marsh flower mist will be enough to fill it."

The feeding of rank eight Immortal Gu often required a huge project.

"With this area of extreme marsh flowers, the sovereign immortal aperture's development is now at eighteen percent. Currently, I have greatly slowed down the rate of time of the immortal aperture, so the production of various resources and white litchi immortal essence has fallen."

Fang Yuan pondered inwardly.

This time, he did not use time path immortal moves to slow down his immortal aperture's rate of time, instead he manipulated the year essence pool which was much more convenient. It did not expend immortal essence and also did not have some disadvantages of time path killer moves, Fang Yuan could adjust his immortal aperture's rate of time whenever he wanted.

"Although I need to accumulate immortal essence, I cannot blindly quicken the time, or else, the tribulations will come quickly as well."

Currently, Fang Yuan was already at rank eight but his battle strength had not increased by a lot. Previously, he had exposed almost all his trump cards when he faced Heavenly Court's ambush in River of Time, so it was not suitable for him to undergo tribulation at this time.

Once he placed his immortal aperture to undergo tribulation, Fang Yuan would become a fixed target. Because he would have to open his immortal aperture which would be sensed by heaven's will, Heavenly Court and other forces could easily discover his location and besiege him.

"The rate of time has been slowed down, but I can still manage my immortal aperture, increasing the foundation of my immortal aperture and expanding my immortal aperture origin core, thus producing even more white litchi immortal essence."

The better the immortal aperture's management, the more immortal essence would be produced.

A long time ago, Fang Yuan managed his immortal aperture to feed his Immortal Gu. Later, he managed the immortal aperture to increase the production and earn immortal essence stones as well as cultivation resources. Currently, his target was to accumulate white litchi immortal essence.

Purely refining immortal essence stones to white litchi immortal essence had too low of an efficiency. Ten thousand immortal essence stones were required to turn into one bead of white litchi immortal essence.

Fang Yuan's immortal aperture could produce one hundred white litchi immortal essence every year, in terms of the outside world's time, that was over half a month.

Time passed as Fang Yuan continued to cultivate in seclusion. It was now summer in the five regions.

Although there were no traces of Fang Yuan, the whole Gu Immortal world of the five regions was in an excited state.

Whether it be righteous path, demonic path, or lone immortals, they were all hectic.

The reason for this situation were the tremors in five regions earth veins.

New Earth Trenches appeared constantly, they first appeared in Southern Border, but this situation was happening frequently throughout the other four regions as well.

Rumble…

Dust and soil rose, Hong Yi fell down on the ground in exhaustion. He was panting and his face was pale as he looked at the enormous ravine in front of him.

When the earth vein shook, he and other Gu Masters began to run wildly.

This was an extremely thrilling escape!

There were a few times when Hong Yi was able to keep his life only because of his good luck.

He had almost fallen in but during the crucial moment, he was able to exert more strength than usual and was able to jump towards the precipice.

"Since when did earthquakes occur here! That was dangerous, I almost lost my life here." Hong Yi stood up only after a long while, but his breathing was still rough. He looked at the ravine and saw only darkness, rough wind blew in the ravine as dust and soil had yet to dissipate.

"Every area of Central Continent seems to be experiencing earthquakes during this time period, creating ravines like this." Even a mortal like Hong Yi felt such a violent change in the world.

"Eh? What is that?" A wild Immortal Gu slowly flew out of the dust and smoke.

An injured wild Immortal Gu flew with difficulty, swaying left and right before it was finally exhausted and fell beside Hong Yi's feet.

Hong Yi was dumbfounded!

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei gave a cry as her whole body let out dazzling purple light.

Following the light, the whole Heavenly Court actually shook slightly, an incomparably enormous formless force poured into the large immortal formation.

The immortal formation rumbled loudly as it started grinding down on Spectral Soul who was locked up at the center.

Spectral Soul resisted with all his might but was unable to defend, his deepest memories were being extracted.

"Alright, I finally obtained the mysteries of the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, hahaha." Fairy Zi Wei was haggard and pale but her expression was of excitement.

She had been working extremely hard these last days, on one hand, she was dealing with earth vein tremors which were bringing forth unexpected situations all over Central Continent, on the other hand, she was strengthening her efforts on dealing with Spectral Soul.

She had put in great efforts to obtain Shadow Sect's dream path research results as soon as possible, activating the whole of Heavenly Court's might in empowering the immortal formation.

Hard work paid off, Fairy Zi Wei finally obtained a breakthrough!

In the blink of an eye, it was the height of summer. Sunlight was scorching but it was not as fiery as the fire in Gu Immortals' hearts.

Earth vein tremors showed no signs of stopping or reducing, instead they became more intense. Immortal materials, wild Immortal Gu, and all kinds of cultivation resources appeared constantly, creating a festive period in all five regions.

Within the Five Xiangs grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan's laughter suddenly echoed.

"I have finally obtained full grasp of the killer move heaven form!" Beside Fang Yuan was the rank nine killer move in the form of a white crane, it was standing obediently and quietly, following Fang Yuan's orders.

"Who could have thought that heaven form's effect is actually this."

"With it, my cultivation might be able to progress rapidly, the issue of calamities and tribulations can also be resolved!"

Fang Yuan stroked the white crane's feathers with bright eyes.

This heaven form killer move came at the perfect time!

Chapter 1682: Searching for Grotto-Heavens

Immemorial white heaven.

An exquisite, pure white crane was flying around Fang Yuan while letting out melodious cry.

Fang Yuan could command this white crane with his thoughts and it was as easy and simple as moving his hand.

"I can finally use this rank nine killer move!" Fang Yuan was endlessly moved as he said softly: "Go."

White crane flapped its large wings and nimbly flew ahead, but before it reached far, it started circling around a part of the sky while emitting cries constantly.

Fang Yuan's lips curled up as he received a series of information from the white crane that showed the inner scenes of the grotto-heaven of the Five Xiangs.

Rank nine killer move heaven form was not an offensive or a defensive killer move, but an investigative type.

Its detection target was everything that existed in immemorial white heaven!

Its detection range was extremely wide, far surpassing Fang Yuan's limits, thus it would be extremely helpful to Fang Yuan in plundering all kinds of natural resources in immemorial white heaven.

Its detection ability was also extremely strong.

How strong?

It could discover hidden grotto-heavens!

Any grotto-heaven, as long as they were in immemorial white heaven, would be detected by heaven form even if they did not open their immortal aperture entrance. Once the white crane was nearby, it could gather information about the inner scenes of the immortal aperture.

Naturally, its detection range towards grotto-heavens was far smaller than ordinary targets.

It had another advantage: it did not use any immortal essence during the whole detection process. The rank nine immortal move heaven form originated from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, it was truly extraordinary, it was like the detection was the innate ability of the white crane.

"But if I want to forcibly intrude into a grotto-heaven, I need to use immortal essence." Fang Yuan's lips curled up as he slowly transferred rank eight white litchi immortal essence.

With the addition of immortal essence, heaven form's whole white crane body began to emit soft and gentle light.

Fang Yuan slowly flew closer, letting the soft light cover him.

At the same time, a hazy white light appeared inside Five Xiangs grotto-heaven.

Fang Yuan followed the white light and several breaths later, he was inside Five Xiangs grotto-heaven, the whole process faced no obstruction.

Although Five Xiangs grotto-heaven was already controlled by Fang Yuan, at this moment, he had successfully entered the grotto-heaven just by relying on heaven form.

"Quite a high immortal essence expenditure, but thinking about it, I am a rank eight Gu Immortal while the killer move is at rank nine level, spending this much white litchi immortal essence cannot be considered a flaw."

"Although there is some white light, the entire process is quiet. Not bad, not bad."

Fang Yuan nodded, satisfied with the result of this trial performance.

It was extremely difficult to charge into a blessed land or grotto-heaven without proper preparations. For example, one could refer to the time Immortal Crane Sect invaded Hu Immortal blessed land or when Heavenly Lord Bai Zu attacked Hei Fan grotto-heaven, their difficulties sufficiently proved the value of heaven form!

"In the long span of history, how many Gu Immortals have appeared? Although it is not easy to become a rank eight, throughout the millions of years, they are absolutely not few in number."

"When Ren Zu's children destroyed the other immemorial seven heavens, only immemorial white heaven and immemorial black heaven remained. After that incident, rank eight Gu Immortals or rank nine Gu Immortals basically only had these two choices to place their grotto-heavens."

"Not mentioning rank nine Gu Venerables, when those rank eight Gu Immortals die, their immortal apertures would often be placed in either immemorial white or black heaven."

"These grotto-heavens would fall down or perish because of the continuous calamities and tribulations, but at the same time, new rank eight figures would appear. So, there must be a portion of these grotto-heavens currently in immemorial black and white heaven."

These grotto-heavens were great supplements to Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

If he annexed one of them, he could skip calamities and tribulations and thus resolve his greatest hidden threat!

Naturally, the precondition was he had to find an immortal aperture grotto-heaven and have the ability to annex them, at the same time, this grotto-heaven must not have devoured any fragment of the immemorial nine heavens.

An immortal aperture grotto-heaven that had annexed any nine heavens fragment would have no more calamities and tribulations, but it would then be filled with heaven's will which could not be cleansed. Fang Yuan could not annex such grotto-heavens, so Five Xiangs grotto-heaven and Hei Fan grotto-heaven were not in his consideration. Although Qi clan's Qi Sea grotto-heaven did not annex a nine heavens fragment and had been relying on the immortal killer move unlimited qi sea to resist calamities and tribulations, Fang Yuan's qi path attainment level became the obstruction to annexing it and it would not be easy to solve this any time soon.

As for the dragon whale grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan had considered it but he was unable to return to the blue dragon whale with Fixed Immortal Travel as it had already moved far away from its previous location. And with Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements in the dragon whale grotto-heaven, even if Fang Yuan had the ability to annex it, he did not dare to make such a move rashly.

Who was to say Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had not arranged some hidden methods in the dragon whale grotto-heaven that were specially waiting for Fang Yuan.

None of the Gu Venerables could be underestimated!

"There are definitely grotto-heavens which suit me." Fang Yuan was confident in this.

This confidence was not only because he had heaven form, it was also because in the five hundred years of his previous life's memories, there had been many grotto-heavens which had appeared during the five regions chaotic war and been a part of the vast changes of the new era.

Among them, Fang Yuan had the deepest impression of Nine Phantoms grotto-heaven. Almost all the Gu Immortals of this grotto-heaven mainly cultivated phantom path, the entire grotto-heaven could turn into phantom form and thus be unaffected by calamities and tribulations.

There was also Dao Formation grotto-heaven, this grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals were extremely proficient in formation path with layers of large formations tightly protecting the whole grotto-heaven.

There was also Holy Deceit grotto-heaven, this grotto-heaven's origin was even greater, its original owner had a close relationship with Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. After he passed away, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable personally made arrangements in Holy Deceit grotto-heaven that caused heaven's will to make wrong judgments about this grotto-heaven, the might of many calamities and tribulations were reduced greatly and were passed extremely easily.

These grotto-heavens were living in seclusion while cultivating Gu Immortals.

Every grotto-heaven contained many Gu Immortals, they were all genuine super forces.

However, there were very few rank eight Gu Immortals.

It was difficult to nurture a rank eight Gu Immortal with just the resources from a grotto-heaven.

As such, powerful super forces were all based in the five regions which possessed rich and enormous amounts of resources, at the same time, the large population and intense competition between each other hastened the arrival of rank eight Gu Immortals.

Summer went and autumn came. The turbulence of earth veins was becoming more frequent and numerous, Gu Immortals welcomed this harvesting season.

Western Desert.

A delicate and beautiful female immortal lightly shot an arrow.

The arrow pierced the sky while leaving behind a trailing arc of light pink and struck an ancient desolate beast.

This ancient desolate beast had been moving rampantly the previous moment, but at the next moment, its whole body let out all kinds of lights as it collapsed to the ground loudly.

Strong wind mixed with yellow sand blew, the entire ancient desolate beast turned into petals and dissipated completely.

"It is actually her!"

"Gong clan's second young miss Gong Wu Hua!"

"Let's leave quickly."

A group of Western Desert Gu Immortals reluctantly looked at the newly created Earth Trench before retreating cleanly.

Southern Border.

Rumble!

Mountain ranges collapsed, causing dust to surge over hundreds of li.

The earth quaked as a huge Earth Trench appeared, devouring the mountain ranges tyrannically.

Ba clan's two Gu Immortals were looking at this with shock.

"This is a famous mountain — Sunny Mountain! It was actually destroyed by the Earth Trench, such a pity…"

Ba De's gaze shone with cold light: "Hehe, what's there to pity? The old mountain has collapsed, there will be a new one in the future. Didn't we discover a large amount of new spirit springs in our way?"

"That's true, earth vein turbulences are not only bringing wild Gu and Gu materials, they are also giving birth to many spirit springs."

"Do you think that is all?" Ba De looked down with no expression but his face showed great expectation: "Experts are popping out one after the other in the Gu Immortal world, didn't Western Desert see the rise of Gong Wu Hua recently?"

"Lord Ba De, how could that Gong Wu Hua compare to you?"

"Hmph, how can you underestimate the heroes of the world? But wait until I advance to rank eight, Gong Wu Hua won't be any threat indeed." Ba De said proudly.

The other Ba clan Gu Immortal was shocked and joyous: "Lord, you, you are finally advancing to rank eight?"

"I was on guard against various influences before, but now the Southern Alliance is established while the Alliance Leader's position is still up in the air. Most crucially, there are countless cultivation resources appearing unceasingly which are enough for me to advance to rank eight."

"Naturally, there is one main reason." Ba De's expression turned solemn: "An unprecedented great era is descending and I don't wish to be swallowed by the tides of this era."

Chapter 1683: Venerable Talent

Chirp chirp chirp!

A large group of blinking birds, that were surrounding a seven-colored cloud, were flying around while chirping constantly to warn the invader.

Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil but his gaze carried the trace of a smile.

The blinking birds' warning was naturally nothing to him.

This species of bird was a desolate beast, but they had low battle strength, they could not cause harm even with such a large scale. Their true power was in speed.

Blinking birds were considered the fastest desolate beast, once their speed erupted, they could escape the sight of a Gu Immortal in the blink of an eye, thus having their name.

Fang Yuan had concealed his aura and seemed like a mortal. But these blinking birds simply did not attack him, they innately sensed a pressure from the seemingly harmless Fang Yuan.

Suddenly, a trace of aura leaked out from Fang Yuan's body.

Swoosh!

At the next moment, the blinking birds burst forth, disappearing within an instant. The seven-colored cloud that was densely surrounded by the birds was now floating alone.

Fang Yuan sighed, he had intended to capture these blinking birds, but these blinking birds had an extremely fast response time and Fang Yuan was also not highly proficient in concealing his aura.

However, it did not matter if they escaped, even if he subdued the blinking birds, they would not be easy to raise. Their food was the white heaven floating dust that was specific to immemorial white heaven, it was not easy to gather and a Gu Immortal's immortal aperture could not produce them.

Fang Yuan slowly flew closer to the seven-colored cloud.

"I didn't expect to run into a seven-colored cloud soil." Fang Yuan sighed.

This thing looked like a cloud but was actually a kind of soil — cloud soil.

In Lang Ya blessed land, Lang Ya land spirit had condensed a large amount of cloud soil to form Cloud Cover Continent, which always remained afloat in the sky of Lang Ya blessed land.

Cloud soil's greatest production area was in the immemorial nine heavens. Naturally, there were also a small number of resource points producing cloud soil in the five regions.

A single colored cloud soil was at most an ordinary Gu material, for example, immemorial yellow heaven's yellow cloud soil or immemorial red heaven's red cloud soil. In the present era, the most common single colored cloud soil in the market was white cloud soil, which mostly originated from immemorial white heaven.

Immemorial black heaven also had a lot of black cloud soil, but it was very risky as there were many soul beasts in black heaven.

Once the cloud soil had six colors, it would be a rank six level immortal material. The seven colored cloud soil in front of Fang Yuan was a rank seven immortal material, and the value of such a large quantity was very high.

After inspecting this large patch of seven colored cloud soil, Fang Yuan discovered there were many bird nests in this soil and they contained many eggs.

These were the blinking birds' eggs!

Fang Yuan was not surprised as the behavior of the blinking birds showed that they seemed to be protecting something. In fact, blinking birds were extremely cowardly even though they were desolate beasts, if there was even a slight disturbance, they would immediately fly away with their fastest speed.

Fang Yuan could incubate these eggs for blinking birds. Incubating desolate beasts was not easy but it would not be much of an issue to Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan did not want to hatch them, instead he wanted to use these eggs as immortal materials to use when refining Gu.

Blinking birds had quite a strict diet and it was not easy to raise them. If he were to raise them, he would have to release them to immemorial white heaven from time to time, and this was too troublesome.

Fang Yuan had deep pockets and did not care about profits from blinking birds.

Ever since he refined the killer move heaven form over a month ago, Fang Yuan had been moving about in immemorial white heaven.

On one hand, he was searching for immortal materials in immemorial white heaven, on the other hand, he was refining Gu in his sovereign immortal aperture.

A month in the outside world was a long time in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan had obtained great success in refining Gu!

Man as Before, Landscape as Before, Self Strength, Pulling Mountain, Pulling Water, Dog Shit Luck, Time Luck, and others were already advanced to rank seven.

He had changed his original Gu refinement plan slightly, advancing luck path Immortal Gu with priority. Over these days, he had similarly gained great harvests in immemorial white heaven, obtaining many immortal materials. This was due to the effect of these rank seven luck path Immortal Gu.

Besides advancing ranks through refinement, Fang Yuan was also improving Gu refinement techniques.

He knew way too many Gu recipes and also knew countless Gu refinement techniques. His refinement path attainment level was at quasi-supreme grandmaster, but he was lacking in experience.

Especially in the aspect of refining Immortal Gu, he did not have a lot of experience at all.

Genuine knowledge came from practice.

Over this period of time, he had repeatedly advanced the ranks of his Immortal Gu from which he discovered many of his problems and remedied all of them. At the same time, he also discovered many more Gu refinement techniques that suited him.

At present, Fang Yuan had gained a lot of new insight and inspiration on Gu refinement. The success rate of his refinement had also increased by a large degree.

There were still continuous earth vein turbulences in five regions, Gu Immortals obtained immortal materials and Immortal Gu, it was a time of great joy. But after thinking deeply, Fang Yuan still chose to explore immemorial white heaven.

If he went to snatch resources of the Earth Trenches from the five regions Gu Immortals, he would have to show himself and might very likely end up fighting.

Each Immortal Gu's advancement increased Fang Yuan's strength by a little. But the degree of this increase was unable to offset the situation from exposing his trump cards in the River of Time.

He needed time to quietly absorb these gains.

Once an intense battle began, his accumulated rank eight white litchi immortal essence would be expended intensely.

Fighting with Gu Immortals was much more dangerous than fighting fierce beasts.

Although Fang Yuan spent immortal essence when exploring immemorial white heaven and there were many battles as well, he was relying on heaven form, which had a precise detection ability.

If there were beasts that were too troublesome or powerful, he would take a detour.

Heaven form's detection range in immemorial white heaven was truly very large and could even easily discover many concealed beasts and plants.

After all, it could even detect hidden grotto-heavens, it was natural for it to discover these fierce beasts and plants.

The more amazing part was that heaven form did not use even a trace of Fang Yuan's immortal essence. This rank nine killer move had unquestionable superiority and power! Fang Yuan had already exclaimed praise for it multiple times.

Exploring the five regions surpassed exploring immemorial white heaven in terms of danger and expenditure, and it was not as good as the latter in terms of benefits.

Gu materials and immortal materials emerged endlessly from Earth Trenches, but these things needed Gu Immortals to arrange them properly before storing them into the immortal aperture.

Managing an immortal aperture was not easy, many resources were interrelated or affected each other.

As a result, most of the Gu Immortals in the five regions would sell these immortal materials obtained from Earth Trenches in treasure yellow heaven.

Their immortal apertures had limited space and could not be compared to Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture. Many times, the immortal materials they obtained did not suit their immortal aperture's environment.

There was another phenomenon because of the unceasing earth vein turbulences, that was treasure yellow heaven's business, more accurately, the transactions between Gu Immortals had increased explosively! Treasure yellow heaven was dozens of times as bustling than before.

If Fang Yuan wanted any immortal materials, he could totally buy them from treasure yellow heaven.

But grotto-heavens were different, every grotto-heaven already had a complete and harmonious ecosystem. When Fang Yuan annexed them, it would save him a lot of trouble and there was no need to consider anything. He could even increase the sovereign immortal aperture's size, his cultivation and dao marks would also increase by a large degree, and calamities and tribulations could even be skipped.

The benefits of annexing a grotto-heaven were too great.

As for the wild Immortal Gu that occasionally emerged from Earth Trenches, Fang Yuan was envious of course, but these wild Immortal Gu had always been top priority for Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan felt it was better for him to directly rob other's Immortal Gu from the grotto-heavens since he had great thief ghost hand.

Heavenly Court.

The large formation slowly stopped, Fairy Zi Wei opened her eyes which shined with sharp light.

She mumbled: "Soul replacement killer move? Such ingenuity!"

Before leaving, she gave another glance at Spectral Soul but did not try to make him surrender.

Over these days, Fairy Zi Wei had been frequently plundering Spectral Soul's memories, seizing his lifetime's cultivation gains.

Fairy Zi Wei could not help but admire Spectral Soul's shocking talent and also acknowledge that in the field of soul path, even if Heavenly Court had already put in enormous efforts, they still could not match Spectral Soul.

"Such a pity that Spectral Soul is currently reduced to a prisoner. It really is a tragedy, he is the most destitute among all the venerables. Actually, if he had remained dead, his name would have been left gloriously in history. Now, he cannot even seek death…"

Thinking of Spectral Soul who was still stubbornly resisting, Fairy Zi Wei once again gritted her teeth hatefully.

She was sure Spectral Soul still had important dream path research results, that was lead soul into dream.

Although Heavenly Court had already deciphered most of this move, it would still be extremely valuable if Heavenly Court obtained it.

Unfortunately, Spectral Soul kept on resisting, although he could not shoulder the entire Heavenly Court grotto-heaven's strength, he was extremely crafty, he would leak some minor information and stall for time.

The first time Fairy Zi Wei used Heavenly Court's strength, Spectral Soul was caught off-guard and the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique's information was stolen.

But when he recovered, Spectral Soul adopted the strategy of abandoning less important information to protect the true secrets, he was still resisting firmly.

"But your actions are in vain!"

"We have the advantage of time."

"The Refinement Path Convention's preparations are already undergoing. Fate Immortal Gu will be completely restored, at that time, Spectral Soul will fall into fate's tracks and have no way to escape."

"The future of the great era belongs to our Heavenly Court!"

Fairy Zi Wei thought of Feng Jin Huang.

After obtaining the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique's information, Duke Long gave these research results to Feng Jin Huang, which could be considered as his first genuine knowledge imparting. Although these research results were someone else's work.

Because they needed to use Feng Jin Huang's Immortal Gu, they needed to deduce suitable immortal killer moves for her so that they could resolve the dream realm surrounding Dragon Palace.

Fairy Zi Wei spared no effort in deducing the killer moves, even deducing together with Feng Jin Huang.

At the beginning, her and Duke Long's goal had only been to help Feng Jin Huang grow slightly faster. But who could have thought that after the deduction succeeded, Feng Jin Huang even found a method to improve the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique.

Creating a brand new Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body with none of its previous flaws. It could last indefinitely!

"The talent of a venerable is truly too terrifying. In front of them, even I feel like I am just an ordinary person…" Fairy Zi Wei sighed mentally.

Chapter 1684: Profound Literature Grotto-heaven

Immemorial white heaven.

Fang Yuan was moving forward on an auspicious cloud.

Half of his concentration was in the sovereign immortal aperture and the other half was on guard.

If it were before, Fang Yuan could not have split his concentration when refining Gu. But his gains were truly huge during this recent period of time.

He lacked neither attainment levels nor Gu recipes, his only shortcoming had been insufficient hands-on practice.

Personally refining Gu helped him grow rapidly in this aspect, his success rate in refinement increased greatly and so the amount of immortal materials wasted had also decreased by a lot.

Refining Immortal Gu had always been a sinkhole, besides Gu refinement, Fang Yuan was also plundering all kinds of natural resources from immemorial white heaven.

He sold a portion in treasure yellow heaven and bought items he needed for refining Gu and managing his immortal aperture.

Treasure yellow heaven's business was especially bustling, the turbulence in earth veins created a pressing demand for exchange of goods in the five regions Gu Immortal world, immortal material transactions in the market were very popular now.

Naturally, the most popular business was still time path immortal materials.

Heavenly Court did not stint on suppressing Fang Yuan, they would purchase all time path immortal materials even with a high price, showcasing an inexhaustible strength, displaying the robust and terrifying foundation of Heavenly Court!

If Heavenly Court found out that Fang Yuan had already obtained one of Red Lotus' true inheritances and possessed large amounts of time path immortal materials, who knew how they would feel?

"There are still two rank six Immortal Gu left, the others have all been advanced to rank seven. Eh?"

Fang Yuan's body suddenly shook.

The auspicious cloud suddenly increased in speed. After a while, Fang Yuan saw heaven form.

The crane form killer move was continuously circling around an ordinary looking spot that seemed to just be made of air.

"It discovered a grotto-heaven." Fang Yuan was joyous.

Using the detection of heaven form, this grotto-heaven's inner scenery was constantly transmitted to Fang Yuan's mind.

"So this grotto-heaven is called Profound Literature grotto-heaven… It is actually a rank eight information path Gu Immortal's immortal aperture… Oh? There is such a large population and they even have a unique cultivation style!"

Fang Yuan could not help but feel curious.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven's population was even larger than Lang Ya blessed land's hairy men. Using an initial estimation, there was also a good number of Gu Immortals.

This grotto-heaven mainly had information path dao marks, thus its environment naturally was suited to produce information path resources. Therefore, the Gu Masters and Gu Immortals here mainly cultivated information path and used information path Gu worms.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven had already been isolated from the outside world for many years, but because it had annexed an immemorial nine heavens fragment, its heavenly spirit was muddle-headed.

However, the immortal killer move of the original owner of grotto-heaven was still effective. This move was called — Assisting Literary Talents, it seemed to be effective for as long as the grotto-heaven existed and its effect was extremely unique.

As long as a purebred human created or recited outstanding poems or writings of any kind, they would obtain recognition and reward from this grotto-heaven. Mortals could sing good poems to attract hope Gu from far away and awaken their aperture. Gu Masters could create amazing poetry verses to obtain Gu worms or even raise their cultivation directly.

"It is somewhat of a pity that I cannot annex this grotto-heaven, I have quite a lot of poetic masterpieces stored in my mind."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily as he transferred his immortal essence into heaven form.

Heaven form slowly started to emit light which moved into Profound Literature grotto-heaven. Fang Yuan flew into the white light to enter the grotto-heaven.

"Such guts! Which vile fiend dares to invade my homeland?!" A vast and mighty voice resounded from within, speaking with righteousness.

Next, an old man in a white robe and resembling a scholar, possessing rank eight aura, showed up in front of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was still inside the white light and could not make a move. The old man pushed his hand without any hesitation, countless literary characters manifested immediately and shot forward like a storm.

Heaven form did not have any offensive ability, the torrent of characters poured in and the white light crumbled. Fang Yuan's situation became awkward, he could not advance, he could only take the initiative to retreat.

"There is actually a rank eight Gu Immortal here!" Fang Yuan was slightly surprised.

According to normal situations, a rank eight Gu Immortal would rarely be born inside a grotto-heaven because the grotto-heaven's resources were not enough to support the emergence of a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Moreover, this Profound Literature grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit was in a muddle-headed state and could not open the immortal aperture's entrance, so Gu Immortals could not easily come out.

Even if this rank eight Gu Immortal had some skills and could secretly come out to immemorial white heaven and plunder immortal materials, the risks were too high. There were many immemorial desolate beasts and immemorial desolate plants in immemorial white heaven along with all kinds of strange and dangerous areas which could pose threats to even rank eight Gu Immortals. This was not a backyard for rank eight Gu Immortals, they not only needed luck to gather resources here, they also had to take risks.

"Let's try another area." Fang Yuan reorganized himself and poured in immortal essence into heaven form for the second time.

Heaven form was a rank nine killer move, it could connect to any grotto-heaven. He connected from the sky the first time, now he chose to enter from underground.

However, when he stepped into white light again and tried to sneak into Profound Literature grotto-heaven, that rank eight Gu Immortal appeared timely before him again.

"You still dare to try again? With me here, you will never succeed!" The rank eight Gu Immortal immediately attacked.

Fang Yuan was still inside the white light and felt helpless as he was unable to activate any other methods.

With no way left, he could only let the white light be destroyed by the enemy while he retreated to the outside world once again.

Fang Yuan's expression was unavoidably dark.

He pondered: "The two areas I chose should be vastly apart from each other, but I was actually detected and obstructed immediately. What defensive method is this?"

It was not strange that he was detected.

After all, Profound Literature grotto-heaven was an information path grotto-heaven and information path was most specialized in detection, gathering intel and spreading news.

However, the rank eight Gu Immortal enemy was able to appear before Fang Yuan promptly, what method was this?

Fang Yuan tried a few more times using not only heaven form killer move but also Fixed Immortal Travel killer move as well, but was still found out and blocked.

Fang Yuan required a very short time to pass through the white light, but this short period of time seemed endlessly long under the obstruction of the rank eight Gu Immortal.

At this moment, Fang Yuan experienced what Heavenly Lord Bai Zu felt when attacking Hei Fan grotto-heaven. His strength was clearly higher than the opponent, but with the enemy blocking the entrance of the grotto-heaven, he was not able to enter the grotto-heaven and this felt really unpleasant.

"Profound Literature grotto-heaven, I will be back." Fang Yuan chose to leave.

Anyway, he already knew the position of Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

It had annexed a nine heavens fragment and could not be moved anymore.

While Fang Yuan left with nothing, Duke Long brought Feng Jin Huang to the bottom of the sea somewhere in Eastern Sea.

Flood dragons roared, raising undercurrents and raging waves, but were helpless against Duke Long.

Everything was tranquil around Duke Long as Feng Jin Huang stood quietly beside him.

Duke Long brought Feng Jin Huang further down. Suddenly, there was a layer of ripple in front of Feng Jin Huang, as if they had broken a layer of formless membrane. Her pupils shrunk slightly as she discovered a large palace at the bottom of the sea.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House — Dragon Palace!

The whole palace shone with slight orange-gold light and was richly decorated, the pavilions and terraces were all grand and beautiful. However, Dragon Palace was surrounded by a large dream realm.

The dream realm was constantly moving and its movement was quite fast. Dragon Palace was obscured from time to time by the dream realm, enticing the visitors.

The dream realm kept on changing and moving, although some gaps appeared occasionally which seemed to let others enter Dragon Palace, Duke Long was extremely cautious and would rather wait than take unnecessary risks.

Right now, he already had a method to deal with this dream realm.

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

He had borrowed Feng Jin Huang's dream wings Immortal Gu while the deduction of the immortal killer move was led by Fairy Zi Wei.

Under the effect of the killer move, a small piece of the dream realm quickly transformed into a human body with closed eyes.

"This is a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body, moreover it is perfect with no flaws." Duke Long's eyes shone as he carefully sized it up. He had once been harmed by a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body thus he was slightly moved.

"Huang Er, your modification is truly brilliant! From now onwards, this Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique can be considered the eleventh extreme physique!" Duke Long praised.

Feng Jin Huang blinked her eyes: "Master, to be honest, I was only able to do so by coincidence. Because I created the killer move shatter dream previously, this modification was done based on its results. I had only thought of giving it a try, but who could have thought, it would truly succeed!"

Duke Long smiled: "No need to be insecure, my good disciple. Do you think your creation of shatter dream was a coincidence? This is part of fate's arrangement. It is fate that…"

Feng Jin Huang immediately pouted: "Master, can you stop saying things like that? I don't want to hear such words. If everything is fate's arrangement, then what's the point of me doing anything?"

Duke Long was stunned and wanted to say something but only gave a long sigh: "Alright, alright, let's not talk about this now. Now is still too early for you, when the time comes, I believe you will comprehend it."

Chapter 1685: Beast Calamity Grotto-Heaven

Central Continent, Earth Trench.

Roar…

A giant desolate beast monkey let out its final roar, it wanted to stand up, but facing the tiny human Gu Immortal before it, it felt its whole body freezing.

This coldness seemed to penetrate the soul itself, even freezing its heated blood.

Immortal killer move — Blood Turns Cold!

The attacker was none other than Fang Yuan's brother, Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

"Congratulations Fang Zheng, you are already able to freely utilize blood turns cold after these few days of use in combat." Zhao Lian Yun slowly flew closer and said with a smile.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng looked at the frozen giant monkey corpse, the red light in his eyes slowly dissipating. His expression was tranquil as he expressed his gratitude to Zhao Lian Yun: "I am flattered. It was all thanks to you protecting me from the side over these days, otherwise, how would I gain such good opportunities to practise my killer move."

The turbulence in Central Continent's earth veins was quite frequent and all the super forces fell into an awkward situation where they did not have enough manpower. To suppress their own internal situation, Immortal Crane Sect had sent Fang Zheng out.

Naturally, Fang Zheng's movement was constantly monitored by Heavenly Court, and as long as there were no mishaps, Heavenly Court was happy to see Fang Zheng growing stronger.

Fang Zheng was saved by Feng Jiu Ge and returned to Central Continent, receiving the support of Heavenly Court. Not only did he obtain blood revenge Immortal Gu, he also obtained cold blood Immortal Gu during his immortal ascension.

Fairy Zi Wei had already made proper arrangements, giving blood turns cold and other immortal killer moves to Fang Zheng. Now, he was already proficient in the killer move blood turns cold and could use it proficiently in battles.

Eastern Sea, at a certain area in the depths of the sea.

Duke Long and Feng Jin Huang had already been refining the dream realm for several days now.

The dream realm surrounding Dragon Palace was much larger than they thought; Duke Long had used the killer move Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation to refine dozens of Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, but new dream realms were still spreading out from Dragon Palace to fill the gaps.

Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation was only a rank six killer move and had limited might because its core Immortal Gu, Dream Wings, was only at rank six.

Actually, after condensing the first Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body, Duke Long could borrow this special vessel to move in the dream realm freely and enter Dragon Palace.

But Duke Long's objective this time was this rank eight Immortal Gu House. Without eliminating this dream realm, he would not be able to safely take this Immortal Gu House.

While Duke Long was condensing Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, Feng Jin Huang was cultivating wholeheartedly.

She was mainly researching the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body, sometimes, she would move her soul into a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body, and sometimes, she would research in her main body.

"Shadow Sect's Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique pursued stability so it could not live long."

"Dream realms are ever-changing, their special trait is uncertainty. So I walked the path of shatter dream and made it more unstable, the result was that under the deduction of Lady Zi Wei, double negative turned into positive, obtaining the perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique."

Every time Feng Jin Huang thought back to this, she felt she had gotten lucky.

"Could it be this is the effect of fate? It wants to borrow my efforts to bring forth the perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique?"

Feng Jin Huang quickly shook her head, getting rid of this thought.

She recalled the words of her master, Duke Long —

"Huang Er, although you have researched the perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, it is still not enough. You need to research this achievement thoroughly to use it in your cultivation. When you find out how to advance your physique to Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, it will be the time for your immortal ascension."

Gu Immortal!

Feng Jin Huang's accumulation was already enough for immortal ascension, but she was always stopped by Duke Long.

Now that Duke Long finally relented, Feng Jin Huang was very excited but also in a dilemma, how could she understand Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique thoroughly?

Feng Jin Huang was pondering about this issue as Duke Long waited patiently.

"Am I pushing her too hard?"

"After all, transforming her own physique into the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique involves the profundities of human path!"

"<<The Legends of Ren Zu>> clearly stated the ten extreme physiques were created by Ren Zu, these are all human path profundities. Perhaps I can impart my gains when I read <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> back then to her."

Duke Long was known as the ancestor of the dragonman. The birth of the new variant human race — dragonman, was brought about by Duke Long alone.

And Duke Long's achievement was a result of his comprehension of <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>.

"Although I took Feng Jin Huang as my disciple, I have not taught her anything. She probably cannot meet my requirements, but it is better if I teach her the profundities of dragonmen. Of course, I still need to warn her that she must not create any dragonmen!"

"No, according to her nature, she might secretly create them. Huang Er is different from Hong Ting, especially her personality and perception of fate… Sigh, people's hearts have changed since ancient times. This kind of dangerous thinking should be unrelated to Bai Qing, it is probably Feng Jiu Ge's influence."

Duke Long had naturally investigated Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Bai Qing.

Achoo!

Feng Jiu Ge rubbed his nose, his body was filled with bloody stains. He mumbled: "Who is talking behind my back?"

He was in a very miserable state, his robe was mostly torn apart, revealing his robust and muscular chest.

"Cough, cough."

He suddenly coughed up blood.

Two Gu Immortals who were hidden revealed themselves, they looked at Feng Jiu Ge's heavily injured appearance but had joyous expressions: "Congratulations Lord Feng Jiu Ge on advancing to rank eight!"

"Mm." Feng Jiu Ge nodded lightly, he felt no excitement towards his rank eight cultivation. In fact, he could have advanced to rank eight long ago but there had never been a suitable opportunity.

There were always all kinds of shackles holding him back. After all, he had a family and was also the most important member of Spirit Affinity House.

"Rank eight cultivation level is no big deal, although I now have white litchi immortal essence, I will need time to accumulate it."

"I don't have enough funds to advance my core Immortal Gu to rank eight."

"Even if I have the funds, I will need others to help me refine Gu."

"Maybe I can rely on Heavenly Court for this?"

Feng Jiu Ge thought about his Dao Guardian status which had a lot of exploitable value.

"But the crucial thing is the inspiration I got from <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> when undergoing the tribulation. Perhaps I can create a song about destiny from this."

"Heaven and earth has fate, everything is arranged by it. But after luck path was born, there was room for change. Everything and everyone in the world has the chance to shine brilliantly now."

"Destiny song will portray this brilliance, it will describe the certainty and uncertainty of heaven and earth as well as the paths of all life!"

A period of time passed yet again.

Immemorial white heaven.

Fang Yuan gazed excitedly at the heaven form crane which was flying around in circles.

"Found it, I have finally found a second grotto-heaven."

"This is… Beast Calamity grotto-heaven?"

"Good, it has not annexed any nine heavens fragment!"

Chapter 1686: Giant Monster Fang Yuan!

After searching for so many days, Fang Yuan found another grotto-heaven and it had not annexed any nine heavens fragment!

"But this is a transformation path grotto-heaven, my transformation path attainment level is somewhat insufficient."

Master, grandmaster, great grandmaster, supreme grandmaster… Fang Yuan was a grandmaster in transformation path, he was lacking attainment by an entire level.

The lack of attainment level was not an issue because it could be resolved with dream realms.

Southern Border had plenty of transformation path dream realms, which were enough for Fang Yuan to breakthrough to great grandmaster attainment in transformation path, it was just that he would have to face some hurdles.

Besides dream realms, Fang Yuan had another backup method for transformation path attainment level. It was to use calamity beckoning Immortal Gu, immortal tribulation tempering aperture, as well as Reckless Savage's true meaning in the northern icy plain.

"The original owner of this grotto-heaven was a transformation path rank eight Gu Immortal who had passed one myriad tribulation."

Rank eight Gu Immortals had to pass three myriad tribulations, after that was rank nine.

Myriad tribulations were terrifying and were also called apocalyptic myriad tribulation. To rank eight Gu Immortals, there was a huge danger of dying but also the chance to rapidly progress in their cultivation.

One myriad tribulation and two myriad tribulations were classifications of a rank eight Gu Immortal's cultivation level.

If Fang Yuan annexed this grotto-heaven, his cultivation would immediately soar to one myriad tribulation level, such terrifying progress could definitely make Heavenly Court panic.

Duke Long and Bo Qing were also only at two myriad tribulations level, passing the third myriad tribulation would be rank nine.

Duke Long, however, knew he was not cut out for that so he merged his immortal aperture with Heavenly Court, changing to a phantom aperture. On the other hand, Bo Qing tried to advance but perished.

"Since this Beast Calamity grotto-heaven has not annexed a nine heavens fragment, how did it pass the calamities and tribulations?"

It would not be easy for it to repeatedly pass calamities and tribulations just using its own strength.

In the past, Lang Ya land spirit was afraid of calamities and tribulations so he lowered his grotto-heaven to a blessed land. This was a very wise choice, of course the method to downgrade a grotto-heaven to blessed land was extremely rare and was not something any grotto-heaven could use.

Heaven form flew in circles while transmitting information.

Fang Yuan discovered a peculiar phenomenon: This grotto-heaven's calamities and tribulations were of one kind, they were all beast calamities.

Beast calamities were a type of tribulation, sometimes, they would be formed from desolate beasts, and sometimes from ancient desolate beasts.

In this grotto-heaven, heavenly tribulations were desolate beast calamities, grand tribulations were ancient desolate beast calamities, and myriad tribulations were immemorial desolate beast calamities.

"What method is this? It can actually restrict the type of calamities and tribulations? If everything is a beast calamity, it will be really easy to deal with them. After all, beasts have physical form and are not difficult to block unlike rain, wind, and fog."

As heaven form's continued to probe, Fang Yuan discovered deeper information.

He sighed: "So this grotto-heaven is not restricting calamities and tribulations, but transforming any calamities and tribulations into a beast calamity. Truly an amazing method!"

There were many kinds of calamities and tribulations, but their formation would be influenced in this Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, transforming into ferocious beasts in the end.

Apart from calamity beckoning Immortal Gu and immortal tribulation tempering aperture, Fang Yuan finally encountered another method that was targeted towards calamities and tribulations, that was beast calamity transformation!

"Every grotto-heaven that can continuously exist is not simple. Profound Literature grotto-heaven is like this. Beast Calamity grotto-heaven is even more so."

"This is truly an unexpected surprise!"

"This grotto-heaven contains a huge population and countless resources, and more importantly, the method of beast calamity transformation. I need to get this method, it will be very useful in dealing with my tribulations."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan transferred his white litchi immortal essence to the heaven form crane.

A while light slowly expanded as Fang Yuan flew in.

He was not blocked by any rank eight Gu Immortal this time because there was no rank eight existence in this Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

However, when he was entering, the whole grotto-heaven started shaking. A profound and vast strength came from every direction, not only influencing the white light but also exerting pressure on Fang Yuan.

"What is this?!" Fang Yuan was slightly bewildered at first before quickly reaching realization.

There was a strange expression on his face: "So it is like this. I am not from this grotto-heaven and came from the outside world, because my strength is too powerful and the grotto-heaven wants to reject me, it is treating me as a tribulation."

This Beast Calamity grotto-heaven could transform calamities and tribulations into all kinds of beasts, currently, this force was influencing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan pondered: "It is possible to forcibly resist this strength, but I fear our fight might end up destroying this method. Although heaven form discovered several inheritance grounds which the original owner left, what if the beast calamity transformation method is not recorded there?"

Just in case, it was better to maintain Beast Calamity grotto-heaven in its original state and not destroy any crucial arrangement.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan boldly retracted his defenses, he then felt endless temporary transformation path dao marks being added to his body. At the same time, his other dao marks also changed into transformation path dao marks!

"Amazing, amazing! Transformation path can project every path, transformation path dao marks can transform into any path's dao marks. Right now, this transformation has been turned upside down, changing other paths' dao marks into transformation path dao marks." Fang Yuan sighed and praised repeatedly: "This method is beyond ordinary, it seems to involve the deepest profundity of transformation path! It feels like I only need to get in and out of here a few times and let this influence affect my body to comprehend the true essence of this method."

"Of course, the quickest method is to charge to those several inheritance grounds and seize the true inheritances there, I can check if there is the original record of beast calamity transformation!"

Fang Yuan's body was transforming and constantly expanding. He gradually turned unrecognizable as he transformed into a beast.

If not for heaven form already inspecting clearly that this transformation had no side effects, Fang Yuan would not have dared to accept this kind of influence.

Bellow—!

After a while, Fang Yuan turned into a large monster with a bull head and human body. He was as large as a mountain, his skin as tough as steel, bull hair filled his body, and his nose let out rough breathing noises as he took large steps forward.

The whole Beast Calamity grotto-heaven was shaken!

Countless people looked at the sky and saw Fang Yuan, after a momentary daze, screams and shouts filled the sky.

"Mon… monster!"

"A monster has appeared again!!"

"This monster is so large, its aura is also completely different from the previous ones."

"Quick, quickly call our beast warriors!"

Under countless people's anxious anticipation, a Combat Beast Warrior appeared.

This was a middle-aged man with rank seven Gu Immortal cultivation level, but his aura was somewhat strange.

He looked plain and his expression was serious as he moved to the top of the city wall.

"There is only one record of such a huge monster appearing in history. I can feel an incomparably terrifying force with just one glance at it."

He sighed inwardly while clenching his fists, the fire of battle intent rising in his eyes: "But for my homeland, to defend love and justice, I will defeat this monster no matter what. Come, my combat beast — Transform[1]!!!"

The middle-aged man shouted loudly and his whole body started to emit light.

Shortly, an eagle cry could be heard, a silver-white giant eagle flew over from the horizon. This was an ancient desolate beast!

The silver-white giant eagle's body also started to emit light.

The middle-aged man jumped while the silver-white giant eagle swooped down, the lights on both grew increasingly brighter and when the two met in the air, the two lights merged together.

Boom!

The lights dissipated. With an eagle head, human body, and two wings on his back, a beast warrior as tall as the city wall showed up.

The crowd immediately cried out in joy.

"He's here, our Eagle Warrior has appeared!"

"Go Eagle Warrior, kill this giant monster!"

"We support you, you will definitely succeed!"

Amidst the crowd's cheers, Eagle Warrior flew to the sky and charged towards Fang Yuan.

He cried out in his mind: "I won't let anyone down! Come, let us have a great fight…"

Bam!

A crisp sound echoed, the silent Fang Yuan slammed down on Eagle Warrior with a single slap.

Boom!

Eagle Warrior's body drew an arc in the sky like a falling meteor before fiercely colliding on the ground, forming a huge crater with dust flying everywhere.

"…" The crowd went silent.

An intense dizziness almost sent Eagle Warrior unconscious.

He used all his strength to conquer it before barely subduing the dizziness, he then slowly climbed out of the deep crater.

"What happened? I… I was actually slammed to the ground by this monster?" Eagle Warrior reacted only after a long while.

Recalling that scene, his eyes revealed an intense fright.

"That speed just now… This is absurd! How can such a large body move have such nimbleness? This is impossible!"

[1] Henshin! Back

Chapter 1687: Monster Rampages

"Normally, such an enormous monster should have a boorish nature with great strength, it is impossible for it to have such agility and speed!"

Eagle Warrior stood up from the deep crater, his head was filled with cold sweat. Suddenly, he thought of a possibility: "Wait a second, could that attack be this monster's combat technique?"

He looked at Fang Yuan who had turned into a giant monster with bull head and human body, the enormous shadow shrouding Eagle Warrior.

Eagle Warrior slowly regained his courage as he thought about this.

"You have a combat technique, I also have a combat technique! I already know your combat technique, but a stupid large animal like you cannot understand my combat technique."

"That's right, as long as I can grasp the opportunity, I definitely have the chance to win!"

Thinking of this, Eagle Warrior's eyes emitted hopeful light.

"He stood up, he stood up!"

"That's right, how could Eagle Warrior be knocked out instantly?"

"Go, Eagle Warrior, we believe in you!"

Seeing Eagle Warrior stand up, the dead silent city suddenly erupted into heaven-shaking cheers.

An eagle cry resounded.

Eagle Warrior flapped his wings and flew to the sky again.

"You have a combat technique, I also have a combat technique! Monster, let me show you, my combat technique — Silver Illusion!" Eagle Warrior shouted.

At the next moment, his body suddenly turned illusory, splitting into six illusory images, they were all lifelike and had no difference from the real body. In an instant, the real and fake Eagle Warriors surrounded Fang Yuan and flew above him in a circle.

The commotion in the city immediately surged to a whole new level!

"Look, it is Eagle Warrior's silver illusion combat technique!"

"He finally used it, look! That monster looks dazed, it does not know which one to attack."

"The chance of victory is here, go, kill that giant monster."

"Ahhh~… Eagle Warrior is truly too cool!"

Eagle Warrior heard the cheers of the crowd which amplified his courage and battle intent in his heart.

But he was cool-headed inwardly: "I must use this chance to make a definite strike, even if I cannot kill this monster, I need to be able to heavily injure it. After all, combat techniques consume a huge amount of stamina and cannot be used repeatedly!"

"That's why, even if this monster is powerful, it cannot repeatedly use its combat techniques. I will first use illusions to make it attack and waste its stamina. After it depletes its own strength, when it has no stamina left, I might be able to capture it alive!"

Eagle Warrior actually wanted to capture Fang Yuan alive, although Fang Yuan could not sense this thought, he clearly saw through Eagle Warrior's combat technique.

Eagle Warriors constantly buzzed around Fang Yuan, occasionally, one or two suddenly swept down and attacked Fang Yuan with their sharp claws and beak.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot without evading, these Eagle Warriors were all illusions with no real threat in their attacks. In Fang Yuan's eyes, it was a dead giveaway.

Fang Yuan was calm and composed, laughing inwardly: 'This grotto-heaven is somewhat interesting.'

First of all, the interaction between mortals and Gu Immortals was interesting.

They were harmonious.

Different from the five regions outside world where mortals were like ants and Gu Immortals were high and above, in this grotto-heaven, Gu Immortals were the guardian spirits of mortals. More importantly, they were even keen to take on this guardian duty.

From this point, Fang Yuan could see the trace of a paradise.

But this was not strange.

Every grotto-heaven formed its own small world. If there was little contact with the outside world of the five regions, the grotto-heaven would form a different social structure and create a style unique to itself.

Secondly, the battle style and cultivation method of Gu Masters and Gu Immortals here was interesting too.

For instance, the opponent before Fang Yuan had merged with an ancient desolate beast silver-white giant eagle to create a kind of human-beast fusion battle form.

This was clearly a transformation path method and its advantage was extremely obvious.

Normally, Gu Immortals would need to expend immortal essence to activate Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves. But the Gu Immortals here only needed to merge with a desolate beast and could possess combat techniques.

The so-called combat technique was just the innate abilities of some desolate beasts or ancient desolate beasts. It was like Fang Yuan's upper extreme heavenly eagle which could enter and exit immortal apertures.

This innate ability was known as combat technique by the people here, it did not expend immortal essence but had a huge demand on stamina, even having some other cost like sacrificing a part of the body or some lifespan.

Be they combat techniques, Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves, if we trace their origin, they were all just in essence — Dao.

Because desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts have dense dao mark accumulation on their bodies, and the fact that certain areas in their bodies have a higher concentration of dao marks, they would possess innate abilities or combat techniques.

Immortal Gu were fragments of the Great Dao, they represented certain laws of heaven and earth.

There was no need to talk about immortal killer moves, they were usually a combination of several Immortal Gu and a large amount of mortal Gu, they were an organized combination of dao marks and Great Dao fragments which went through specific profound procedures to achieve a greater overall effect and power.

In fact, the most primitive immortal killer moves had been created by Gu Immortals who used the dao mark distribution of desolate beasts as reference. They imitated and experimented with these distributions and created immortal killer moves eventually.

"The Gu Immortals here can merge with desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts to use the beast's innate ability. They don't need to spend painstaking effort to refine any Immortal Gu and can also save on the danger and cost of training and creating immortal killer moves."

This advantage was truly prominent!

Immortal Gu were hard to find and every Immortal Gu was unique.

But there was a lot of desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts, even immemorial desolate beasts like the upper extreme heavenly eagle could be found in groups.

The desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts possessing innate talents would often look stupid because of their lack of intelligence. But after they merge with Gu Immortals, the Gu Immortals would possess their innate talents and they would also possess the Gu Immortal's wisdom. This was a win-win situation for both parties, their advantages made up for each other's deficiency!

"But this method is not flexible enough, there is only a fixed method to use when fighting. Innate abilities are not varied enough and easily targeted and restricted, they are full of shortcomings." Fang Yuan also saw through the disadvantages.

"But overall, this method's advantages are still huge, far surpassing the disadvantages. If it is popularized, the five regions will definitely welcome it with open arms!"

"Fortunately, this method was not leaked out in my previous life, otherwise my memories would have been completely different."

Because this method was simply the best way to mass produce Gu Immortal battle strength, although it could not affect high level battle strength, it was enough to turn around some situations.

The five regions had many rank six Gu Immortals who did not have even one Immortal Gu!

And these people were the majority of the Gu Immortal world in every region.

When one region had this method while another did not and they had a fight, based on the mid to low level Gu Immortal battles, the region with this method would have a high chance of winning.

"This fusion ability is not anything new but it has never prospered. The greatest obstacle is the conflict between dao marks."

"But this grotto-heaven has a method to turn other dao marks into transformation path dao marks!"

"So Gu Immortals can casually fuse with desolate beasts. This fusion method is the same as Beast Calamity's transformation method."

After deducing this, Fang Yuan wanted possession of this transformation path method even more.

"I have proper things to do, these flies should stop bothering me." As he thought to himself, Fang Yuan activated a time path method.

His current time path killer moves were no longer like before.

Eagle Warrior was still probing when he shockingly discovered that time around him had slowed down by countless times.

"This!? Time has become so slow! How is this possible?!" Eagle Warrior was thoroughly horrified.

He was quite confident in his speed but with time itself being influenced, he was unable to display his greatest advantage, speed!

"Let's end this." Fang Yuan extended his palms slowly, his ten fingers opened up and grabbed the two eagle wings.

"Darn it, darn it! Move, move!!" Eagle Warrior roared inwardly, but despite using all his strength to fly, he only flew a meager distance.

Swish!

At the next instance, Fang Yuan exerted strength, tearing apart the two wings instantly!

"Ahh—!" Eagle Warrior's expression was twisted in pain. Blood flowed out from the wounds on his back, gushing out wildly like a fountain.

"Eagle Warrior!!!"

"No—!"

Countless people cried out in shock, fear and horror took over their high spirits from earlier. Some even fainted on the spot while some covered their faces.

Fang Yuan slowly put his hands on Eagle Warrior's head.

Eagle Warrior's heart thumped madly as he felt an intense aura of death!

"So this was its combat technique?"

"Slowing down time, truly a terrifying combat technique."

"But… even if I die here, it was of some value. At least, I managed to expose its secret!"

Thinking so, Eagle Warrior screamed loudly: "Monster! So what if you kill me? There are still many beast warriors coming to kill you, your death is all but…"

Bam!

Fang Yuan exerted strength in between his hands, and like a watermelon smashing on the ground, Eagle Warrior's head burst, white-red brain matter and bones splattered everywhere.

Fang Yuan relaxed his palms.

Plop.

The headless Eagle Warrior corpse fell on the ground, creating a dust cloud.

Fang Yuan looked at the city.

His body was gigantic, the tall city walls could only reach his knees. His expression was tranquil but his bull head horrified countless people. White cloud moved beside his shoulders, and what should have been a clear sky was blocked by his enormous figure, his shadow shrouding everyone's heart.

There was a huge crowd in the city, but no one made a sound.

It was deathly silent.

Fang Yuan slowly moved towards the city[1].

At the next moment, like an explosion, countless people began to scream and cry as they started escaping in all directions like headless flies.

From high up in Fang Yuan's vision, these mortals looked like a group of ants that were dispersing through the four city gates.

Fang Yuan ignored them and continued to move towards the city.

Bam.

His calf knocked into the city wall, instantly causing it to collapse entirely.

He walked on the city's main street but even if it were to enlarge by five to six times, Fang Yuan's heel would still cover the whole street.

Buildings crumbled like small paper boxes as Fang Yuan knocked into them, there were also some unlucky mortals who were directly stepped into meat paste.

[1] Shingeki no Fang Yuan Back

Chapter 1688: Obstruction

Bellow—!

The monster Fang Yuan let out a roar, his giant body crossing a forest while destroying countless gigantic trees easily.

"Retreat, retreat!" Deer Warrior was holding a long spear, he was coughing out blood as he went to face Fang Yuan, using his life to fight for time for Spirit Spring Forest's inhabitants.

But in the end, Deer Warrior's neck was snapped by Fang Yuan, dying a miserable death.

The image ended here creating a buzzing commotion in the hall. Tens of energetic and vigorous warriors - men and women, old and young - were talking in low voices, their speech and expressions were filled with shock and anger.

At this time, an emaciated old man coughed twice from a raised platform.

The hall immediately fell silent, all the beast warriors looked at the old man with respectful gazes.

The old man spoke: "You have seen the images, since the Bull-headed Demon God descended, it has destroyed Sacred Eagle City, Dark Valley, and Spirit Spring Forest."

A red haired boor shouted: "Lord Combat Beast King, what are we still waiting for? Almost all the Combat Beast Warriors in the world are here and are waiting for your command to eradicate this Bull-headed Demon God!"

"Yes, Lord, give us the command."

"We can't wait anymore."

"We have already gotten information about Bull-headed Demon God, Eagle Warrior and Deer Warrior died miserably at his hands, we must avenge them!"

Many Combat Beast Warriors spoke, the collective mood in the hall was stirred into agitation.

The old man only extended his hand and pressed down, the hall fell silent once again. He continued: "Sigh, looks like you still don't truly realize the severity of this beast calamity. I know that everyone present here has outstanding battle achievements, but this monster is different from normal. More accurately, if we don't deal with this properly, it might lead to the end of the world!"

"What do you mean?"

"This monster is strong indeed but haven't there been giant monsters who have killed several Combat Beast Warriors before?"

"This monster is large and possesses two combat techniques, its time slowing combat technique is especially troublesome. But it can also be countered."

The old man shook his head, saying with a solemn expression: "This Bull-headed Demon God has bottomless strength, it could be said to be among the most terrifying beasts. You should know how the first generation Combat Beast King died, right?"

All the Combat Beast Warriors were visibly moved at these words.

"Lord Combat Beast King, you mean…"

"No way, is this giant monster at that level?"

The old man nodded slowly: "This Star Snail Hall we are currently in is the corpse of star sea snail. The first generation Combat Beast King was the strongest Combat Beast Warrior in history, but to kill the star sea snail, he had to sacrifice his life. And this Bull-headed Demon God is at the same level as the star sea snail."

The old man's reply sent the hall into complete pin-drop silence.

"So." The old man looked at his surroundings and continued: "I assembled everyone to move together to kill this Bull-headed Demon God but we actually don't have a high chance of winning. You must use all your strength for us to have a chance of victory. Please battle with the awareness that you are going to die!"

"Awareness of death…" Someone mumbled.

"Hehehe." Someone suddenly laughed.

The mood suddenly became invigorated, the Combat Beast Warriors had a similar fire burning in their eyes.

Their battle intent soared!

"I already had the awareness of sacrificing for my homeland long ago!"

"Yes, so what if I have to sacrifice my life in order to save the lives of my family and friends?"

"We can't let this Bull-headed Demon God continue to wreak havoc, so what if it is comparable to the star sea snail? I believe my fist and I believe in everyone!"

"Yes, I believe in my comrades' strength. The first generation Combat Beast King fought alone, but we are different, we have each other!"

Some people shouted, some people raised their arms, the morale continued to rise.

The old man showed a gratified smile: "Good, I am going to merge with the star sea snail's shell and transport you all. We will besiege the Bull-headed Demon God and catch it off-guard! Remember, the future of this world is weighing on your shoulders."

"We understand!!!"

The star sea snail's shell began to shake.

Fang Yuan was walking on a wasteland.

He still had the appearance of a monster with a bull head and human body, his size was as tall as a mountain, his shoulders at the height of the clouds and his steps created craters. Each step of his produced an earth-shaking sound.

"The first generation Combat Beast King should be this grotto-heaven's original owner."

Fang Yuan was already certain.

He had destroyed three locations and took away inheritances of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's original owner. These inheritances were intact, and although they had lasted for many years, they were not taken away by other Combat Beast Warriors.

"The cultivation method of merging with beasts is convenient but unfortunately is not the proper Gu cultivation method. This kind of path only gets narrower the more one walks on it, so these people aren't even aware of Beast Calamity Immortal's true inheritance."

"Hmm? Who is it?" Fang Yuan suddenly stopped, his gaze became vigilant.

At the next moment, starlight overflowed and Combat Beast Warriors appeared one after the other, surrounding him tightly.

"Monster, go and die!"

"For the peace of the world, I will have no regrets even if I have to sacrifice everything!"

"Everyone, attack together. Believe in yourself, believe in your friends. Even if the monster is stronger, it is not our match."

The battle started suddenly!

At the same time, at a certain seabed in Eastern Sea.

"Master, it's done! There are no longer any more dream realms coming out." Feng Jin Huang looked at the rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace with excitement.

Duke Long nodded.

"Our painstaking effort over the past few days was not in vain, the greatest obstacle is gone. Dragon Palace is covered by a layer of dream realms, although the framework is not disturbed, the entire Immortal Gu House has already stopped working, it is the perfect chance for us to take it now."

As Duke Long pondered, a past memory suddenly surfaced in his mind.

The red 'longevity' character written in the hall was very conspicuous.

Duke Long sat at the main seat, surrounded by dragonmen.

"Grandfather, I am here to offer birthday wishes! I wish you blessings as deep as Eastern Sea, and longevity as tall as Southern Border mountains. This is a desolate beast that I hunted personally for you, I hope grandfather likes it." A dragonman youngster half-knelt on the ground as he held a plate in front of him, there was a tiny seahorse on the plate.

"This is the desolate beast happiness seahorse, it is very fast and hard to kill."

"Seventh young master only has rank six cultivation level, it is very hard for him to kill it, but to think he actually captured it alive!"

"I heard that in order to capture this happiness seahorse, seventh young master spent a month at the bottom of the sea without moving, his filial piety is truly touching."

The surrounding people discussed, there were human Gu Immortals as well but most were dragonmen.

Among these dragonmen, there were Gu Immortals as well as mortal Gu Masters; they were all Duke Long's descendants.

Duke Long was the ancestor of the dragonmen, he created the dragonman variant human race. Seventh young master, a rank six dragonman Gu Immortal, was Duke Long's most beloved grandson.

"Good, good, grandpa accepts your gift." Duke Long smiled affectionately.

Distinguished guests and grandchildren filled the hall, this filled Duke Long's chest with warmth.

But now…

Duke Long suddenly returned to reality.

There was only the dark and cold seawater around him and that deathly silent Dragon Palace.

The past was no more, the warmth that once filled his heart had already been buried in history.

"Who is it? Come out." Duke Long suddenly spoke, his expression calm as his sharp gaze scanned several areas.

"As expected of Heavenly Court's Duke Long, you have such keen perception." An old woman slowly revealed herself. She was hunch-backed, she had deep wrinkles on her face that resembled the pattern of a purple venomous snake, extending from her face to her arms and to her whole body.

"Duke Long, we are definitely going to obtain this Immortal Gu House." Another Gu Immortal appeared, he was dressed in a white robe, he looked young and was handsome.

"Your Central Continent wants to take what belongs to our Eastern Sea? Hmph." The third Gu Immortal snorted coldly, he was robust and his triangular eyes shone with cold light.

The final Gu Immortal slowly approached Duke Long from behind, he wore a black robe, his face could not be seen, he was silent like an eerie ghost, filled with dark energy.

"Granny Rong, Yang Zi He, Shi Miao, and Zhang Yin, you are all lone and demonic immortals of Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world. Was it easy for you to cultivate to rank eight? Why are you sending yourselves to death by coming before me?" Duke Long was still relaxed even when he was surrounded by four rank eight Gu Immortals.

"No need to speak nonsense, let's fight!" Shi Miao took the lead.

A huge battle erupted!

Chapter 1689: Failure

Immemorial white heaven, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

"Bull demon, face this move!" A golden haired ape shouted as it charged towards Fang Yuan while carrying the might of wind and thunder.

Bull-headed Demon God Fang Yuan stood on the spot without moving, quietly looking at the golden haired ape approaching him. Only when the ape reached in front of him did he lift his hand slightly.

Swoosh!

At the next moment, his fist that was raised from kneel level suddenly appeared right before his chest.

A straight punch.

It was an ordinary movement, but in Fang Yuan's current state, it had terrifying might.

Before the golden haired ape could react, it felt an incomparable strength that sent it flying backwards.

Bam!

After flying a short arc in the air, the golden haired ape crashed into a mountain. Rocks and boulders were smashed and fell down, burying him.

"What kind of strength is this, even Golden Ape is not its match!"

"I have never seen such strength matched with such speed… It is indeed a monster on the same level as the star sea snail!"

Besides the buried Golden Ape, there were several Combat Beast Warriors around the battlefield, but right now, they all felt a chill as they saw Golden Ape's ending.

"Pull yourself together! This is clearly a combat technique, it will expend its stamina intensely if it uses it many times." One of the Combat Beast Warriors, Lightning Lion, roared.

Fang Yuan had already defeated most of the Combat Beast Warriors sent by Combat Beast King, but there were still five who had some strength left.

They were the strongest five Combat Beast Warriors!

There were two Lion Warriors, Lightning Lion and Dharma Lion. The former had a lion head and human body, and grasped lightning powers, while the latter had a human head and lion body, and had extremely powerful recovery.

A mountain sized mollusk, called Stone Mollusk. Its two large shells were open and could spit out countless meteor-like stones.

A gigantic rhinoceros that looked like it was forged from steel, it was called Steel Rush.

The last one was an exquisite Frost Butterfly with the size of an adult's fist, it had a human shape with butterfly wings and could let out powerful frost energy.

"Hehehe, stupid bull, you are trapped." Unknowingly, the exquisite Frost Butterfly had appeared above Fang Yuan's head.

Frost energy burst forth, covering Fang Yuan's head and shoulders and quickly spreading down.

Roar!

Steel Rush let out a loud roar as it rushed straight towards Fang Yuan, causing an earthquake.

"Have a taste of my new combat technique!" Stone Mollusk suddenly started moving in circles rapidly, letting out an astonishing speed as it closed in on Fang Yuan.

Its two shells opened and it clamped down on Fang Yuan's whole lower half.

At the next moment, Steel Rush fiercely knocked Fang Yuan to the ground.

Freezing air had frozen Fang Yuan's arms in a large block of deep blue profound ice.

"The time is now!" Lightning Lion and Dharma Lion attacked Fang Yuan's head from the left and right.

"Die!" The five of them shouted together, their battle intent soared to their peak state.

Boom—!

An intense explosion occurred, causing boundless surging air currents. The five Combat Beast Warriors were like small planks in a hurricane as they coughed out blood and were sent flying away by the air currents.

In the dust cloud, a mountain sized black figure was gradually revealed.

Fang Yuan quietly stood on his original spot, he looked at the five Combat Beast Warriors that wanted to fight him struggle on the ground, before continuing to move ahead.

Bam Bam Bam…

His every step shook the surrounding land and left behind large footprints.

"Damn it!"

"Don't leave…"

"Stop, stop it!"

Combat beast warriors struggled to stand up, but only Lightning Lion was able to barely stand up.

"It is Lightning Lion!"

"Go, you must stop this monster!"

Lightning Lion charged towards Fang Yuan without any fear once again, his gaze was filled with resolute light: "If you want to slaughter the others, you will have to step past my corpse."

Boom!

No one saw how Fang Yuan attacked, they only saw Lightning Lion getting slammed back at an even faster speed.

The giant lion's body was dragged along the ground, creating a thirty meter sized gully before it stopped.

Lightning Lion fainted, there was no movement from him anymore.

Fang Yuan continued moving forward.

He had controlled himself and did not take the lives of these people. Different from when he had just invaded, after inheriting several inheritances, his attitude had already changed. Right now, the way he looked at it, everything in this Beast Calamity grotto-heaven was his property. This naturally included these Combat Beast Warriors.

"There is the final inheritance ground left. As long as I take this inheritance, I can combine all the inheritance contents and obtain the complete contents."

Soon, Fang Yuan reached before the star sea snail.

The star sea snail was an immemorial desolate beast, but the one in front of Fang Yuan was only its corpse.

Beast Calamity Immortal had been heavily injured when fighting the star sea snail and had suffered a fatal, irrecoverable wound. On his deathbed, he had left behind the inheritances and also forged this star sea snail into the final inheritance ground.

"Bull-headed Demon God, I have been waiting for you." This generation's Combat Beast King stood on the top of the star sea snail and looked at Fang Yuan.

He was already very old and was like a small ant when compared to Fang Yuan's size.

But this ant's eyes burned with blazing flames.

Starlight suddenly shined on the star sea snail's body and covered the old man's body.

Several breaths later, the starlight became eye-piercing.

After the starlight dissipated, a heavily armored giant stood in front of Fang Yuan, only slightly shorter than Fang Yuan.

"Oh? So this method is not limited to live beasts, it can even be used on an immemorial desolate beast's corpse!" Fang Yuan was inwardly surprised.

But shortly afterwards, he understood.

This transformation path method was reliant on dao marks and did not differentiate between alive or dead targets.

Although the star sea snail was dead, its shell still retained a vast number of star path dao marks which could be used by the old man.

"This should be this grotto-heaven's greatest trump card, right? Unfortunately, even if it were a living star sea snail, it would be no match for me. Let alone its corpse that has lost so many dao marks since its death."

Fang Yuan mentally sneered as he charged towards the star armored giant.

The battle was intense but the result was within Fang Yuan's expectations.

In the scarred battlefield, Fang Yuan was still standing proudly while the star armored giant was collapsed on the ground on the verge of death.

"There is no hope…" The other Combat Beast Warriors who had come to help out in the battle were kneeling on the ground, their faces were pale.

Starlight shined, the star armored giant once again turned back into the current generation Combat Beast King and there was also the star sea snail shell with cracks all over it.

Fang Yuan examined for a while and discovered the profundities within the star sea snail.

He laughed and suddenly spoke: "Beast Calamity heavenly spirit, are you still not coming out?"

"…"

All the Combat Beast Warriors were dumbstruck and shaken.

"I… I… what did I just hear?"

"That giant monster spoke, it can actually speak human language?!"

"Am I hearing things because I am too old and am about to die soon?" The Combat Beast King mumbled with a dull expression.

But at the next moment, an even more astonishing scene played out.

Beast Calamity heavenly spirit flew towards Fang Yuan along with several Immortal Gu.

The heavenly spirit was in the form of a young qilin, it spoke with a crisp and clear sound: "Foreign Gu Immortal, although you came here and obtained many inheritances, you have not obtained my full recognition. You recklessly killed innocent people and rampaged wildly, you are powerful but you can only obtain my main body's immortal killer moves. As for Immortal Gu and this grotto-heaven's inheritance rights, don't even think about it."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan let out laughter filled with deep meaning.

The young qilin was solemn: "I know what you are thinking, even I won't be able to win against you if you use force. But I can make these Immortal Gu self-detonate and destroy the grotto-heaven, you will gain nothing from this."

Fang Yuan was silent.

He felt somewhat troubled when he saw the young qilin's resolute look. A heavenly spirit was like a land spirit, it would not lie.

Fang Yuan was unable to inspect where Beast Calamity Immortal's Immortal Gu were.

And his blood light spirit suppression was not high enough level to pose sufficient threat to the grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit.

"So it was like this, the Combat Beast Warriors here were originally a part of the inheritance. I realize Beast Calamity Immortal's intention." After a long while of silence, Fang Yuan suddenly spoke.

"Even if you understand now, it is too late. Everyone only has one chance. But you are not leaving empty-handed, according to the main body's arrangements, immortal killer moves will be handed to you." The heavenly spirit had made its point clear, it wanted him to leave.

After Fang Yuan obtained these immortal killer moves, he did not remain or use force, leaving Beast Calamity grotto-heaven through the entrance which was opened by the heavenly spirit.

Eastern Sea.

The battle between five rank eight Gu Immortals was astonishing!

Large sea waves and tsunamis surged, dark clouds rumbled in the sky with lightning flashing and thunder roaring. Undercurrents rose in the sea, poison path, water path, soul path, and all kinds of terrifying methods had already exterminated all living beings in the surroundings.

"If you have any methods left, use them." Duke Long was still relaxed.

Feng Jin Huang was standing beside him, she was completely safe with not even a hair out of place. But right now, her face was filled with shock. After all, this was the first time she was seeing the fight between rank eight Gu Immortals at such a close distance, this had truly broadened her perspective.

Granny Rong, Yang Zi He, and others were solemn and distressed.

After truly exchanging moves, they tasted Duke Long's power. Although Duke Long was alone and had a burden, Feng Jin Huang, the four Eastern Sea rank eights were actually unable to gain an upper hand since the start. Despite the four immortals using all their strength, they were unable to change the situation. Right now, they already saw signs of defeat!

"He already has quasi-rank nine strength, besides an Immortal Venerable or a Demon Venerable, we have no way to deal with him!"

"Such powerful strength, as expected of Heavenly Court, as expected of Duke Long…"

The morale of Granny Rong, Yang Zi He, and the others had already sunk to rock-bottom.

"Damn it, we plotted to get Dragon Palace for so long but Heavenly Court is going to take it away."

"Sigh, let's go. We are not Duke Long's match and with us being on guard against each other, we cannot cooperate completely, there is no meaning in staying."

Seeing there was no choice, the four Eastern Sea rank eights left immediately.

Duke Long did not give chase.

His goal this time was Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace and his goal never changed.

"Dragon Palace was corroded by dream realms and has already fallen apart, I wonder how many Gu are still remaining? How many core Immortal Gu are damaged?"

Duke Long sighed inwardly as he moved to take Dragon Palace.

"Hmm?!"

At the next moment, an astonishing scene occurred.

Dragon Palace suddenly let out an extraordinary splendor and flew to the sky.

Duke Long remained standing on the spot, he was not able to obstruct Dragon Palace in time and could only look as it flew away. A trace of blood flowed out from the corners of his lips as his eyes revealed shock: "Dragon Palace is actually completely intact, not only this, one of its cores is a dream path Immortal Gu!"

"Hahaha, Duke Long, let's see how you fight against us this time!" The four Eastern Sea rank eights had returned.

Duke Long's expression sank.

The situation had turned troublesome.

He was besieged and Dragon Palace had flown away while spreading its aura everywhere, it would definitely create turmoil in Eastern Sea!

Chapter 1690: Myriad Beings Assimilation Transformation

"Immortal killer move — Myriad Beings Assimilation Transformation." Fang Yuan mumbled.

He was sitting on the auspicious cloud moving through empty air in immemorial white heaven, it was vast and boundless.

After leaving Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, he actively absorbed the benefits from this trip.

Beast Calamity Immortal's unique method was immortal killer move myriad beings assimilation transformation, after using this move, it could add a great number of transformation path dao marks and also transform the target's other dao marks into transformation path dao marks.

This move expended an enormous amount of immortal essence and also required abundant emotions. These emotions had to be positive and righteous. From this point, Fang Yuan finally realized the cause of the nature of those Combat Beast Warriors in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

Fang Yuan did not lack immortal essence. Over this period of time, although he had spent a lot in advancing the ranks of his Immortal Gu, his gains were similarly a lot. Especially in the later stage of Gu refinement, Fang Yuan's progress was huge and his expenditure had continued to fall. Currently, Fang Yuan's total amount of rank eight immortal essence was a lot and could support two battles of rank eight level intensity.

Fang Yuan had abundant emotions as well, he could easily create the positive emotions through wisdom path methods. His wisdom path attainment was very high after all.

What Fang Yuan lacked were Immortal Gu.

There were four Immortal Gu that formed this move, among them the core was a rank eight Immortal Gu — Adaptation!

It went without saying that this was a transformation path Immortal Gu, and was also the vital Gu of Beast Calamity Immortal. The other three Immortal Gu were all rank seven.

"Even if the heavenly spirit does not give me these Immortal Gu, I can snatch them. I have already improved great thief ghost hand and it is now much more reliable."

"Currently, I only need heaven form to constantly scout and find the place where these Immortal Gu are hidden, then I can use my theft path method to get them."

"However, it is somewhat troublesome to obtain the whole of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven."

As far as Fang Yuan was concerned, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven itself had an enormous value to him. But the heavenly spirit was able to destroy the grotto-heaven, so if he rashly used force, his losses would far outweigh his gains.

"From my deduction based on this myriad beings assimilation transformation, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals might also have a trump card."

Desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts could be used for myriad beings assimilation transformation, so could the star sea snail's shell. These Gu Immortals did not grasp myriad beings assimilation transformation, the reason was that Beast Calamity Immortal used this move on the entire Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

That meant, if the situation came to it, the entire Beast Calamity grotto-heaven could merge with the Gu Immortals through myriad beings assimilation transformation.

This could create a temporary rank eight battle strength!

Naturally, Fang Yuan could win against this kind of rank eight, but all of the resulting losses would be incurred on Fang Yuan. Even if he won, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, which had used myriad beings assimilation transformation, would suffer severe damage.

"This means, I need to deduce a way to restrict them from using myriad beings assimilation transformation with the entire Beast Calamity grotto-heaven."

"Also, I can use familiar face to invade once again."

Beast Calamity heavenly spirit said a person only had one chance to inherit it, but how strong could its detection ability be? Could it distinguish Fang Yuan's true identity? According to Fang Yuan's deduction, this possibility was very low.

However, just as Fang Yuan was deducing restraining methods, he obtained some news.

This news was important!

"Dragon Palace has appeared? Moreover, Duke Long personally made a move but was not able to acquire it? Oh, it was because he was obstructed by an alliance of four Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals?"

"Interesting! Currently, the rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace is flying in the skies of Eastern Sea without hiding its aura, it has already created a huge commotion, countless forces and Gu Immortal experts are paying close attention to it."

Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly.

He knew of Dragon Palace's existence.

There were relevant clues in Shadow Sect's true inheritance. But these clues were only superficial clues and were not significant enough. The most valuable content recorded was: Dragon Palace had a restriction that its inheritor must be a dragonman!

Although Fang Yuan wanted to own a rank eight Immortal Gu House, he never had a good opportunity or time. Although he had Bai Ning Bing, it would be difficult to search for Dragon Palace and it would take a great amount of time and energy.

According to the previous situation, although the rank eight Immortal Gu House was strong, were Fang Yuan to take the risk to search for it and end up unable to obtain it, he would quickly be pursued and hunted by Heavenly Court.

The benefits were huge but the risk was even greater, so Fang Yuan had not made a move.

"So Heavenly Court had been secretly searching for Dragon Palace and almost got it."

Knowing this, Fang Yuan could not help but praise those four Eastern Sea rank eights: Great job!

He did not think for long, Fang Yuan immediately left immemorial white heaven and moved towards Eastern Sea.

Beast Calamity grotto-heaven was here and would not be discovered easily, he could deal with it slowly. Dragon Palace's matter was urgent, he could not let Heavenly Court take it.

This was a rank eight Immortal Gu House and had an unknown dream path Immortal Gu!

Days later, Eastern Sea.

Boom!

Amidst an intense explosion, Gu Immortal Shi Miao spat out a large mouthful of blood while retreating rapidly.

Duke Long gave a loud roar, his body turned into light rays as he charged at Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace.

The distance between the two was rapidly shrinking, but at the crucial moment, Granny Rong moved and blocked Duke Long.

Her whole body was releasing purple gas, she was heavily injured and was pale as paper.

Duke Long's momentum was ferocious but his pupils shrunk when he saw the purple poisonous air around Granny Rong, he rapidly changed his direction and detoured.

Granny Rong was a poison path Gu Immortal, this purple poisonous air was her trump card and even Duke Long was not willing to touch it.

Granny Rong was not in a good state, over these days of fighting, her loss was the greatest. One of her core Immortal Gu was destroyed, her speed fell greatly and she was forced into an extremely passive state. She had relied on her determination and the help of the other three Gu Immortals to persist till now.

It was very wise of Duke Long to detour around Granny Rong.

Granny Rong could only watch Duke Long with a bitter expression but was unable to give chase.

Among the four rank eights, the other two were still several li away.

Boom!

Duke Long flew above Dragon Palace and slammed at this rank eight Immortal Gu House heavily.

Bam.

The Immortal Gu House fell into the sea, immediately raising an enormous wave.

Dragon Palace acted on its own, it did not fly to the sky again, instead moving deeper into the sea.

Duke Long was about to give chase when suddenly, his body paused and he struck towards the area left of him.

There looked to be nobody to his left, but his ferocious attack was suddenly stopped, it was blocked by a Gu Immortal.

The Gu Immortal revealed his figure and smiled at Duke Long: "As expected of Senior Duke Long, you could see through my disguise."

Duke Long frowned, sneering: "Song Qi Yuan, you are the first supreme elder of Song clan, a rank eight Gu Immortal, but you actually sneak attacked?"

The Gu Immortal was Song Qi Yuan.

"It seems Eastern Sea's righteous path is finally making a move. Who else is there, come out now." Duke Long glanced below at the sea, Dragon Palace gradually disappeared from his sight. He did not give chase, instead hovering in the air while letting out terrifying battle intent.

At the next moment, two more Gu Immortals showed themselves.

One was a middle aged man in blue robe, he was Qing Yue clan's first supreme elder Qing Yue An.

Another looked to be a young girl with bright eyes, exquisite rainbow clouds coiled around her body. She was Hua clan's first supreme elder Hua Cai Yun.

"Lord Duke Long…" Hua Cai Yun was just about to speak.

"Enough nonsense!" Duke Long shouted and took the initiative to attack.

Boom boom boom!

Several immortal killer moves were exchanged, the three righteous path rank eights were immediately suppressed and forced back.

"Duke Long is too powerful, he can easily suppress three Eastern Sea rank eights by himself!" Fang Yuan was inwardly shocked, he had transformed into a sea snake and was currently swimming in the sea.

Righteous path rank eights were often stronger than lone rank eight cultivators. This was because they had more exemplary immortal killer moves and ample cultivation resources.

The alliance of these three righteous path rank eights could absolutely win against the four person alliance of Granny Rong, Yang Zi He, Zhang Yin, and Shi Miao.

But they were still not Duke Long's match.

Duke Long was too ferocious, he was only using transformation path methods even until now, and had not used his most proficient qi path killer moves.

From this, one could see how powerful Purple Mountain True Monarch was, he had actually forced Duke Long to use his signature qi path killer moves.

"It was not that Purple Mountain True Monarch was weak, but Duke Long was simply too strong!" Fang Yuan looked at the distant Dragon Palace and slowly left the battlefield.

Since Song Qi Yuan, Qing Yue An and others appeared, it meant Eastern Sea's righteous path had already discussed and made decisions. Among the five regions, Eastern Sea was the richest in resources and thus had the highest number of rank eight Gu Immortals.

"Only three righteous path rank eights have appeared currently… there are definitely more coming." Fang Yuan decided to bide his time.

Sure enough, like he expected, two more righteous path rank eights showed up and obstructed Dragon Palace.

Zhang Yin, Granny Rong and others quickly came and fought these two righteous path rank eights.

A huge battle erupted under the sea.

Fang Yuan quickly hid in the mud at the bottom of the sea, waiting for a good opportunity to strike.

Chapter 1691: Exposed

Swoosh—!

Following a sharp sonic boom, Dragon Palace turned into a golden light as it moved towards the sky with an extremely fast speed.

"Where are you going!"

"Die."

"Want to obstruct me? Not a chance!"

Several Gu Immortals battled while giving chase, each displaying their great might. Intense battles followed the trail of Dragon Palace all along the way.

Wherever it went, mounds crumbled and the sea split, the sky changed colors and countless beings met with calamity, rank six and rank seven Gu Immortals all escaped in fright.

Only rank eight Gu Immortals had the qualifications to take part in this battle.

The battles of Duke Long, Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, Song Qi Yuan, and other rank eights did not allow rank seven Gu Immortals to interfere. Unless they were the likes of Feng Jiu Ge and Fang Yuan. But now, both Fang Yuan and Feng Jiu Ge had advanced to rank eight.

"Most of the Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals are already participating in the battle, but there are a few who have yet to show themselves." Fang Yuan was patiently observing from far behind, waiting for a perfect opportunity.

From the time he rushed over to Eastern Sea, over ten days had already gone by. Over these days, the battle between rank eight Gu Immortals was a splendid show with none willing to make concessions. Occasionally, new rank eights would join in while some would temporarily retreat.

They allied sometimes and acted against each other sometimes. As long as anyone neared Dragon Palace, they would be met with the joint attack of everyone else. Fang Yuan could not find any opportunity to make a move.

But he was extremely patient and was not in the least bit worried.

"Being able to observe the skills of these rank eight Gu Immortals from here is also an enormous gain. This information is very valuable."

"Duke Long is truly terrifying! In this battle, he is no doubt the strongest, but because of that unknown dream path Immortal Gu in Dragon Palace, the joint attack of other rank eights, as well as being concerned about the safety of Feng Jin Huang, he has not been able to obtain Dragon Palace."

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with sinister light.

Not just the rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace, Feng Jin Huang who was beside Duke Long was also his target.

This girl possessed a dream path Immortal Gu and was also Duke Long's disciple, looking at how Duke Long protected her, her importance could be seen clearly.

But although Fang Yuan had such a scheme, he similarly did not find an opportunity to make a move against Feng Jin Huang!

"A chance, a chance… it will definitely appear."

"Eastern Sea's righteous path has clearly already discussed with each other. Someone retreats while another comes in, taking turns to maintain their battle strength and also retain their control of the situation. This is to be on guard against Central Continent and Heavenly Court's reinforcements."

"Duke Long has been fighting alone, but he is still the strongest. If there are reinforcements from Heavenly Court, this stalemate will definitely be broken."

"Even if Heavenly Court does not send reinforcements, the four person team of Granny Rong, Zhang Yin and others won't be able to last long."

"Among the three sides, the righteous path is the most stable, the other two sides have the possibility of overturning this balance. But once the balance is broken, there will definitely be a chaotic battle. And this chaos will give me the chance to make a move!"

Fang Yuan was extremely clear about the situation.

But right at this time, there was a sudden explosion in front; Song Qi Yuan was struck and became lightly injured, coughing out a mouthful of blood.

Zhang Yin turned his head around and chuckled: "I have already struck you with fatal dark lightning, chase me if you are not afraid of dying."

Song Qi Yuan's defenses were thorough and comprehensive but after getting struck by this move, he got injured. His defensive methods were immediately torn, fatal dark lightning could not be underestimated.

Thereupon, the entire group of pursuers immediately split into two, one group ahead and one group behind.

"Fatal dark lightning is Zhang Yin's trump card, it has a huge cost to activate, it is formless, colorless and cannot be sensed. It can be arranged in the sea or air, once touched, it will explode. What should we do?" The remaining three rank eight Gu Immortals were also of the righteous path.

"We need to give chase, it will be dangerous for Hua Cai Yun alone."

"We don't have time to make a detour, we can only control beast groups to charge through this lightning formation!"

The three righteous path members quickly thought of a way and released their respective ancient desolate beasts.

Song Qi Yuan waved his hand, these ancient desolate beasts' auras immediately soared to the level of immemorial desolate beasts.

Boom boom boom!

The false immemorial desolate beasts could trigger the fatal dark lightning traps.

These ancient desolate beasts constantly died to pave a path for the three righteous path rank eights.

The three rank eights quickly moved ahead through the path.

"This is a little troublesome, let's take a chance." Fang Yuan was uneasy and wanted to cross the lightning formation as well.

Boom!

He was immediately struck by the fatal dark lightning, but did not dare use reverse flow protection seal and could only endure the damage forcibly.

"This dark lightning is truly troublesome, it is better to make a detour." Fang Yuan coughed out a mouthful of blood, changing his original intention.

Boom!

He was struck again.

"Ridiculous, this fatal dark lightning actually spread out this far, its range is too wide." Fang Yuan clenched his teeth and swallowed his blood.

Boom boom boom!

Fang Yuan continued to trigger fatal dark lightning traps, his luck path methods seemed to have no use.

After about eight minutes, Fang Yuan forcibly endured the pain as he caught up to the rank eight Gu Immortals' battle.

"Come and face my killer move, red pestilence insignia!" Granny Rong shouted and used all her strength to shoot out a red insignia.

Hua Cai Yun snorted as she pushed forward her hands, sending out a lump of cloud.

This cloud was pitch black and was like an inverted pot, its shape was peculiar. It quickly moved and absorbed the red insignia.

Granny Rong's expression immediately changed, she had lost control of the red pestilence insignia.

The cloud continued to move as it tossed the red pestilence insignia away.

Hua Cai Yun said proudly: "Your red pestilence insignia is useless against my pot tossing cloud! It will only be tossed away by me, I will never get hit."

"The f*ck!" Fang Yuan cursed in his mind. By some weird coincidence, the red pestilence insignia had been tossed towards him.

Dodge!

Fang Yuan was disguised as a sea snake and could not casually increase his speed, so he barely managed to dodge.

The red pestilence insignia flew far away and exploded, the surrounding sea area met with calamity, living beings met their end with countless sea organisms turning into mush from the intense poison.

Fang Yuan was also struck by the move, he endured the rank eight killer move and turned into a sea snake corpse, continuing his disguise.

It was not easy for Fang Yuan to stalk from behind, he was constantly hit by the splattering effects of the moves in this battle. Fortunately, he remained far behind and with the rank eight Gu Immortals all paying attention to Dragon Palace and each other, they had not discovered him.

However, this did not last long, Fang Yuan's identity was finally exposed several days later.

It was a rank eight lone cultivator who found him, he was Yang Jun and had been chasing after Dragon Palace in his Immortal Gu House Fragrant Treasure Horse Chariot when he discovered Fang Yuan by chance.

Fang Yuan struck him and immediately escaped.

This movement finally attracted the attention of other rank eights, but Fang Yuan had left immediately. Even if Duke Long wanted to do anything, it was too late.

Central Continent, Infallible blessed land.

The radiance of the formation disappeared.

After inspecting for a while, Fairy Zi Wei nodded in satisfaction and thought: "With this formation here, who can destroy Infallible blessed land? Even if Fang Yuan came here, he would also be trapped."

Fairy Zi Wei was confident in this formation.

A bright light suddenly descended from the sky and arrived in front of her, revealing its true form.

"Greetings to Lady Zi Wei." It was Feng Jiu Ge. He already had rank eight cultivation now and his tone carried a trace of being on equal status with Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "Feng Jiu Ge, I called you for one matter. Dragon Palace has appeared, Lord Duke Long is chasing after it but has encountered obstruction from Eastern Sea's rank eights. Go to Eastern Sea, reinforce Lord Duke Long, protect your daughter Feng Jin Huang, and help my Heavenly Court take Dragon Palace."

Feng Jiu Ge was silent for a moment but rejected in the end: "Huang Er is protected by Lord Duke Long, she won't be in any danger. But… when I advanced to rank eight, I gained an inspiration and wanted to create a new song. I want to enter the River of Time now to observe the different types of worldly affairs throughout the eras, I want to experience the journey of myriad beings' lives."

Fairy Zi Wei was dazed for a moment: "Alright then, guard the River of Time in place of Li Huang."

Chapter 1692: Working With Longevity Heaven

Eastern Sea, late at night.

Stars filled the sky, the calm sea suddenly turned turbulent with fierce waves.

Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace charged out of the sea, flying into the sky rapidly.

There was a rank eight Gu Immortal waiting in the sky, it was Qing Yue clan's first supreme elder, Qing Yue An.

"Puff!" He muttered lightly as he waved his arms rapidly.

Immediately the phantom image of a mountain descended from the sky, the mountain ranges extended far and beyond, encircling the entire Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Mountain Ranges!

Dragon Palace's movement was obstructed, it crashed into the phantom mountain like it had truly slammed into a solid one.

"Hmph!"

There was a cold snort as a rank eight Gu Immortal charged out of Dragon Palace, it was rank eight lone immortal Shi Miao.

Shi Miao spat out a mouthful of acid water, this acid water did not look impressive but it grew with the wind, turning into a huge wave after several tens of feet.

The wave crashed into the phantom mountain and had an incredible effect, the mountain started melting like snow exposed to the sun.

The acid wave opened a path for Dragon Palace as it nearly got out of the encirclement, but Song Qi Yuan arrived right at this moment.

His aura burst out and grand light pillars shined in all directions, dissolving the waves and also causing Dragon Palace to shake, when it landed on Shi Miao, it felt like he was hit by a lightning bolt.

After this, Song Qi Yuan did not stop, he raised his head and pointed with his finger.

A sharp light shot out like lightning, vanishing instantly.

Far away, Fang Yuan who was using star eyes Immortal Gu to observe the battlefield felt his vision going dark, he could not see anything anymore.

Fang Yuan's expression turned dark, he knew that the star that he had refined using star eyes Immortal Gu was destroyed by Song Qi Yuan!

"Rank seven star eyes Immortal Gu might be unique, but against a rank eight Gu Immortal, it is too weak, not only can it be discovered, it can also be stopped.

Song Qi Yuan's immortal killer move is even more profound, it moved along the starlight and found the star of origin to destroy it."

"Even though the star was destroyed, star eyes Immortal Gu suffered no injuries, it can be used again after further preparation."

Even though these Eastern Sea Gu Immortals could not defeat Duke Long, they were still rank eight with brilliant methods, they could not be underestimated.

Earlier, Zhang Yin's fatal dark lightning, Hua Cai Yun's pot tossing cloud, Yang Jun discovering Fang Yuan who was in familiar face disguise, and Song Qi Yuan's attack that destroyed Star Eyes' star, they proved this point.

But even so, Fang Yuan did not want to give up.

"Dragon Palace is very important, it is far more important than I had expected!"

"It is a rank eight Immortal Gu House that contains dream path Immortal Gu. These days, in this battle, it displayed very powerful offensive and defensive methods, if I can get it, I will obtain peak rank eight battle strength!"

Fang Yuan's main body chased while heaven form killer move stayed in immemorial white heaven, dealing with Beast Calamity Grotto-heaven and finding the hiding spot of adaptation Immortal Gu.

Heaven form killer move was rank nine and extremely mobile, even within immemorial white heaven, there were few existences which could threaten it.

Because of the earth vein's turbulence, the Gu Immortals of the five regions were in chaos.

Especially, Eastern Sea, the emergence of Dragon Palace caused a battle among rank eights, it was truly spectacular.

On this day, Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven also started to tremor intensely.

Bzzz bzzz bzzz….

Orange-yellow light flickered endlessly, enveloping the sky of Longevity Heaven.

Next, an aura started from an extremely weak state and grew rapidly, soon filling the world and causing fear in everyone.

Such a change had already attracted the attention of Five Elements Grandmaster, Bull Demon, and Flower Lady.

Five Elements Grandmaster was a lone cultivator of Northern Plains, but after getting trapped by Longevity Heaven, he felt despair after struggling and decided to join Longevity Heaven, he was not stationed in Longevity Heaven permanently.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady were a duo that took the role of North Desolation Immortal together.

Bull Demon was a muscular brute with a thick beard and a thunderous voice, he was extremely tall and strong, having a powerful aura. Flower Lady was a little girl with a flower on her head, she sat on the muscular man's shoulder, giggling as her crystal-like eyes flickered with innocence.

"What happened?" Five Elements Grandmaster was very uncertain.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady looked at each other, the latter giggled: "West Desolation Immortal Bing Sai Chuan has awakened!"

Longevity Heaven was a bit different from Heavenly Court, it had Four Desolation Immortals and Eight Extremities, a total of twelve positions. Among which, the Four Desolation Immortals were only meant for rank eight Gu Immortals, while the Eight Extremities needed at least rank seven cultivation level, and they had to be elites among rank sevens.

"Bing Sai Chuan?" Five Elements Grandmaster's brows rose, he felt that the name was familiar but he could not get more information from just that name.

At this moment, there was a loud roar, ripples of light flickered in the sky, rainbows extended like rivers as they pierced through the horizons.

A figure walked down from the river, he had a tall body and delicate face, nevertheless, his eyes were extremely sharp and icy, emitting a cold gaze. From his right ear to the left corner of his lips, there was an ugly scar, it was flickering with white light, while emitting the coldness of a thousand year profound ice.

Seeing this face, Five Elements Grandmaster's eyes burst out with bright light as he became deeply shocked: "I remember now, this is the Bing Sai Chuan who was born in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's generation, he was a rank eight legend, a time path great expert, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had tried three times before subduing him. He did not die, he is actually the West Desolation Immortal of Longevity Heaven?!"

West Desolation Immortal was born in the same generation as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, even though he lost, it was not a disgrace. After all, be they Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable, they were invincible in the world with no equal.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to make three attempts to subdue this West Desolation Immortal, it showed that he had great strength!

"Greetings, Senior West Desolation." Bull Demon and Flower Lady quickly went to greet him while Five Elements Grandmaster followed after with an expression of reverence.

West Desolation Immortal Bing Sai Chuan's seniority was simply too high.

Bing Sai Chuan went up to the three, he nodded after looking around: "I am awake but I do not have much lifespan, time is limited. Give me the information of the current world, I need to know about it."

Longevity Heaven had very comprehensive information.

They had detailed information of the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the reappearance of Dragon Palace in Eastern Sea, and the Refinement Path Convention of Central Continent's Heavenly Court.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building truly collapsed…" Bing Sai Chuan sighed deeply.

"It was Fang Yuan, that demon was reborn using Spring Autumn Cicada, he is rank eight already." Five Elements Grandmaster gritted his teeth.

Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly as he said: "Good job, Fang Yuan, he is truly a demon, he did a great job in destroying Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

Five Elements Grandmaster was stunned: "What?"

Bull Demon looked at Flower Lady: "…"

Flower Lady looked at Bull Demon: "…"

The three immortals were completely shocked.

Next, Bing Sai Chuan added: "Fate Gu is about to be repaired, it seems that this Refinement Path Convention is the final one. There is no time, we have to contact Fang Yuan now and make an alliance!"

The gazes of Five Elements Grandmaster, Bull Demon, and Flower Lady changed abruptly.

Was this Bing Sai Chuan really the West Desolation Immortal? Could he possibly be a fake one?

"Longevity Heaven wants to cooperate with me?" Fang Yuan received this message and became quite shocked.

It was easy to contact him, Lang Ya land spirit could do it.

Bing Sai Chuan used Lang Ya land spirit to contact Fang Yuan, he spoke openly: "I am West Desolation Immortal, the current leader of Longevity Heaven. Fang Yuan, you are an otherworldly demon but you have yet to obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance? If Heavenly Court repairs fate Immortal Gu, it will not benefit you at all. Similarly, Longevity Heaven does not want to see Heavenly Court succeed. If they repair fate Gu, it would be too helpful to Heavenly Court, it would also go against the luck path of my Ancestor Giant Sun. Let us forget our past conflicts and resist the strong enemy together!"

Fang Yuan was quiet for a while before asking: "You are?"

Bing Sai Chuan!

Soon, Fang Yuan learned who the other party was.

He should be the real deal.

Fang Yuan sighed at Longevity Heaven's foundation, they even concealed a rank eight legend like Bing Sai Chuan, he had only appeared now.

And in Longevity Heaven, among the Four Desolation Immortals, East Desolation Immortal had the highest status, the great Bing Sai Chuan was only second place?

Who in the world was the East Desolation Immortal?

Longevity Heaven's change of attitude made Fang Yuan deeply surprised. But to think of it, against the terrifying Heavenly Court, it was possible for Fang Yuan to work with them.

After all, he was a rank eight Gu Immortal now, the leader of Shadow Sect who possessed deep dream path research results, his name shook the world!

A while ago, Heavenly Court even infiltrated Northern Plains and attacked Lang Ya blessed land, the two sides had immense conflicts.

The saying goes, the enemy of an enemy is my friend!

If they could cooperate, Fang Yuan naturally wanted to work with Longevity Heaven.

After all, Heavenly Court was the true enemy.

But how could they trust each other?

To gain Fang Yuan's trust, Longevity Heaven opened its treasury and traded immortal materials with Fang Yuan, they could even exchange Immortal Gu.

From this step, they seemed to be very sincere.

"Since we are cooperating, Lord Bing Sai Chuan, why don't we work together to fight for Dragon Palace?" Fang Yuan had a thought as he initiated.

"Good idea!" Bing Sai Chuan was in full agreement, any person with a brain could tell that Dragon Palace had immense value.

Chapter 1693: Zi Wei Borrows Gu

Since rebirth, Fang Yuan's strength had been growing rapidly, it was rising at a shocking speed.

Especially in recent times, he advanced to rank eight and possessed countless Immortal Gu, it was truly a rare situation.

However, he was still not strong enough to contend for Dragon Palace.

Among the rank eight Gu Immortals fighting after Dragon Palace, there was Duke Long with pseudo-Immortal Venerable battle strength and multiple Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals, it could be said that Eastern Sea's strongest immortals were here.

Fang Yuan had too little time since his rise, against the peak experts of a region, against Duke Long, trying to snatch an Immortal Gu House that had the power to retaliate was just too difficult for him.

But Fang Yuan knew that he could not watch on the sidelines.

If Heavenly Court obtains Dragon Palace, they would grow even stronger. Especially that mysterious dream path Immortal Gu, it was not simple! It might have been created naturally by this world itself, it was the seed that the heavens had planted into Eastern Sea to start the era of dream path.

At this time, drawing in Longevity Heaven's strength would make the situation even more chaotic.

The more chaotic it was, the more Fang Yuan would be able to take advantage of the situation.

He was rank eight now, but against Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals, he did not dare to be careless. The foundation of rank eight Gu Immortals was immense, they would easily hit him with their killer moves if he was not careful.

As for Duke Long, Fang Yuan knew clearly that he was not his match. After all, Fang Yuan had personally witnessed how Duke Long had fought Purple Mountain True Monarch.

"Duke Long is protecting Feng Jin Huang, he is not going all-out. I have not seen him use any qi path methods yet. Even so, with just his transformation path methods, he is already the strongest person here, he is resisting almost everyone alone."

"Bai Ning Bing and the rest are still cultivating on the Red Lotus island, even if they have the help of future self, they would only have peak rank seven battle strength."

"It is a pity my incomplete Immortal Gu House was destroyed, if I had it, after this period of development, it would have rank eight battle strength, it would be very useful to me."

"If I can steal adaptation Immortal Gu from Beast Calamity Grotto-heaven, I would be able to unleash myriad beings assimilation transformation, I will temporarily gain great battle strength. It is a pity that we do not have time, heaven form is still investigating."

Fang Yuan felt some regret.

But reality was like this, not everything could go smoothly and appropriately.

Dragon Palace would not tire, Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals had not fully shown up, while Duke Long was waiting for Heavenly Court reinforcements, there was still some time before they truly fought for the Immortal Gu House's ownership.

Fang Yuan was also concerned about Longevity Heaven's attitude change. But even if they had ill intentions, luring them into the battle was much more useful for Fang Yuan than the potential threat.

With this move, he could try to obtain Dragon Palace, damage Heavenly Court, and probe Longevity Heaven, it could achieve many goals.

But a few days later, Bing Sai Chuan did not arrive, instead, he obtained some crucial information — Heavenly Court had found a stone lotus island in the River of Time, they had full control of it now!

Bing Sai Chuan suggested: "You have Spring Autumn Cicada, you are the rightful inheritor of Red Lotus' true inheritance. If Heavenly Court takes away your fortuitous encounter, you will suffer while they grow stronger. Red Lotus Demon Venerable was able to damage fate Gu, very likely, his true inheritance also contains the way for us to destroy fate Gu for good!"

Bing Sai Chuan's words had no issue, he did not know that Fang Yuan had already obtained one of the Red Lotus true inheritances.

Fang Yuan did not have any method to destroy fate Gu, but what if the other Red Lotus true inheritance had it?

It was possible.

Of course, there was a possibility that Bing Sai Chuan gave false information to trap Fang Yuan.

Right now, Fang Yuan had two choices, he could stay and observe Dragon Palace, or go to the River of Time and contest for Red Lotus' true inheritance with Heavenly Court.

The former was filled with chaos and danger, so was the latter, the risks were great.

Fang Yuan sensed acutely that this choice was crucial. He started to think, what was the best course of action in this situation?

Southern Border.

Virtue Paradise.

Two rank eight Gu Immortals walked side by side and ascended the mountain, their auras were completely concealed, resembling mortals.

The one on the left wore a grey hemp garment, it was very simple and plain, but his muscular body could not be concealed. He wore a conical hat that was large and wide, it covered his face under the shadow, concealing his appearance.

It was the famous current generation Paradise Earth inheritor in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world — Lu Wei Yin.

The one on the right was a woman, she had a graceful figure with hair that extended to her waist, and was adorned in a beautiful purple robe that was mysterious and elegant. Her eyes were like deep pools, with a sense of sorrow shrouding her face.

It was Heavenly Court's leader, the person who had Star Constellation Chessboard, the number one wisdom path great expert in the current world — Fairy Zi Wei!

Fairy Zi Wei had actually quietly appeared in Southern Border and met with Lu Wei Yin, what was the reason behind it?

Along the way, Lu Wei Yin and Fairy Zi Wei spoke, even though there were few words, the atmosphere was amicable.

As they walked, a small red pavilion emerged from the dense greenery, Lu Wei Yin pointed at it as he said: "Lady Zi Wei, it has been a long journey, let's go rest a bit in that pavilion."

"Good idea." Fairy Zi Wei smiled as she walked.

The two walked into the red pavilion, there were stone benches inside, instead of sitting down, Fairy Zi Wei walked towards the edge and looked at the wide view of mountains and rivers.

This pavilion was built at the edge of a cliff, it had an extremely good view.

Fairy Zi Wei looked outside, Virtue Paradise was filled with tall mountains and clean rivers, there were treehouses and villages around the mountains, lots of commotion could be heard from chickens and dogs, there were columns of smoke rising from houses, it was a serene and tranquil atmosphere.

In the sky, there were many floating mountains. These mountains were made from float soil and could stay in the sky, there were many specialties in each mountain, their environments varied. Some had long green vines that extended like hair. Some had drizzles and beautiful rainbows. Some had waterfalls with huge crashing torrents that gathered in huge pools.

Cranes flew, apes shrieked, there was lots of life and immortal materials everywhere, desolate beasts and plants were abundant in numbers.

The thing that Fairy Zi Wei noticed was that the mushroommen and humans lived harmoniously in the villages, kids played together, husbands and wives cared for each other, children were also filial towards their parents.

"It is truly a paradise! Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable wanted to create such a world, but humanity is the ruler of the world, how could variant humans possibly be equal with us? But even so, I admire Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. Because he had contributed his whole life towards this dream, he had never sought benefits for himself." Fairy Zi Wei said slowly.

Heavenly Court belonged to humans, its ideology was to rule over the variant humans, but Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable wanted equality for all, in his opinion, be it variant humans or pure humans, all life in this world should be equal.

Because of their ideological differences, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable did not enter Heavenly Court, he created his paradises in the five regions and tried to establish the utopia of his ideals.

Lu Wei Yin nodded: "Even though our ideologies are different, our attitude towards the demonic path that harms the world is the same. Lady Zi Wei is here to borrow Gu, if you are borrowing other Gu, forget it. But this benevolence Gu can benefit the world, why would I stop you? However, if outsiders want to borrow Gu, according to the Immortal Venerable's rules, you need to walk and ascend to the top of the mountain to gain the qualification to borrow Gu. This journey is difficult, the higher your cultivation level, the worse it is. Please do understand, Fairy Zi Wei."

"This mountain is truly not easy to ascend, but I understand Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's intention. Getting up this mountain will benefit me quite a bit too." Fairy Zi Wei said softly as she smiled, light flickered in her eyes: "Alright, let's continue."

River of Time.

Heavenly Court's four Immortal Gu Houses stood in different positions as they surrounded an immortal formation.

The atmosphere was heated among the Gu Immortals.

"Lord Feng Jiu Ge, we have already encircled this stone lotus island, we can explore it already." Shang Xunzi said.

Feng Jiu Ge nodded, he originally wanted to use the River of Time to solidify and strengthen his inspiration regarding the song of destiny. To think that after entering the River of Time for this short period, the stone lotus island showed up and became besieged by Heavenly Court.

"The stone lotus islands were created by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, I should go ahead and see the methods of this world-shocking Demon Venerable." Feng Jiu Ge was about to move and enter the immortal formation.

Boom!

With a loud sound, the Immortal Gu House that he was in shook intensely.

"Enemy!"

"Who is so daring as to attack us Heavenly Court?!"

The immortals were furious and shocked.

Who else but Fang Yuan could it be?

Heavenly Court's group was slightly dazed, someone started to shout: "Demon, you managed to escape last time, but you actually dared to return! Then accept your death."

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, he had thought about it for a moment before deciding to come to the River of Time, and trying to get Red Lotus' true inheritance.

After all, Dragon Palace's scene was chaotic, all the forces had not gone all-out yet, there was too much uncertainty.

But at the stone lotus island, if he did not come, Heavenly Court would definitely get it. Fang Yuan had Spring Autumn Cicada, his advantage was huge when it came to the stone lotus islands.

"Fang Yuan, we meet again." Feng Jiu Ge's voice reverberated within the Immortal Gu House, there were deep emotions in his voice.

Fang Yuan's expression focused, it seemed like in this battle, he was going to fight Feng Jiu Ge once again!

Chapter 1694: Contesting For Red Lotus’ True Inheritance

"Fang Yuan, we meet again." Feng Jiu Ge's voice reverberated from within the Immortal Gu House, there were deep emotions in his tone.

"It has been a long time indeed." Fang Yuan sighed.

Years had passed, Fang Yuan met with Feng Jiu Ge again, it was like a meeting of old friends, their words had no animosity in them.

But they were not friends after all, after that brief talk, they went silent.

At this moment, there was only the sound of waves in the River of Time, surging forward with continuous motion.

Feng Jiu Ge still remembered the first time he met Fang Yuan, back then, he was still not an immortal, he had obtained Hu Immortal blessed land with the status of a mortal. But now, he was renowned in the world, he had rank eight cultivation level and his speed of growth was rare even in history, it was truly shocking to the world.

Feng Jiu Ge was also rank eight with brilliant battle results, his strength was no longer the same as before, he had rank eight fate armor Immortal Gu, and because of his Dao Guardian status, he was heavily supported by Heavenly Court.

Fang Yuan had once saved Feng Jiu Ge's life, he had returned the favor as well. Because of their different identities, Feng Jiu Ge had failed in many attempts to pursue Fang Yuan. They had fought many times and gained a deep understanding of each other. Both were wary of each other, but they appreciated the other person's capabilities and talent immensely.

"Fang Yuan, you lost to us once, you managed to escape last time in the River of Time, to think that you would dare to come back and court death!" A voice broke the temporary silence.

The person who spoke had starry blue armor, he had a rough appearance and his body was strong, he emitted a powerful rank eight aura and was standing on Shark Flow Lever.

Fang Yuan took a look and discerned that this was a person who had participated in the battle last time.

Even though last time, he did not know who this was, he had obtained information already. This person had woken up from Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard, he was an experienced rank eight star path expert, Xing Ye Wang.

Fang Yuan inspected Heavenly Court's group again.

The three remaining Xunzi occupied Present and Past Pavilion, they looked at Fang Yuan with deep hatred, their eyes were spewing fire. Last time, Fang Yuan used time cutting edge and killed Xun Guo Zi, causing their revival methods to fail, only three were left now.

Rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye had the same status as Xing Ye Wang, he controlled Eternal Yacht with a grim expression.

Xing Ye Wang stood on Shark Flow Lever, looking at Fang Yuan with deep battle intent.

Meanwhile, Feng Jiu Ge stayed in Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform, he had now shown up yet.

"Four time path Immortal Gu Houses, three rank eight Gu Immortals, as well as many rank seven Gu Immortals including three of the Xunzi, and this super immortal formation…" Fang Yuan evaluated their strength.

On the whole, it was not bad.

Because Heavenly Court had not sent too many people here. But thinking about it, Central Continent's earth veins were moving, other than maintaining control, Heavenly Court placed all its attention on repairing rank nine fate Gu, a lot of manpower and resources were expended for it.

From Heavenly Court's perspective, Fang Yuan was not their main enemy, in their overall plan, Fang Yuan was not a part of it.

Thus, Fairy Zi Wei had once offered to recruit Fang Yuan back in Lang Ya blessed land.

Heavenly Court's goal was the entire world, the great era of dream path, and to become the ruler of the world.

This was the grandness of Heavenly Court!

Thus, Heavenly Court's focus had always been to fully restore fate Gu!

Moreover, last time Fang Yuan escaped barely with his life. Afterwards, Fairy Zi Wei used Heavenly Court's foundation to buy all sorts of time path materials and disrupted Fang Yuan's growth.

He had hidden his tracks and even when the earth veins moved and countless Immortal Gu and immortal materials appeared, he did not show up.

Due to all these reasons, Heavenly Court had not increased their numbers in the River of Time.

"Of course, they might have some groups lying in ambush?" Fang Yuan smiled coldly, regardless of what they did, as long as they fought, Heavenly Court would summon them anyway.

Roar!

With a huge sound, Fang Yuan used familiar face to turn into the immemorial year monkey again.

The monkey body was huge like a mountain, it pounced towards Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform, that was where Feng Jiu Ge was.

"Such a courageous demon, let me fight you!" Xing Ye Wang moved Shark Flow Lever as he intercepted with great speed.

Fang Yuan moved rapidly above the water, he pointed his finger as immortal killer move spring scissors flew out.

The scissors were green in color and moved agilely, even though it was huge like an elephant, it shrunk when it got in front of Shark Flow Lever.

Xing Ye Wang was a little shocked, he knew about spring scissors, but to think there was such a transformation?

The mini spring scissors flew down and became large again when it got to the shark lever of Shark Flow Lever.

Crack.

With a snip, the scissors cut and a huge shark head fell off.

Crack.

With another snip, another shark lost its head.

Xing Ye Wang was very shocked, he quickly moved Shark Flow Lever aside, he could not dare continue trying to obstruct Fang Yuan, he needed to know how to handle spring scissors.

After stopping Xing Ye Wang, Fang Yuan moved quick as the wind, arriving in front of Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform.

Within the Immortal Gu House, Feng Jiu Ge had a plain expression as he controlled it calmly.

Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform burst out with a dazzling light, stopping Fang Yuan's advancement as if he had crashed into a metal wall.

Fang Yuan who was in the immemorial year monkey form laughed as he punched with his huge fists.

The huge fists landed on Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and caused it to shake, rubbles flew everywhere as it got pushed back.

"Fang Yuan got stronger again!"

"That's right, he has at least modified spring scissors and winter coat. The former can change sizes and become hard to guard against, while the latter has fused with his immemorial year monkey transformation, his monkey fur is like frost and his skin is like ice, his defenses are extremely thick."

The three Xunzi guarded Present and Past Pavilion, they talked to each other with lingering shock.

Ever since Fang Yuan escaped pitifully last time while exposing all his trump cards, Heavenly Court had deduced all sorts of killer moves that he had. But to think that in this battle, all of their deductions were outdated, Fang Yuan's modifications were far beyond Heavenly Court's expectations, they were greatly caught off-guard.

Not just that, Fang Yuan had also made many deductions on the four Immortal Gu Houses. Looking at how he dealt with Shark Flow Lever and Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform, it was evident.

Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was not low, he also had the help of wisdom Gu which Heavenly Court did not manage to deduce.

Fang Yuan, who had the light of wisdom and sufficient intel, made great gains when he deduced matters regarding the four time path Immortal Gu Houses!

In the previous battle, Fang Yuan exposed his trump cards, but at the same time, Heavenly Court also expended their trump cards, Fang Yuan could learn a lot of details about them.

It was not easy for Gu Immortals to create immortal killer moves, modifications were even harder. Then what about Immortal Gu Houses?

Immortal Gu Houses were the collective body of multiple immortal killer moves.

Thus, modifying Immortal Gu Houses was even tougher.

Fang Yuan could modify immortal killer moves because he had wisdom Gu. Heavenly Court wanted to modify Immortal Gu Houses but they did not have wisdom Gu, the difficulty was even higher, thus, these four Immortal Gu Houses did not have many changes, they were also similar to before.

Fang Yuan lost last time but he gained lots of information, he could deal with these Immortal Gu Houses now. This was also why he gave up on Dragon Palace for now and chose to target the River of Time.

"The northern corner is destroyed, the Gu worms cannot be retrieved."

"Three layers of autumn light shields have been broken, only one is left!"

"Immortal Gu Autumn Light has cracks on it…"

The Gu Immortals inside Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform reported, they had nervous expressions.

Feng Jiu Ge was the person in charge, he still had a calm expression.

He did not attempt to fight personally, because he knew that only relying on his sound path cultivation, he could not make useful efforts in this River of Time. Only the time path Immortal Gu House could resist Fang Yuan.

Feng Jiu Ge thought to himself: "Fang Yuan can suppress two Immortal Gu Houses, but Heavenly Court still has another two. This battle has just begun!"

Fang Yuan's barrage of attacks made him pant loudly, even though Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform was shattered on the outside, its foundation was unaffected, it only lost a large number of mortal Gu. Those rank seven Gu Immortals inside the Immortal Gu House were trying to repair it rapidly.

After the initial burst, his attacks got softer, the Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform got past the initial stage as Fang Yuan's ferocious attacks started to weaken. Xing Ye Wang had already repaired Shark Flow Lever after facing spring scissors killer move, it charged over again.

At the same time, Present and Past Pavilion and Eternal Yacht came from the left and right, forming a complete web.

"Fang Yuan, I want to see how you will deal with four Immortal Gu Houses together!" Xing Ye Wang shouted loudly.

Fang Yuan looked at his encirclement as his eyes shined with bright light, he smiled and shouted loudly: "Bing Sai Chuan, are you still not going to act?"

Before he finished his words, Bing Sai Chuan appeared, standing behind Present and Past Pavilion.

"Who?!" The three Xunzi were very shocked, because Present and Past Pavilion was most specialized in investigation, they were able to detect Fang Yuan but not Bing Sai Chuan.

Bing Sai Chuan roared as he pushed with both palms, immediately, cold winds blew and frost energy surged, covering the whole of Present and Past Pavilion.

At the next moment, the entire Present and Past Pavilion became sealed in a transparent profound ice, the three Xunzi were unmoving inside, a frightened expression frozen on their faces.

On Eternal Yacht, rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye who had a calm expression showed a change of attitude: "This immortal killer move is… immediate time freeze! You are the time path great expert of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's era, Bing Sai Chuan!"

Bing Sai Chuan cultivated time path and was most skilled at freezing time, his time path killer moves were able to imitate the effects of ice path. He was a rank eight legend, his battle strength was at its peak, on the same level as Li Huang.

But right now, Li Huang was deployed elsewhere, in exchange for Feng Jiu Ge who had just reached rank eight. Regardless, this was the River of Time, even if Li Huang was here, without using the time path Immortal Gu House to fight against Bing Sai Chuan, he would not be his match.

Bing Sai Chuan waited for a long time before striking with great impact! He targeted the weakest enemy, directly sealing a time path Immortal Gu House and preventing it from joining the fight again.

"Amazing!" Fang Yuan could not help but praise.

Bing Sai Chuan looked at Qing Ye: "I am Longevity Heaven's Bing Sai Chuan, to think that someone of this generation recognized me."

As he said that, he smiled warmly but did not act mildly, he attacked the rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye who was on Eternal Yacht.

Fang Yuan had the help of Bing Sai Chuan, they managed to suppress the remaining three Immortal Gu Houses that Heavenly Court possessed!

At the next moment, a fifth time path Immortal Gu House appeared.

This was a gatehouse with a simple but elegant structure, its supporting pillars were bright red in color, it was quite auspicious. There were two dazzling words written on its entrance plaque — Year End.

Rank seven time path Immortal Gu House — Year End Gatehouse!

Chapter 1695: Contesting For Dragon Palace

Year End Gatehouse suddenly appeared in the River of Time, the side that got shocked was Heavenly Court instead of Fang Yuan's group.

This was because Heavenly Court only had four time path Immortal Gu Houses stationed here, this fifth time path Immortal Gu House Year End Gatehouse came from Northern Plains, it was owned by the Huang Jin tribes.

"Since when did an Immortal Gu House enter?"

"Oh no, what is it trying to do to the river suppression lotus sealing formation?"

"Quick, stop it!!"

Heavenly Court's side shouted, even rank eight Gu Immortals showed shock on their faces.

Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly, frost energy oozed out of his body, he slammed with both palms as Eternal Yacht was sent to the bottom of the river.

Fang Yuan shouted loudly, he mustered his strength and attacked Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform, raining down punches like a flurry of meteors, forcing the latter to retreat continuously.

Present and Past Pavilion was sealed, it had sunk into the river, vanishing entirely.

Xing Ye Wang who was on Shark Flow Lever had an ashen expression, he tried to stop Year End Gatehouse but it was too late.

As the immortals watched, Year End Gatehouse got close to the river suppression lotus sealing formation as the gatehouse started to shine in a pure white light.

Next, a voice could be heard from within: "Take a good look, this is my five elements profound light!"

Ringgggggggg!

There was a loud sound as a mystical five colored light shot out of the gatehouse, landing on the river suppression lotus sealing formation.

The five colored lights resembled five river currents that merged and weaved together, melting the layers of the river suppression lotus sealing formation, causing a huge hole in an instant!

"Quick, repair the formation!"

"What method is this, the river suppression lotus sealing formation was completely powerless against it?!"

The rank seven Gu Immortals controlling the super immortal formation were furious and shocked.

Feng Jiu Ge's pupils shrunk, he recognized it: "That must be Northern Plains' rank eight lone immortal Five Elements Grandmaster! This person cultivates formation path and mimics the five paths of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, he is a formation path great grandmaster. He was actually recruited by Longevity Heaven!"

After using this move, Five Elements Grandmaster panted heavily, his aura diminished until it became extremely weak.

His five elements profound light was most skilled in breaking immortal formations, he had prepared this move for a long time, once it was unleashed, half of the river suppression lotus sealing formation was destroyed, it was on the brink of destruction.

Of course, this was because Fang Yuan had given Longevity Heaven crucial information.

Fang Yuan had a deeper understanding of this river suppression lotus sealing formation, after all, he was locked in and had broken out of it personally.

With this intel, Five Elements Grandmaster was able to modify his five elements profound light to counter this river suppression lotus sealing formation!

Once the formation was broken, the stone lotus island inside became exposed before everyone's eyes.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily as he jumped up.

Boom!

He kicked hard and stomped Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform into the river, creating a huge wave.

Next, he shot out like a cannonball, flying into the formation, towards the stone lotus island.

The Gu Immortals in the river suppression lotus sealing formation were flustered, they worked up a sweat trying to stabilize the formation and prevent it from collapsing. If this super immortal formation broke, its controllers would face huge backlash. These Gu Immortals were also trying to save their own lives.

The formation's controllers were too busy with their own matters, they could only watch as Fang Yuan went in.

"Red Lotus' true inheritance!" Fang Yuan looked at the stone lotus island as his eyes flashed with a bright light. The Spring Autumn Cicada inside time path clone's aperture was shaking, right now, Spring Autumn Cicada was rank seven and had Fang Yuan's personal immortal killer move to discern if the stone lotus island was real.

It was the real deal!

In the previous Red Lotus true inheritance, Fang Yuan made great gains, he was lifted out of his difficult situation. If he could obtain this Red Lotus true inheritance as well, how much would he grow?

"Fang Yuan, don't think of leaving!" At this moment, Xing Ye Wang shouted as he moved Shark Flow Lever and attacked Fang Yuan's back.

"Scram!" At the crucial moment, Bing Sai Chuan appeared, blocking Shark Flow Lever.

"Fang Yuan, quickly go get Red Lotus true inheritance!" Bing Sai Chuan fought as he said to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked at Bing Sai Chuan deeply, it seemed that Longevity Heaven was very sincere about cooperating! He got closer to the stone lotus island without stopping.

"Don't think about it!" Rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye who was inside Eternal Yacht went around Bing Sai Chuan and Xing Ye Wang, going towards Fang Yuan.

"Want to chase him? Hehe, get past me first." Year End Gatehouse suddenly appeared abruptly, blocking Qing Ye's path.

Qing Ye frowned but laughed coldly: "My Eternal Yacht is the fastest, it can ride the waves of the River of Time, how can you Year End Gatehouse stop me? Hmm?!"

Suddenly, Qing Ye's expression changed as she saw that an immortal formation had appeared around Eternal Yacht.

"Setting up a time path formation in such a short time?" Qing Ye shook, he finally understood the formation path attainment that Five Elements Grandmaster had.

"This Red Lotus true inheritance is mine!" After obtaining Longevity Heaven's reinforcement, Fang Yuan obtained enough time to successfully get close to the stone lotus island, he was about to step onto it.

But at this moment, a change occurred, the stone lotus island erupted with a formless force and pushed Fang Yuan far away.

"What happened?" Suspicion rose in Fang Yuan's mind: "I have Spring Autumn Cicada with me, unless… once this stone lotus island lets me in, the defenses will vanish? Or will a loophole appear that would allow others to take advantage of it?"

Boom boom boom!

At this point, attacks that approached like a wild storm rained down on Fang Yuan's immemorial year monkey body and surrounded him.

The river suppression lotus sealing formation was finally stabilized, even though it was damaged, the hole was shrinking, the rank seven Gu Immortals controlling it were now able to find time to fight Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was obstructed by the formation, he could not get close to the stone lotus island as easily now.

"This formation is likely created by Heavenly Court to target stone lotus island. The stone lotus island rejected me earlier because of this formation?"

Fang Yuan was thinking about this when Feng Jiu Ge who was inside Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform arrived before him.

The two sides started to fight again, they clashed and exchanged moves, the situation was in a deadlock.

At the same time.

Eastern Sea.

"Li Huang pays respects to Lord Duke Long!" In the sky, flames scattered as a muscular old man appeared, it was Heavenly Court's reinforcement, rank eight Gu Immortal Li Huang.

Duke Long nodded as he patted Feng Jin Huang who was beside him.

Feng Jin Huang was surrounded by a circular qi wall, she floated lightly towards Li Huang.

"Protect Huang Er, if anything happens to her, I will hold you accountable." Duke Long said plainly.

Li Huang had a grim expression as he said confidently: "Don't worry Lord Duke Long, with my verdant sun flame cloak, who in the world can harm Feng Jin Huang?"

Duke Long stopped looking at him, he looked towards the sky, in order to protect Feng Jin Huang, he had wasted some time, Dragon Palace had flown away already.

Duke Long smiled, feeling no nervousness.

He clenched his fists, it was time to take action.

At the next moment, he vanished on the spot.

Dragon Palace was obstructed by Qing Yue An again, while the other rank eight Gu Immortals fought each other.

"The chance will slip by easily, I need to grab my opportunity!" Qing Yue An's eyes burst out with brilliance, after so many days of fighting, he had finally obtained his fourth chance.

But right when Qing Yue An was about to reach Dragon Palace, an immense force approached, the aura of death almost suffocated him.

He quickly turned around, enduring the fatal attack, he managed to block it but flew away like a sandbag, spitting out huge amounts of blood.

"Duke Long, you!" Qing Yue An had a hoarse voice filled with anger.

Duke Long floated in the sky expressionlessly, his horns were flickering with purple-gold light, his long hair fluttered in the wind, his body was tough as a monolith, his dragon pupils shined with cold light.

Qing Yue An struggled to stabilize his body, he wanted to counter attack but his expression suddenly changed.

A dragon-shaped qi shot out of his chest, exploding.

Boom!

The explosion was not loud, but Qing Yue An's defenses were like useless scraps of paper.

Qing Yue An looked at Duke Long with disbelief and fright as he retreated!

He was bleeding intensely, his ribs were broken, his chest was almost fully blown off, his heart and lungs could be seen.

"Take this Duke Long!"

"This Immortal Gu House is mine!"

Song Qi Yuan and Zhang Yin flew over, the two temporarily stopped fighting each other as they faced against Duke Long together.

Duke Long smiled nonchalantly.

Roar—!

The dragon roar erupted as Song Qi Yuan and Zhang Yin flew away with a confused and flabbergasted expression.

They suffered serious injuries, they did not even see what move hit them before they were defeated.

"Be careful, without that burden, Duke Long is using his full power!"

"Is this his true strength?"

"Everyone, work together, we must not let him succeed!"

Duke Long's powerful disposition made the remaining rank eight Gu Immortals feel deeply threatened, they started to target him collectively.

Duke Long breathed in deeply, he actually shut his eyes.

He did not move, only when the surrounding killer moves reached before him did he open his eyes abruptly.

Immortal killer move — Qi Engulfing Mountains and Rivers!

"Hmm?!" At once, the rank eight Gu Immortals shook intensely as they felt an unparalleled pressure slamming down at them from all around.

Not just them, the killer moves that they activated, even the sky and sea of all the surroundings were facing this immense pressure.

Many killer moves collapsed, the rank eight Gu Immortals as well as Dragon Palace fell into the water like dumplings falling into a pot.

The world became still, nothing was left standing.

Except Duke Long, he was standing proudly in the sky, looking down at the immortals in distress with his cold dragon pupils.

At this point of the Dragon Palace contest, he had finally displayed his true strength.

Having pseudo-Immortal Venerable battle strength, it suppressed his enemies and obtained the upper hand!

"Kill!"

"Duke Long, I want to kill you!"

"I do not believe that you can defeat all of us!!"

A few breaths of time later, huge waves surged in the sea, the rank eight Gu Immortals who were humiliated by Duke Long attacked him together with great intensity.

Duke Long snorted coldly, his dragon tail appeared and his body became covered in scales, the horns on his head became as sharp as blades.

He opened his mouth and roared, it was immortal killer move dragon roaring wave.

Next, his body flickered from place to place, he appeared near his enemies as he punched their faces with his fists, tore defenses with his claws, and created a bloody storm around the area.

Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals were not his match, they were all furious and shocked, they used their immortal killer moves but were constantly obstructed, even if they succeeded, they could not injure Duke Long.

After such a long time, other than protecting Feng Jin Huang, Duke Long had also collected lots of information, he had grasped the weakness of some of these Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals' methods.

"Old fiend, you are too much!"

"Face my fatal killer move!"

"Restrain him, I have even stronger methods!"

Eastern Sea's rank eights were furious, they were about to use even stronger methods.

Immortal killer move — Qi Engulfing Mountains and Rivers!

Puff puff puff.

At the next moment, Eastern Sea's rank eights fell like dumplings again, into the depths of the ocean.

Duke Long controlled the tempo of the battle completely, his battle experience was even deeper than the depths of this ocean itself!

Chapter 1696: Feng Destroys Red Lotus

"Come!" Duke Long suddenly appeared above Dragon Palace.

An immense suction force sent the rank eight Immortal Gu House slowly towards Duke Long's phantom aperture even though it resisted him desperately.

The other rank eight Gu Immortals saw this and went over, using their killer moves on Duke Long.

Duke Long sighed as he vanished on the spot.

Without restraint, Dragon Palace flew out of the sea, into the sky once again.

Eastern Sea's rank eights were about to chase it when Duke Long appeared in the sky again, obstructing their paths.

Dragon roars resounded again, Duke Long moved like lightning, flickering around the rank eight Gu Immortals effortlessly, the intense battle created loud explosions resembling an unceasing thunderstorm, countless innocent lifeforms were implicated, huge tsunamis were created on the sea surface.

Without Feng Jin Huang burdening him, Duke Long displayed terrifying battle strength, nobody present could match him equally.

However, these Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals all had deep foundations, they had their own trump cards.

Even though they were losing to Duke Long, their lives were not endangered. They were wary of each other originally, but against Duke Long, they could cooperate seamlessly.

At once, Eastern Sea's righteous path, demonic path, and even lone cultivators worked together to fight Duke Long.

Duke Long felt increasing pressure.

His outburst earlier suppressed everyone, it was because he had concealed himself earlier and managed to catch all of the Eastern Sea rank eights off-guard with that one attack.

But as the battle continued, Duke Long's methods were slowly discerned by the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, they started to find counters or appropriate methods to deal with them.

In this world, there were no invincible Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves, there were only invincible Gu Immortals.

Any immortal killer move, no matter how complex, had a structure, it would have advantages and weaknesses.

Duke Long was very powerful indeed, none of the Eastern Sea rank eights were his match. But this situation was special, everyone was trying to get the Immortal Gu House, nobody wanted to fight him to the death. As the Immortal Gu House flew continuously all over the battlefield, Duke Long could not set up a battlefield to trap it.

Dragon claws moved like a tornado, many Eastern Sea rank eights were forced back, Duke Long crashed into Dragon Palace as he grabbed it with his hand.

At once, a pair of huge phantom dragon claws appeared and tightly grasped Dragon Palace.

Dragon Palace shook intensely, it shattered the phantom dragon claws as it escaped.

Duke Long sighed, this situation had already happened many times. It was not easy to take Dragon Palace, he had to fight off the competitors first before trying to subdue it. But Dragon Palace was a rank eight Immortal Gu House after all, it had great power and could not be taken easily.

Duke Long's many attempts ended in failure.

"Duke Long is too strong, what do we do?"

"When he fights seriously, we will have no chance to get close to Dragon Palace, not to mention obtain it!"

"Duke Long is the only one attempting now, thankfully this Immortal Gu House is strong enough!"

"We cannot let this go on. Dragon Palace's resistance is getting weaker, Duke Long will subdue it eventually."

Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals all had injuries, they communicated with each other as they wanted others to use their trump cards against Duke Long.

Getting to rank eight, who would not have their own secret trump cards?

These immortal killer moves were definitely very powerful or mysterious and profound, but nobody wanted to expose them. Nobody could say for sure if their killer moves would fail in such a complex battle environment.

The stronger the killer move, the greater the backlash.

Even Duke Long was not using his triple qi retraction killer move.

Not that he did not want to use it, but the risks were too great, he could likely cripple himself.

When he fought against Purple Mountain True Monarch earlier, he had probed multiple times, only until he was sure that the enemy did not have other methods did he unleash triple qi retraction in the end.

Right now in this situation, if Duke Long used triple qi retraction and the enemy coincidentally countered it, what would happen?

These Eastern Sea rank eights were numerous and they all had deep foundations, who knew what methods they truly possessed!

Notched arrows were the most threatening. Gu Immortals who concealed their killer moves were also very threatening.

River of Time.

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Fang Yuan was still in his immemorial year monkey form, his killer move activated successfully as he grabbed towards the space in front of him.

A huge fan with a long handle appeared out of nowhere, held in his hands.

"Bing Sai Chuan, get aside!"

Fang Yuan twisted his waist as he gathered strength in his arms, waving the fan ferociously.

Gush!! Wild winds blew, sweeping ahead as the storm sent Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and Shark Flow Lever into a tornado, restraining them as they flew outside of the river suppression lotus sealing formation.

But at the crucial moment, Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang flew out of their Immortal Gu Houses, charging at Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan.

Even though they did not cultivate time path, the river suppression lotus sealing formation did not break apart, time path was restricted in the formation as other paths were amplified.

Heavenly Court sent rank seven Gu Immortals which were elites, they worked together during this period and were able to mostly repair the river suppression lotus sealing formation, even though the hole was still present, it had become much smaller.

"Five Elements Grandmaster, quickly use your profound light!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Five Elements Grandmaster's voice came from within Year End Gatehouse: "I cannot use it a second time in this short period, this formation has been modified by a lot, the previous profound light will be ineffective now."

Immortal killer move — Song Warrior!

Feng Jiu Ge's body shook as four song warriors emerged, encircling Fang Yuan.

Xing Ye Wang's body was covered in starlight specks as he stabbed towards Bing Sai Chuan like a hedgehog.

Bing Sai Chuan and Fang Yuan looked at each other before flying up and abandoning their enemies, targeting the river suppression lotus sealing formation instead.

This was the wisest plan.

As long as the river suppression lotus sealing formation was destroyed, Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang would have to return to their Immortal Gu Houses.

Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang quickly tried to stop them, while Five Elements Grandmaster continued to control his immortal formation to trap the Eternal Yacht that Qing Ye was controlling.

In the intense battle, river suppression lotus sealing formation shook more and more intensely, more cracks were appearing as it endured Fang Yuan's and Bing Sai Chuan's attacks.

However, Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and Shark Flow Lever, which Fang Yuan blew away earlier, had reentered the battlefield, Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven were starting to be suppressed.

"Fang Yuan, you still refuse to trust me now?" The situation was dire, Bing Sai Chuan shouted in anxiety.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light, he snorted coldly as he approached Bing Sai Chuan.

Bing Sai Chuan spread his arms as a ball shaped light shield appeared around him and Fang Yuan.

This was his defensive immortal killer move, anything that hit the light shield, be it lifeforms or killer moves, would freeze in time.

"Break it!" Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang shouted together.

Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and Shark Flow Lever erupted with powerful attacks, targeting Bing Sai Chuan's light shield.

But any killer move that landed on it froze in time, at once, there was a myriad of colorful attacks surrounding the light shield, it was a dazzling sight.

Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth, his body shook as he sustained the shield.

Even though he had rank eight peak battle strength, in this formation, time path was suppressed, at the same time, he was facing the attack of two rank eight Gu Immortals and two Immortal Gu Houses, it was not easy.

Fang Yuan obtained this prime opportunity, he dispelled immemorial year monkey transformation and activated emperor yama.

At this point in the battle, he finally obtained a chance to change his battle tactic.

Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang had rich battle experiences, they did not give Fang Yuan any opportunity to change his transformation, he was often interrupted.

After becoming emperor yama, Fang Yuan started to use his killer moves.

His aura surged rapidly from weak to strong, and from strong to a terrifying level.

Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang had solemn expressions, they were very alert.

At this point, Fang Yuan finally had the time to unleash his trump card.

Immortal killer move — Luo Po Seal!

"Be careful!" Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth as he dispelled his defensive killer move, moving forward.

Without obstruction, the frozen attacks from earlier struck towards Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan.

Bing Sai Chuan stood in front and paved a way for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan held onto Luo Po seal as he waited in anticipation, he charged towards Xing Ye Wang while enduring the attacks.

Xing Ye Wang quickly retreated while Feng Jiu Ge went around, trying to attack Fang Yuan from the rear.

Fang Yuan suddenly laughed coldly, he flew up and shot Luo Po seal towards the river suppression lotus sealing formation.

The huge formation stopped working, several rank seven Gu Immortals inside died on the spot.

Bing Sai Chuan suddenly felt the pressure lifting, swoosh swoosh, large amounts of water from the River of Time gushed into the formation.

Immediately after, with cracking noises, river suppression lotus sealing formation disintegrated piece by piece.

Five Elements Grandmaster was deeply shocked: "Fang Yuan's Luo Po seal actually attacked the core of the formation and destroyed the core Immortal Gu, how did he deduce it?"

Boom!

Feng Jiu Ge's attack landed on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's attention was on destroying the formation, he could only endure Feng Jiu Ge's ferocious attack.

Even in emperor yama form, Fang Yuan spat out three mouthfuls of blood, large numbers of soul path Gu worms died and multiple Immortal Gu were injured.

Without the formation's help, the battle environment changed rapidly, Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan obtained the upper hand again.

Both sides fought for a while, the river suppression lotus sealing formation had about one-third of its original size left, the remaining rank seven Gu Immortals were desperately holding on, but the formation was just a step away from destruction, they had no hope left.

"Cover me!" Fang Yuan said to Bing Sai Chuan.

Bing Sai Chuan used the ball shaped light shield, protecting Fang Yuan as he dispelled emperor yama, turning into the immemorial year monkey again.

"Cover me!" Feng Jiu Ge shouted the same thing.

Xing Ye Wang and the two Immortal Gu Houses surrounded Feng Jiu Ge immediately.

Immortal killer move — Assimilation Wind Song!

Feng Jiu Ge took a huge risk and successfully summoned the number one wind in the world!

Bing Sai Chuan broke out in sweat as he shouted to Fang Yuan: "Oh no, my defensive killer move cannot block the winds of assimilation, let's retreat!"

But out of their expectations, the winds of assimilation did not target the defensive shield, it attacked the stone lotus island.

Under Fang Yuan's shocked gaze, the stone lotus island was devoured by the winds of assimilation, the fragments were assimilated into wind.

The winds of assimilation became larger and larger, if anyone tried to get onto the island, they would have to face this world-destroying wind!

"Feng Jiu Ge, you!" Bing Sai Chuan was furious and anxious.

Fang Yuan's expression was ashen.

"If we cannot get it, neither will you." Xing Ye Wang laughed wildly.

Chapter 1697: Neither Victory Nor Defeat

The winds of assimilation ravaged in the River of Time.

When Feng Jiu Ge used assimilation wind song, there were sounds of howling winds. But when the actual winds of assimilation started blowing, it became extremely quiet, there was no sound at all.

The quiet winds of assimilation made every Gu Immortal present feel a chill down their spine.

The stone lotus island was continuously eroded by the winds of assimilation until it completely vanished, the winds grew larger and larger, multiple times its initial size after devouring the stone lotus island, it was like a pillar that supported heaven and earth.

However, it could not display its might in the River of Time, even though a lot of water was assimilated into wind, the entire River of Time did not budge, it had lost a completely negligible amount of water.

Even though the winds of assimilation were powerful, against the River of Time, it was too small, like a tiny insect on a bull.

All the Gu Immortals and Immortal Gu Houses had to steer clear of the winds of assimilation, Feng Jiu Ge was no exception.

"The stone lotus island was really destroyed!" Fang Yuan was deeply shocked, earlier when he wanted to get on the island, he was repelled by its protection force. To think that it was completely helpless against the winds of assimilation.

"Don't tell me this formation played a role in suppressing the stone lotus island earlier? Or was the island already at its limit, so it could not block the winds of assimilation?"

Fang Yuan watched as the river suppression lotus sealing formation continued to break apart.

Feng Jiu Ge also had a heavy feeling.

Even though he destroyed the stone lotus island, in his opinion, he had failed.

In order to find Red Lotus' true inheritances, Heavenly Court had paid a huge price in manpower and resources, they managed to find a stone lotus island after so much work, and trapped it using the river suppression lotus sealing formation. But to think that Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven worked together to obstruct them.

Feng Jiu Ge had no choice but to destroy the stone lotus island, all of their hard work had been wasted.

But nobody could blame him for his actions.

Because it was necessary!

After the river suppression lotus sealing formation got hit by Luo Po seal, it was definitely going to break apart. Once the formation breaks, Feng Jiu Ge and Xing Ye Wang would be forced to return to the Immortal Gu House.

This way, Heavenly Court's side would lose their battle strength.

In contrast, Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan would be like fish in water in this River of Time, without the formation restraining them, their battle strength would surge.

The enemy was strong while they were weaker, Feng Jiu Ge had no confidence in continuing the struggle, Fang Yuan would obtain the stone lotus island eventually. Thus, when there was still a chance, he decided to cut his losses short by destroying the stone lotus island.

"Such resolution." A sharp light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, he did not hide his praise.

Bing Sai Chuan sighed deeply, showing a dejected look.

He was hoping to find some way to destroy fate Gu from the Red Lotus true inheritance, but now, even though Fang Yuan had the key Spring Autumn Cicada, the stone lotus island was already destroyed.

He was very disappointed, he did not know that Fang Yuan had already obtained one true inheritance in secret!

Fang Yuan was obviously not going to tell Longevity Heaven about this, even Heavenly Court was in the dark.

Rumble!

With a chain of loud explosions, the heavily damaged river suppression lotus sealing formation broke, most of the Immortal Gu were destroyed, while the Gu Immortals controlling the formation died one by one.

River water moved in as huge waves were formed, the River of Time was restored to normal.

"Let's retreat!" Feng Jiu Ge gritted his teeth as he spoke.

The battle was not in Heavenly Court's favor.

Even though they had three rank eight Gu Immortals, in this situation, even if Duke Long came, they would not win.

Feng Jiu Ge and the rest were not time path Gu Immortals, they could only hide in the Immortal Gu Houses, relying on them to fight.

And these time path Immortal Gu Houses were only rank seven, if they had one rank eight time path Immortal Gu House, Heavenly Court would have a chance of victory!

Even though Heavenly Court had immense foundation, it was not without limits.

Firstly, after Lord Huang Shi died, they no longer had any time path rank eight Gu Immortals. Even though they created four time path Immortal Gu Houses, they were only rank seven. Heavenly Court did not have the ability to create a rank eight time path Immortal Gu House in such a short period of time!

Actually, Fairy Zi Wei's arrangements were not wrong.

Even though Fang Yuan obtained a Red Lotus true inheritance and modified most of his killer moves, while also raising the rank of his Immortal Gu, his increase in battle strength did not make this battle any easier, Fang Yuan alone could not obtain this Red Lotus true inheritance.

Heavenly Court did not expect that Longevity Heaven would suddenly cooperate with Fang Yuan.

After all, Fang Yuan destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there was deep enmity between Fang Yuan and Longevity Heaven. This was not just simple hatred, Fang Yuan did not just destroy a rank eight Immortal Gu House, he destroyed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangements, the pride and glory of the Huang Jin tribes.

"Longevity Heaven actually gave up on revenge and cooperated with Fang Yuan. Is this because of Bing Sai Chuan?" Feng Jiu Ge returned to Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and looked at Bing Sai Chuan, frowning.

Heavenly Court's three Immortal Gu Houses were retreating rapidly.

Fang Yuan roared, he turned into the immemorial year monkey and chased after them.

Bing Sai Chuan fought side by side with him.

The two had powerful and ferocious attacks, they aimed at Heavenly Court's three Immortal Gu Houses.

Even though there were three rank eights on Heavenly Court's side, they could only defend, resist attacks, and escape.

Present and Past Pavilion finally broke out of Bing Sai Chuan's killer move, it quickly flew out of the River of Time, appearing above the surface.

The three Xunzi were very angry, they wanted to attack Fang Yuan, but they saw that the three Heavenly Court Immortal Gu Houses were escaping, the river suppression lotus sealing formation had broken up, the rank seven Gu Immortals controlling the formation had almost all died, the remaining few were struggling in the River of Time, they were not far from dying.

"Quickly retreat!" Feng Jiu Ge transmitted.

The three Xunzi gulped as they quickly joined the group and escaped.

Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan, as well as Five Elements Grandmaster controlling Year End Gatehouse, chased after them.

These four Immortal Gu Houses were very sturdy, they defended each other and were hard to catch.

But Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan got stronger as they fought, in this River of Time, their battle strength was far above their usual standards.

"The tributary of the River of Time is close by, we are about to escape!" Qing Ye shouted, raising the morale of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

"Want to leave? Not so easy!" Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly, shortening their distance.

"All of you retreat, we will block them!" The three Xunzi were resolved to die, they stayed behind along with the tattered Present and Past Pavilion.

As the three Xunzi stalled for time desperately, the other three Immortal Gu Houses managed to escape through the tributary of the River of Time.

Present and Past Pavilion was completely destroyed, the three Xunzi died as well.

Fang Yuan was filled with regret that he did not capture any rank eight Gu Immortal, this was a really good chance.

Fang Yuan did not want to chase after them, in the outside world, Feng Jiu Ge and the rest could fight normally.

He swept through the battlefield and collected the immortal apertures, annexing them.

Bing Sai Chuan and Five Elements Grandmaster did not move, they watched by the side.

There were quite a few rank seven Gu Immortals who died, they did not have qualification to join Heavenly Court so they still retained their rank seven immortal apertures.

Fang Yuan annexed them and made great gains.

"Let's go to Eastern Sea." After a while, Fang Yuan suggested.

Longevity Heaven had displayed their fullest sincerity in the battle over Red Lotus true inheritance, they were reliable allies for now.

Both sides had the same goal, to prevent Heavenly Court from repairing fate Gu.

If Heavenly Court obtained the complete fate Gu, they would regain their former glory, they would threaten the other four regions.

After staying for a while in the River of Time, Fang Yuan and Bing Sai Chuan confirmed that the Red Lotus true inheritance was truly destroyed. Even though they did not obtain it, they had managed to stop Heavenly Court from getting it, this result was neither defeat nor victory.

Soon, Fang Yuan and the rest left the River of Time, heading to Eastern Sea to stop Duke Long.

But along the way, they heard that the commotion in Eastern Sea was over, the outcome had been determined.

The eventual victor of this battle over Dragon Palace was Duke Long! Duke Long had incredible battle strength, he suppressed the Eastern Sea rank eights, afterwards, Heavenly Court's new member, rank eight Gu Immortal Chen Yi went there with an Immortal Gu House. At the crucial moment, Eastern Sea's lone immortal Yang Jun suddenly turned to help Duke Long, allowing him to successfully suppress the rank eight Immortal Gu House and keep it.

But Duke Long suffered heavy injuries as a result.

At the final moment, Eastern Sea's rank eights stopped holding back, they used their trump cards.

But it was already too late, after getting the Immortal Gu House, Duke Long left immediately without second thought.

"To think that this rank eight lone immortal Yang Jun was recruited by Heavenly Court!" Five Elements Grandmaster shook his head continuously. He was once a lone immortal too, but he had become a member of Longevity Heaven now.

"That might not be the case, Yang Jun might have been Heavenly Court's spy in Eastern Sea from the start." Fang Yuan thought of Prince Feng Xian in Northern Plains, he was a spy implanted into Northern Plains from the start, his identity had not been exposed.

Fang Yuan looked at Bing Sai Chuan for a moment, deciding to continue keeping this as a secret.

Chapter 1698: Slaughter Begins

Central Continent regional wall.

"Go, quickly go!"

"Catch up, don't break away from the group."

A group of Western Desert Gu Masters shouted as they ran.

Behind them, the ground tore open, like a giant beast opening its mouth to devour people.

"Ahh—!"

"Save me!!"

Amidst cries and screams, a small group of people at the back fell into the Earth Trench, most of them were smashed to bits, those that luckily survived would also die eventually.

"Father, I can't hold on anymore!" Zhang Ping was a young man who had just become a rank two Gu Master, he was showing a flustered expression now, his primeval essence had already dried up.

"Oh no." Zhang Quan was a rank three Gu Master, he was covered in sweat now. He was already trying his best, using his killer move to not only move himself but also his son Zhang Ping.

If Zhang Ping ran out of primeval essence, Zhang Quan's killer move would be ineffective on him. By then, Zhang Ping would become very slow, Zhang Quan would be helpless as he watched his son fall into the abyss.

"What should I do?" Zhang Quan was helpless and anxious.

He regretted his decision deeply, if he had known this, he would not have brought his son to join the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention!

He had considered this because of his son's refinement path talent, he wanted to train his ability and gain more knowledge. But to think that they encountered an earth vein tremor while crossing the regional wall.

Right when Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping were despairing, the sight in front of them cleared up.

Zhang Quan was dazed before reacting, they had passed Central Continent's regional wall, they had arrived in Central Continent.

Because of earth vein tremors, other than causing lots of Earth Trenches, Gu materials, and Gu worms to appear, the five region's regional walls were also shrinking.

Right now, Gu Masters needed less than half the time to cross two region's regional walls compared to before.

"But so what?" Zhang Quan sighed deeply.

Zhang Ping was out of primeval essence and stamina, Zhang Quan had to carry him, but because of this, their speed was very slow, they were almost about to get devoured by the Earth Trench.

At the crucial moment, a mystical light shot towards them as the remaining Gu Masters were all brought into the sky.

The Earth Trench parted below their feet, soon, a huge and unfathomably deep abyss formed below them.

Only until they landed on the periphery of the Earth Trench did the mystical light enveloping these Gu Masters disappear.

"What is going on?"

"Who saved us?"

"Such an incredible method, I'm afraid it has to be a great Gu Immortal who saved all of us!"

The Gu Masters were all extremely excited from surviving that, they started talking among themselves.

Above the sky where they could not see, a Spirit Butterfly Valley Gu Immortal smiled kindly as he retreated his gaze from these Gu Masters.

The Gu Immortal flew rapidly, patrolling the area.

Central Continent's Refinement Path Convention had begun, many Gu Masters had been coming here for the last few days from the other four regions.

The Gu Immortal was a member of Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, he had received a compulsory mission from the sect to patrol this area and prevent the demonic path from causing trouble.

Many Gu Immortals received the same mission as him. These were all members of the ten great ancient sects, some independent sects, or even slave Gu Immortals captured by the ten great ancient sects, as well as lone immortals close to the ten sects.

This time, Heavenly Court held the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, security was extremely strict, it was unprecedented.

Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping's group was luckily saved by the Gu Immortal, retaining their lives.

After getting into Central Continent, they rested for a while before going to the closest sign up spot.

Central Continent Refinement Path Convention had many sign up spots, they were evenly distributed all over Central Continent.

A few days later, Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping arrived at Scorpion Needle Sect with some Gu Masters that had similar objectives.

This was an ordinary sect, its specialty was in raising Gu that resembled scorpions, they were most famous for scorpion needle Gu. This was an offensive Gu worm, once used, it could shoot out scorpion needles. The needles were sharp and fast, they were poisonous and hard to deal with.

Scorpion Needle Sect had already made the arrangements.

Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping walked into the registration hall, it was packed with people.

A large portion were Central Continent locals, the remaining were like them who had come from the western region.

Scorpion Needle Sect was situated near Western Desert, many Western Desert Gu Masters came here to sign up.

The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention always attracted countless Gu Masters to participate, this time was no exception.

Following the procedures, Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping were brought into a hall for assessment.

The test only had four questions, it was not easy but not hard either. The test was regarding basic skills, any Gu Master with enough experience can pass, those who were trying their luck would be eliminated, to save on resources and manpower.

Zhang Quan and Zhang Ping passed the test without any unexpected surprises, they successfully signed up.

After getting out of the hall, they held a token each.

The token recorded the participant's name, sect, path, and the time and location of his test.

When a Gu Master signs up, their names could be fake, their paths and sects could also be kept secret.

Because of this, during every Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, a large number of lone cultivators, demonic path members, and even Gu Immortals would join while concealing their identity.

"A hundred primeval stones per person signing up, this is too expensive." Zhang Ping kept his token as he said grudgingly.

"So you must perform well this time, don't waste our investment." Zhang Quan looked at Zhang Ping with a gaze of anticipation.

"Yes." Zhang Ping nodded: "Oh yes, father, I saw that many Central Continent Gu Masters signed up directly, they did not need to take the test."

Zhang Quan smiled: "These people had gotten a certain position in the previous convention, they are able to join it directly now."

"Father, didn't you get a placing yourself in the last convention? Why do you have to pay again?" Zhang Ping did not understand.

Zhang Quan shook his head: "That is because I am not a Central Continent person, only Central Continent Gu Masters have this treatment."

"So that's it." Zhang Ping nodded.

This was clearly favoritism towards the locals, it was unfair but the young Zhang Ping soon accepted it.

This was Central Continent's territory after all, the convention was also held in Central Continent, what's wrong with helping their own people?

And this was not unfair either, because this test only looked at the basics, any Gu Master with refinement path attainment could pass it.

"The Refinement Path Convention is about to begin." In Heavenly Court, Duke Long used his investigative killer move as he paid attention to the situation in Central Continent.

His face was still pale now, his injuries sustained from obtaining Dragon Palace had not healed.

"This Refinement Path Convention will be very crucial, oh Red Lotus, do you know, after this convention, fate Gu will be fully restored." Duke Long's eyes became dazed as scenes of the past surfaced in his mind.

"Spring Autumn Cicada? You actually designed such a heretical Immortal Gu, Hong Ting, what are you trying to do?" After learning of this, Duke Long immediately went to find Red Lotus Immortal Venerable, Hong Ting.

Hong Ting clenched his fists, saying to Duke Long: "Master, I've already said it before, I want to revive them, let everything start over again."

"You!" Duke Long pointed at Hong Ting, he was shivering from anger.

Hong Ting lowered his head: "Master, scold me if you want, beat me if you want, but I will never give up!"

Duke Long looked at Hong Ting angrily, he did not scold him, instead, he sighed after a long while of silence: "Hong Ting, my disciple, you are too naive. Even if you are an Immortal Venerable, what can you do to fate? Go ahead and try, I won't stop you. You will definitely fail, but I hope that countless failures can wake you up."

Many days later.

"Master…" Hong Ting was covered in injuries but he was extremely excited, he came before Duke Long: "I finally found the only hope, I am about to succeed, I will definitely change fate!"

"How can that be possible?!" Duke Long did not believe him at all.

"I am relying on this — love Gu. I had obtained inspiration from <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>. It says that love is a type of fate, in that case, love can definitely change fate!" Hong Ting said in increasing excitement.

Duke Long was extremely furious and shocked: "Heresy, blasphemy, Hong Ting, don't forget your identity! You are a righteous path Immortal Venerable, you want to change history, do you know that such actions will have an unimaginably bad effect?"

"Oh master!" Hong Ting raised his head, looking at Duke Long with glimmering eyes: "You still don't understand?"

"Understand what?"

"Times have changed! The hearts of the people have changed too. Our generation does not need restrictions…"

Before Hong Ting finished his words, Duke Long shouted: "Enough! You actually said fate Gu is a form of restriction? Hong Ting, enough is enough, at this rate, you will fall into the demonic path! I… I do not want to exterminate you in the name of justice!!!"

Breathing in deeply, Duke Long regained clarity in his eyes.

His memories were kept away, but Duke Long still had a sense of guilt left in him.

"Oh Red Lotus… you did not understand after all." Duke Long muttered: "No matter how times change, fate Gu will always be the protector of humanity. You are disregarding the big picture of humanity for your personal selfish goals, I failed in my teachings!"

"You are my disciple, as your master, I will atone for your mistakes."

"I do not have much time left."

"But it is fine, I just need to wait until fate Gu is repaired."

"I will not allow anyone to ruin this Refinement Path Convention!"

Boom—!

At the same time, Scorpion Needle Sect erupted with an intense explosion, countless Gu Masters who participated in the Refinement Path Convention died or got injured.

As dust clouds settled, an ancient desolate year snake hissed in the rubble of Scorpion Needle Sect.

Watching the ancient year snake slaughter more Gu Masters, Fang Yuan left with a cold smile.

Using an immortal killer move with Fixed Immortal Travel as the core, he left for the next location.

Heavenly Court wanted to repair Fate, they had to hold the Refinement Path Convention to gain success dao marks. How could Fang Yuan allow them to succeed so easily?

A merciless slaughter had begun.

Chapter 1699: Attacking Everywhere

Unification Sect was one of the sign up locations of the Refinement Path Convention, it was filled with people as well.

"The Refinement Path Convention is about to start! To think that I would get a second chance in this lifetime, thank the heavens." A middle aged Gu Master sighed deeply.

The Gu Masters nearby recognized him as they started to talk among themselves.

"Quickly look, it is refinement path master Luo Sheng!"

"He had lost in the previous Refinement Path Convention due to some accident, it seems he wants to compete again."

"Normally, the Refinement Path Convention is held once in a hundred years, Luo Sheng was not supposed to have a chance. But to think that ten years later, the ten great ancient sects would hold it again!"

The middle aged Gu Master heard their discussions as he kept a peaceful expression.

He was way beyond the age of vanity, he just wanted to prove himself now.

"My opponents this time cannot be underestimated."

"Even though I worked very hard during this period, Central Continent is too huge, the five regions have countless geniuses."

"And even at this spot, there are already many new talents…"

The middle aged Gu Master looked around, focusing his attention on three Gu Masters. One was an old man that had been reputed for many years, he was also a refinement path master. Another was a young man, and the last one was a young girl. The former had performed well in the previous convention while the latter was a rising star that had emerged in the last ten years.

"This Refinement Path Convention is still going to be that intense!"

"I must make good use of this opportunity, I cannot fail anymore…"

"I will prove myself, I will let my wife and children be proud!"

Boom!

At the next moment, a huge ancient year beast descended from the sky, crushing the entire hall to ruins.

The middle aged Gu Master's grand ambitions vanished into thin air.

The young Gu Master with a great future, the genius young girl who was highly thought of died pathetically on the spot, her bones and flesh were mashed together, even her corpse could not be seen clearly.

"Onto the next location." In the sky, Fang Yuan's figure flickered and vanished.

This was the fifteenth spot that he had attacked.

Central Continent lost many Gu Masters, these were just mortal Gu Masters, how could they handle the ancient year beasts?

Even rank six Gu Immortals might not be able to face these ancient year beasts.

Fang Yuan slaughtered these Gu Masters mercilessly, he created lots of bloodshed, more and more talented Gu Masters were killed, even Heavenly Court was feeling heartache.

"This demon Fang Yuan, he is truly evil and vicious, he came to cause trouble after all!"

"Damn it, are we going to watch and do nothing?"

"Lady Zi Wei, I wonder if…"

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head: "Fang Yuan is very vigilant, he only sent out ancient year beasts each time to attack, even though he slaughtered many Gu Masters and caused great chaos, he rarely attacked personally."

Fairy Zi Wei sighed deeply: "His wisdom path attainment is truly deep, he knows that the more he attacks, the more clues he would leave behind, and the more easily we can find him. It is very hard for me to locate him, I will need more clues and even more time."

"But how can he have so many ancient year beasts?" Some Gu Immortals frowned.

"According to Southern Border's information, Xia Cha had a year essence pool in her immortal aperture, he should have used this to capture so many year beasts." Fairy Zi Wei said.

Even though her expression was calm, she was filled with rage.

Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal yet he attacked these mortals without restraint, he was really bullying the weak and was simply too shameless, he had no bottom line!

Most demonic path Gu Immortals would not do this.

This was the tacit consensus among Gu Immortals, but Fang Yuan broke it without concern.

"This Fang Yuan is truly the greatest plague to all lifeforms in this world!" Fairy Zi Wei was furious while feeling sadness for those innocent lives: "The longer he lives in this world, the more lifeforms he would harm and kill."

Duke Long was truly calm, his heart was like a tranquil lake.

"Good, Fang Yuan showed up, didn't we expect this to happen? Follow our plan, even if we have to pay a huge price, we must repair fate Gu!" Duke Long was immensely determined.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals heard his orders and realized: Nothing in this world could affect Duke Long's determination.

Fang Yuan was a real problem, Heavenly Court could not ignore him, they had a plan already.

Several days later, the people who were in deep fear of Fang Yuan's assaults received accurate proof and information.

All evidence pointed to Fang Yuan, he was the culprit!

Everyone was extremely riled up.

"Fang Yuan has already become a Gu Immortal?!"

"There really are immortals in this world…"

"Fang Yuan, you killed my father, I will definitely take revenge for this immense hatred!"

"Even rank fives are just ants if they do not become Gu Immortals."

"Fang Yuan is evidently trying to ruin the Refinement Path Convention, for the sake of my life, I'm not going."

"Go! Why not? If we do not go, wouldn't we fall into that Fang Yuan's scheme?"

"That's right, even though I am a mortal Gu Master and will not be Fang Yuan's match, to avenge my wife's death, I will even give up my life, I will not let this demon Fang Yuan succeed!"

Some were fearful, some felt emotional, some backed out, while some became determined.

Time passed, days went by, the Refinement Path Convention continued.

Fang Yuan was all alone but Central Continent had many sign up locations for the Refinement Path Convention. Even though he had Fixed Immortal Travel, he could not eliminate every Gu Master that went.

Because many places were secretly guarded by Central Continent's Gu Immortals.

Especially when Heavenly Court made arrangements after Fang Yuan's attacks, they sent out missions to countless Gu Masters to move around and distribute tokens to other participants of the tests.

This way, the participants in Central Continent became dispersed, nobody went to sign up locations, Fang Yuan's slaughter became very inefficient.

Even though Fang Yuan tried, more than ten thousand Gu Masters died in his hands, but he could not stop the Refinement Path Convention from starting.

The sign up phase was over, the true competition had already started.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan appeared at a place in Central Continent, he was about to attack when he suddenly frowned.

"Where are you going, Fang Yuan?"

"Die!"

A Central Continent rank eight Gu Immortal pounced at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gave a glance at him, he did not want to fight, he used his killer move to escape.

"Central Continent's Gu Immortals have been getting faster and faster recently, is it because I've used Fixed Immortal Travel's killer move too frequently, they have already deduced it?"

"Even so, they seem to be able to detect where I would show up, what is this investigative method? Time path?"

At the next moment, Fang Yuan's surroundings changed, he was hundreds of thousands of li away from the previous place.

But his expression was grim, he sensed acutely that three rank eight Gu Immortals were approaching him from three directions.

"Fang Yuan, where are you going?"

"Heavenly Court has prepared more than ten investigative killer moves for you, you cannot escape!"

"Especially one of them, it was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, known as people's accusation! Hahaha, demon, did you think of this? The more people you kill, the more hatred you gather, these mortal Gu Masters' hatred will continuously track you down."

The three rank eights arrived before Fang Yuan.

Immortal battlefield killer move — Rumor Cage!

Suddenly, a fourth rank eight Gu Immortal appeared above Fang Yuan, using an immortal battlefield to trap him.

"We caught Fang Yuan!"

"Lord Zhou Xiong Xin's rumor cage is truly the battlefield killer move with the fastest activation time, even Fang Yuan could not react in time."

The four Gu Immortals were overjoyed.

"Lord Duke Long, we finally trapped Fang Yuan." Inside Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei was extremely excited.

"Mm." Duke Long replied plainly.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes shined brightly: "Lord Duke Long, the chance is rare, I recommend that you act personally to eliminate this Fang Yuan now!"

Duke Long shook his head: "Fang Yuan is nothing but a troublemaker, repairing fate Gu is the important thing now. It is not time for me to act."

"Lord Duke Long…" Fairy Zi Wei wanted to speak more but suddenly, her expression changed.

At this instant, Central Continent's areas, especially those that were holding refinement competitions, were targeted with Gu Immortal level attacks.

In fact, not only refinement competition locations, even some famous resource points in Central Continent were attacked by Gu Immortals, they were looted.

"Even Infallible blessed land is being attacked!" Fairy Zi Wei's expression was grim, she could not believe it: "There are actually so many Gu Immortals targeting us?"

Chapter 1700: Rumors Become Tigers

Fang Yuan floated in the air, it looked like he was staying motionless amidst a blizzard, soon, thick white snow gathered on his body.

But looking from afar, it seemed like he was covered in a thick fox skin coat.

This was the modified time path killer move, winter coat!

Fang Yuan had many defensive killer moves, the strongest was reverse flow protection seal, but Reverse Flow River was clearly dried up now, this killer move could not be used anymore.

Other than that, Fang Yuan had emperor yama, winter coat, bloodstained conqueror's robe, purple thought light shield, hair armor, lion fur armor, divination tortoise transformation, ghost official garment, and other defensive methods.

Hair armor and lion fur armor were mortal killer moves, even though Fang Yuan had used them for some time, they were eliminated long ago.

Purple thought light shield was Purple Mountain True Monarch's method, it had defended against Duke Long's fists in battle earlier, it was quite useful. But Fang Yuan only had this killer move and did not cultivate it, he lacked the crucial Immortal Gu.

Bloodstained conqueror's robe was originally Fang Yuan's method, it was used for some time. Even though the core Immortal Gu was now rank seven, a rank seven method was useless now.

Divination tortoise transformation was considered a defensive method, but similarly, the ancient desolate beast divination tortoise was useless in a rank eight battle.

Ghost official garment had a huge origin, being designed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, it was used to defend against wisdom path methods.

Emperor yama killer move which combined ghostly concealment, Soul Beast Token, and ghost official garment had incredible defense, it could be used in rank eight battles.

But its defensive was still lower than winter coat.

Emperor yama was a comprehensive method, it had both offense and defense, by using the yama children, it could even fight against a group.

Meanwhile, winter coat focused on defense, after Fang Yuan annexed Xia Cha's immortal aperture, his time path dao marks increased in numbers drastically to being his highest path, winter coat's power was greatly amplified.

And most crucially, after some modifications, winter coat's defense was even better than before!

While he could not use reverse flow protection seal, winter coat was Fang Yuan's new replacement.

Bam bam bam…

The three Central Continent rank eights attacked Fang Yuan furiously, he did not dodge, he used winter coat killer move to block all of the attacks.

"What killer move is this?"

"It seems like Xia Cha's winter coat…"

"How can this be? Xia Cha's winter coat is not like this."

The three rank eights had varying expressions as they conversed secretly, they were very shocked by winter coat's defense.

Next, they placed all their attention on Zhou Xiong Xin.

These three rank eights came from Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, but Zhou Xiong Xin was different, he was a recently awakened Heavenly Court member.

Zhou Xiong Xin had already activated his immortal battlefield rumor cage, in this environment, all other paths were suppressed, only information path was amplified!

Fang Yuan's winter coat killer move was suppressed, but the other three rank eights' offensive methods were also suppressed.

As the three rank eights looked at Zhou Xiong Xin, Fang Yuan was also assessing this immortal battlefield rumor cage.

Rumor cage consisted of many silver text and characters, these characters were large as horse carriages or small as ants, they weaved together into a huge ball, enveloping Fang Yuan and the other four rank eights.

Because there were gaps between characters, the round ball seemed to be connected with the outside world, it was not completely shut off.

Fang Yuan had a serious expression.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, his time path clone was bathed in the light of wisdom, he was trying to deduce the mysteries of this immortal battlefield.

But regarding information path, Fang Yuan was not skilled in it.

If this was a time path or refinement path immortal battlefield, Fang Yuan could use his time path and refinement path quasi-supreme attainment levels to deduce it immediately. But against information path, he lacked the attainment, he could only deduce it using the light of wisdom forcefully.

Undoubtedly, it was wise that Heavenly Court sent out information path Gu Immortal Zhou Xiong Xin to deal with Fang Yuan.

If this was any other Gu Immortal that Fang Yuan has met before, he would be prepared with specialized methods. But this was the first time Fang Yuan was seeing Zhou Xiong Xin.

Zhou Xiong Xin wore a white robe, he had a square face with an air of righteousness, his body was quite muscular.

Those who could become Heavenly Court members were elite experts among rank eights. Forget about the rest, just that rumor cage alone was incredibly profound, it could be activated rapidly and was the fastest immortal battlefield killer move that Fang Yuan had ever seen!

"Fang Yuan, since you are trapped, don't think of leaving alive. You committed so much slaughter, so many innocent lives died in your hands! Now, you will experience the bad karma that you have created!" Zhou Xiong Xin said in a righteous tone, his aura burst out as he used two immortal killer moves.

Immortal killer move — Malicious Rumors!

Immortal killer move — Rumors Become Tigers!

Instantly, the silver characters in the cage started to shine in a dazzling light.

The dense light flowed like water, moving in the air as it gathered and swirled.

Next, from the silvery light, silver tigers emerged.

The tigers attacked as Fang Yuan shot out like lightning, facing them.

Strength path giant hand!

Fang Yuan rushed to the silver tigers as he attacked, but the giant hand only lasted for a moment before it broke.

Fang Yuan's brows rose, the silver tigers had great battle strength.

Immortal killer move — Spring Scissors!

The jade green scissors flew out with great agility, wherever it went, the scissors snipped as tiger heads fell, tigers were cut into halves and their corpses faded into silver light that flickered and scattered.

Spring scissors was unstoppable!

Zhou Xiong Xin's eyes flashed with a different light, he thought: "It is different from our intel, after the battle for Red Lotus' true inheritance, Fang Yuan's spring scissors seems to be modified again, it has grown more powerful!"

Zhou Xiong Xin was an information path Gu Immortal, he could rapidly gather information about any change or unusualness.

"Spring scissors killer move had not been modified for hundreds of years in Xia Cha's hands, but Fang Yuan could constantly modify it? Is Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment level really so high? Or maybe his time path attainment level is very high, after all, this is a rank eight killer move, it is not easy to modify!"

Zhou Xiong Xin was secretly shocked.

Even though he was still under the suppression of rumor cage, spring scissors killer move still slaughtered countless silver tigers like they were thin paper.

But Zhou Xiong Xin did not fluster.

"The battle is under my control, slowly, you will see my power, Fang Yuan." Zhou Xiong Xin laughed to himself secretly.

A moment later, Fang Yuan frowned subtly.

"The silver tigers are endless, it is clearly one with this rumor cage battlefield, no matter how many I kill, they will regenerate!"

"And most importantly, these silver tigers are growing stronger!"

"Strange…"

Normally, methods like these silver tigers are meant to expend the enemy's reserves through advantage in numbers.

But these silver tigers were growing stronger at a rapid rate, it was far beyond normality.

Earlier, spring scissors killer move was unstoppable, but now, it seemed slow. Not only did the silver tigers grow stronger, they were much tougher and more agile now, they often managed to escape from spring scissors, causing it to miss its target.

At this time, the time path clone finally made some useful deductions.

Fang Yuan looked at Zhou Xiong Xin as he spoke: "So that's it, this is the unification of information path and human path methods! You are using the grudge of the whole of Central Continent's mortals to display this move? Similar to the people's accusation killer move earlier."

Zhou Xiong Xin's eyebrows twitched, Fang Yuan actually discovered the profundity of this move so quickly it was truly shocking.

"Since you found out, there is no point hiding it. Indeed, this move was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, it uses the will of Central Continent's people."

"Fang Yuan, you slaughtered so many people, everyone is furious. One mortal might be weak, but what about countless mortals? Their collective power is beyond your imagination."

"Thus, continue to struggle. You cannot defeat the unified will of every person, this is the bad karma that you gathered, this is simply just desserts!"

Fang Yuan was silent.

He started to attack rumor cage itself.

But before he found out the mysteries of this immortal battlefield, even if he used Luo Po seal, there would be little effect, he would be wasting rank eight immortal essence.

At the same time, somewhere in Central Continent.

"Fang Yuan is trapped, he is likely in a certain immortal formation or immortal battlefield. I can barely sense him anymore, our connection is about to be broken." Shen Cong Sheng said.

He was an Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortal, the first supreme elder of super force Shen clan, he cultivated sound path.

When Fang Yuan went after Eastern Sea's Dragon Palace, he had been hit by this investigative method unknowingly. Now, even though he was inside rumor cage, Shen Cong Sheng could still sense Fang Yuan's whereabouts slightly.

"Brother Shen's investigative methods are truly admirable." At his side, Song Qi Yuan said with a deep sigh: "Back in the days, I was hit by your investigative methods, it was truly a nightmare."

"Haha." Shen Cong Sheng laughed loudly: "We were still young, to think that you managed to steal the inheritance secretly, causing us to end up with no gains despite our hard work."

"It is expected that Fang Yuan would obstruct the Refinement Path Convention, he has deep enmity with Heavenly Court after all!"

"Indeed, even years ago, he was already fighting with Heavenly Court in treasure yellow heaven by exposing secrets of both sides."

"Heavenly Court wants to repair Fate, even if he is an otherworldly demon, he would not want them to succeed. Heavenly Court would have too great of an advantage after all."

The surrounding Gu Immortals also spoke, some had cold and indifferent expressions.

Taking a look, these were all rank eight Gu Immortals!

Song Qi Yuan, Qing Yue An, Shen Cong Sheng, Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, Shi Miao, and others, this was an unprecedented gathering!

"Alright, isn't this situation good? Fang Yuan is also a problem, with him resisting and fighting Heavenly Court, we will have less issues here. Hmm… Dragon Palace is nearby, there is no mistake." Shen Cong Sheng led the way as he moved ahead of the group.

It turned out that because Duke Long snatched the rank eight Immortal Gu House from these Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals, they had lost their face.

Thus, during this Refinement Path Convention, these people gathered secretly, they wanted to obtain Dragon Palace and salvage their reputation!

Chapter 1701: Killing Rank Eight!

A group of Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals flew along Central Continent's mountain ranges at a low altitude.

After Duke Long took the Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace by force, he caused Eastern Sea's righteous path, demonic path, and even lone immortal rank eights to work together.

"It should be here." Shen Cong Sheng suddenly stopped as he showed a suspicious expression towards the mountain below him.

This mountain was very plain, it was surrounded by mountains and was nothing special.

"This?" Hua Cai Yun frowned, shaking her head: "I did not find anything with my investigative method."

"Mm… but I feel that this mountain is different." Qing Yue An said.

"It is here." Granny Rong said with certainty.

The surrounding Gu Immortals looked toward her.

Granny Rong was a poison path Gu Immortal, how did she have such incredible attainment in investigative methods?

"There is an illusion formation here." Song Qi Yuan's eyes shined with crystal light as he spoke.

"But we do not have any formation path member now." Hua Cai Yun added.

Zhang Yin laughed coldly: "Why are we hesitating? Let's break into the formation by force. Earlier in Eastern Sea, we were all wary of each other, that allowed Duke Long to succeed. Now, we have set an alliance, we will advance and retreat together, even if Duke Long comes, so what?"

"Hahaha, he is right, let's charge in!" Song Qi Yuan laughed loudly, attacking.

Boom boom boom!

Rank eight Gu Immortals had incredible methods.

In a chain of explosions, the illusion formation seemed to have shattered, it exposed the true scenery.

Below the mountain, there was a huge rock cavern, the cavern had natural dragon markings, it resembled dancing dragons that intertwined together.

Eastern Sea's immortals only took a glance before they lost interest in this cavern with dragon markings.

They flew into the cave and found that there was a huge hole below.

They flew along the path, going down.

After passing a long tunnel, light appeared before the immortals' eyes.

"This is a natural Earth Trench below the cavern!"

"This is not a new Earth Trench, it must have existed for a very long time."

"Is Dragon Palace at the depths of this Earth Trench?"

"Duke Long took away the Immortal Gu House, why did he put it here?"

Eastern Sea's immortals discussed.

The Earth Trench was unfathomably deep, it was completely dark and eerie.

Compared to the Earth Trench, they were too small, they were like insignificant flies.

Roar!

Suddenly, an intense gust of wind emerged from the Earth Trench, blowing upwards.

At the same time, the entire Earth Trench started to shake, the rocks along the cliffs of the Earth Trench started to fall.

The expressions of Eastern Sea's immortals changed, they felt a strong sense of threat.

The tremors started abruptly and ended just as abruptly.

More than ten breaths later, the entire Earth Trench returned to normal.

"What exactly is down there?"

"No matter what it is, it was able to make all of us feel danger, it is not simple!"

"I want to see what Duke Long is up to."

Eastern Sea's immortals were about to explore the depth of the Earth Trench when rainbow lights started to shine in the Earth Trench, a super immortal formation appeared and enveloped all of the Gu Immortals.

"They were waiting in ambush!"

"Such an amazing immortal formation!"

"Who is it?"

An old Central Continent rank eight Gu Immortal appeared before the Eastern Sea immortals.

He was wearing a gray robe, he was covered in a deep level of sadness all over his body.

Eastern Sea's rank eights were very knowledgeable, they quickly recognized this Central Continent rank eight expert.

"Oh? You are Wind Cloud Manor's Old Man Bei Feng?"

Old Man Bei Feng sighed: "Yes indeed, you have come here to attack Hidden Dragon Cave, it is very unwise. With me here, no matter what objective you have, you will not succeed."

"Hidden Dragon Cave! This is Hidden Dragon Cave?!" Many Eastern Sea Gu Immortals felt greatly shocked.

Hidden Dragon Cave contained the legendary immemorial desolate beast Di Zang Sheng, everyone knew that. But its location had never been exposed.

Old Man Bei Feng was originally able to become a Heavenly Court member, but because his beloved grandson Feng Chan Zi made a mistake, Old Man Bei Feng took the punishment together and they were tasked to guard over Di Zang Sheng in Hidden Dragon Cave.

Because of specific reasons, Duke Long placed the rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace here. These Eastern Sea Gu Immortals searched for clues and found their way to Hidden Dragon Cave.

"Puff!" Old Man Bei Feng's body shook as he activated the super immortal formation.

This super immortal formation was able to trap Di Zang Sheng, it was naturally very powerful, Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals were all swept by its power, their eyes blurred as they found that they were trapped in a huge space after regaining their vision, isolated from each other.

At the next moment, Eastern Sea's immortals struck and attacked their surroundings.

A rank eight battle was about to begin!

At the same time, immortals acted all over Central Continent.

Mountain Tortoise Valley.

Inside the valley, walls were steep, almost perpendicular to the ground.

Demonic path Gu Immortal Nine Ghost Finger sneaked in here.

He looked at the mountain tortoises here with a look of desire.

There were many mountain tortoises, they filled the entire valley, among them were gigantic desolate beast mountain tortoises.

"Mountain tortoises that are rare in Eastern Sea are common in Southern Border and Central Continent. This Mountain Tortoise Valley is the largest mountain tortoise breeding ground in Central Continent. Hehehe."

Nine Ghost Finger laughed smugly to himself.

This was originally the resource point governed by Spirit Butterfly Valley of the ten great ancient sects. But now, the Gu Immortal guarding this place was drawn away to protect a certain Refinement Path Convention area.

"However, even though the person left, they left behind warning methods." Nine Ghost Finger did not enter abruptly, he stayed outside and investigated for a long time, realizing the truth.

This was an earth path immortal killer move.

"Let me see how to unravel this method!" Nine Ghost Finger's eyes shined brightly, his ten fingers quickly deduced and they flew all over the place.

His fingers moved fast, alternating between real and phantom, there were originally ten fingers but soon, only nine finger phantoms were left.

Nine Ghost Finger's wisdom path inheritance was very unique.

The missing finger represented the 'one in the Great Dao' that fled, it was the most profound heavenly secret[1].

Nine Ghost Finger only secondarily cultivated wisdom path, he primarily cultivated soul path. His fingers danced as he muttered phrases to himself.

The more he deduced, the more his eyes shined with brilliance.

And meanwhile, countless li away in Moonlight Mound, a serious battle ensued.

Rank seven lone immortal Xie Bao Shu floated in the sky, his aura was grand as he attacked Moonlight Mound with a barrage of attacks.

He was dressed in a blue robe, he looked like a scholar with a handsome jade face, he had the appearance of a good looking young man.

His opponent, the female immortal guarding Moonlight Mound, was in a sad state, she said furiously: "Xie Bao Shu, you are not worthy of being a famous lone immortal of Eastern Sea, you actually acted so demonically and tried to plunder Moonlight Mound! Go and steal from the ten great ancient sects if you dare, we are both lone immortals yet you still target me! Back then, I bought your year Gu, I had given you business!"

Xie Bao Shu sighed: "Fairy Yue Hua, unless I had no choice, I would not do this. My year Gu business has flopped, I need another source of income. If you can give me half of your moonlight mushrooms, I will leave now without question."

The Central Continent female immortal wanted to cough out blood: "I had spent thirty years nurturing my moonlight mushrooms and put in huge effort, you want half of them now, you are dreaming! Even if I cannot defeat you, you will not have them, before I escape, I will destroy the entire Moonlight Mound!"

"Can you?" Suddenly, a soft whisper was heard behind the Central Continent female immortal.

"Ambush!" The female immortal was very shocked, someone had actually sneaked behind her without her noticing.

"Who?!" The female immortal wanted to turn around and check but at the next moment, her vision went dark as she fainted.

You Xian Zi stood above Moonlight Mound as he looked at the Central Continent female immortal, before turning to Xie Bao Shu with a smile.

You Xian Zi specialized in theft path, he was the Gu Immortal most skilled at collecting Earth Trench black oil in Eastern Sea. His appearance was ugly and he looked like a lecher, but he was best friends with Xie Bao Shu.

Xie Bao Shu came to Central Continent for resources, You Xian Zi naturally came to help.

Inside rumor cage.

Fang Yuan shouted as he unleashed immortal killer move myriad dragon.

Myriad dragons flew and fought against the countless silver tigers.

At once, dragons and tigers fought, there were beautiful silver sparkles when they fought, amidst deep killing intent.

After a few breaths of time, the dragons fell in numbers, they were not the tigers' match.

Fang Yuan's face was grim as he continued to activate myriad dragon, holding his own.

"Lord Zhou Xiong Xin's methods are truly powerful!

"This combination is amazing, using rumor cage, malicious rumors, and rumors become tigers, his battle strength is increasing endlessly."

"The longer this drags on, the more disadvantage it is for Fang Yuan. But he is in a desperate situation, he can no longer escape."

The three Central Continent rank eights watched by the side, guarding the formation from a corner.

Zhou Xiong Xin alone was able to suppress Fang Yuan.

Any Heavenly Court Gu Immortal would have incredible talent, they were genius experts.

"Normally, I only have upper-tier rank eight battle strength, I am inferior to Li Huang. But with my information path advantage, using Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's killer move and borrowing the wills of Central Continent's countless humans, my battle strength will continue to grow."

"At this rate, I will eventually kill Fang Yuan through attrition!"

Even though Zhou Xiong Xin had the advantage, he did not become careless.

Even though he had just woken up, a huge amount of information had allowed him to gain a deep understanding of Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan's great strength, craftiness, and threat was deeply etched into Zhou Xiong Xin's mind.

"Information path and human path… Heavenly Court truly has deep foundations, by just sending a counter, I am in deep trouble."

Fang Yuan looked at Zhou Xiong Xin as he sighed to himself.

The enemy did not expose any weaknesses, they were very vigilant against Fang Yuan and used all sorts of investigative methods, any sort of commotion would be detected, Fang Yuan's countless battle tactics could not be used.

Fang Yuan had become rank eight for a very short period of time, he was reliant on reverse flow protection seal and Luo Po seal, and others to stabilize his battle strength at upper-tier rank eight.

In earlier fights, he was either in the five regions' regional walls, five regional mountain range, or the River of Time, Fang Yuan could use the environment or other people to his advantage, shortening the difference in strength between him and the enemies.

But now, he was deep in Central Continent, he was countered by a true rank eight great expert.

In terms of information path, he had too shallow attainment. Human path was worse.

"Forget it, the probing ends here, it is time to use my territorial advantage." Fang Yuan's lips moved as he exposed a crafty smile.

At the next moment, his ambush was activated.

Rumble!

A huge formation activated in the outer world of Central Continent.

Rumor cage was like an egg, it was smashed by the terrifying force!

"Why is there a formation here?!" Central Continent's four immortals were shocked and furious.

"Make a guess?" Fang Yuan laughed heartily, turning into the immemorial year monkey as he jumped towards Zhou Xiong Xin, punching with his fist.

Rumor cage broke, the backlash made Zhou Xiong Xin spat out mouthfuls of blood.

Time path method activated, time was slowed in the surroundings, Zhou Xiong Xin could not dodge in time, he was hit by Fang Yuan's fist as he crashed to the ground.

"Quick, save Lord Zhou Xiong Xin!"

"Let's attack together!!"

The other three Gu Immortals charged at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly, the formation activated again, stalling the three rank eights for a breath of time.

Using this chance, Fang Yuan's huge body descended as he landed before Zhou Xiong Xin who was like a rag doll.

Immortal killer move — Spring Scissors!

A huge pair of scissors was held in the monkey's hands. The blades were tens of feet long, they stabbed into the soil on the ground.

Next, the huge scissors snipped, the ground was like a soft piece of tofu when compared to the sharp blades.

Crack!

With a soft sound, the scissors closed up as the two blades met.

Blood splattered.

Zhou Xiong Xin's head flew in the sky before it landed on the ground.

Zhou Xiong Xin had died!

[1] This has nothing to do with the novel so don't worry if you don't understand it. It's a common Chinese novel concept about one part allowing for variance. Back

Chapter 1702: Common Enemy Hatred

"More than half of Imprisonment Valley's southern thorns were stolen by a mysterious Gu Immortal."

"Red river beach's immortal formation was destroyed, the blazing red stones inside were all plundered by three Gu Immortals."

"Someone wants to steal Falling Heavenly River's primeval sand, he was forced away by Heaven's Envy Manor's immortal killer move that was left behind."

…

Fairy Zi Wei took command in Heavenly Court, observing the situation of the entire Central Continent, all of these news made her frown more tightly.

She was furious.

The huge Central Continent had abundant resources and talents, Heavenly Court's leaders and Central Continent's ten great ancient sects had worked effortlessly for countless generations to create this prosperity.

But now, because of these thieves, it was a huge mess.

Meanwhile, Duke Long sat in his seat and listened to Fairy Zi Wei report the disastrous news, his face was extremely calm.

"No matter, so what if we lose some resources? They are just tiny problems." Duke Long said as he shut his eyes, resting as his arm supported his chin.

Fairy Zi Wei breathed in deeply, telling herself to calm down but at the next moment, her eyes widened as she said angrily: "Fang Yuan has already escaped, three of our Central Continent rank eights were injured, while senior Zhou Xiong Xin… he was killed by Fang Yuan!"

"Oh?" A sharp light flashed in Duke Long's eyes, he stopped resting as he sat up straight, saying: "Zhou Xiong Xin was specially chosen to fight Fang Yuan, he had the greatest strength among them but was actually killed by Fang Yuan while the rest escaped with injuries, there must be a reason. Where is the battle report?"

"Here." Fairy Zi Wei handed an information path Gu worm to Duke Long.

The battle report was very detailed, because other than Zhou Xiong Xin, the other three Central Continent rank eights were alive.

After seeing the report, the hall went silent.

Long after, Fairy Zi Wei said: "I originally thought that Fang Yuan killed senior Zhou Xiong Xin using Luo Po seal, to think that the killer move used was spring scissors."

"According to this intel, spring scissors was modified again. And most importantly, when Fang Yuan transformed into the immemorial year monkey, his battle strength has broken through to the peak of rank eight!"

Saying so, Fairy Zi Wei sighed deeply.

She had known that Fang Yuan was a threat long ago. If he was allowed to grow freely, he would become a huge problem.

Fairy Zi Wei had expected this to happen, but she did not expect that this day would come so quickly!

"How long has Fang Yuan become a Gu Immortal? In just the blink of an eye, he became rank eight. And with another blink, he reached the peak of rank eight, even my battle strength is only at upper-tier rank eight level."

At once, Fairy Zi Wei felt a little dejected.

Duke Long looked at Fairy Zi Wei as he said slowly in a low tone: "Zi Wei, don't look down on yourself, Fang Yuan grew rapidly not just because of his talent, he also had external help. He was chosen by Red Lotus Demon Venerable and obtained Spring Autumn Cicada. He also got Spectral Soul's true inheritance and inherited Shadow Sect. He even has ghostly concealment, that is part of Thieving Heaven's true inheritance. And don't forget, with the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, how many benefits did Fang Yuan get from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?"

"We are already paying a lot of attention to him, your measures were not wrong. The reason why we failed was not just because of Fang Yuan, but also because of the forces affecting him. We are not eliminating Fang Yuan alone, we are also contesting the forces that surround him.".

"These are either Immortal Venerables or Demon Venerables, they were the reason Fang Yuan could grow to this extent."

Fairy Zi Wei heard this and showed a shameful expression: "I had lost my cool and stability, thank you for the reminder, Lord Duke Long."

Duke Long smiled faintly: "I am not consoling you, this is just a fact. However, even though Fang Yuan has peak rank eight battle strength, as long as he is not rank nine, he cannot overturn our Heavenly Court. Zhou Xiong Xin's death was clearly reported, it was because Fang Yuan used an immortal formation to destroy rumor cage."

"Fang Yuan is crafty and vicious, he purposely stalled for time and made rumor cage stronger with the will of Central Continent's people, far beyond its original capabilities. By destroying it afterwards, Zhou Xiong Xin suffered immense backlash that he could not endure, causing him to be heavily injured."

"Even though the remaining three rank eights tried to help immediately, Fang Yuan was prepared and used the formation to disrupt them. By turning into the immemorial year monkey and gaining peak rank eight battle strength, he caught everyone off-guard and killed Zhou Xiong Xin."

"Fang Yuan had always been pretending to be weak, using rumor cage, he harmed our Gu Immortal. Even though Zhou Xiong Xin was very vigilant, he still fell for Fang Yuan's trap."

"Actually, if both sides fought fairly, even if Fang Yuan had peak rank eight battle strength, he could not kill Zhou Xiong Xin. The battle afterwards could prove this point, our three rank eights fought together and retreated, Fang Yuan could not retain them."

Fairy Zi Wei nodded continuously, Duke Long's analysis was the same as hers, she agreed: "There is no strongest Immortal Gu, only strongest Gu Immortal. Fang Yuan has grown fully now, he has powerful methods and vicious plans, he is also ruthless and achieves outstanding results. Right now, he has peak rank eight battle strength, our arrangements earlier were all disrupted, should we send Li Huang to deal with him?"

Duke Long shook his head: "Li Huang must continue to guard the Refinement Path Convention. Restoring Fate is the most important goal, we cannot divert anyone away from that objective. Even if we make Li Huang go after Fang Yuan, he has Fixed Immortal Travel. Even if teleportation fails, Fang Yuan would still want to waste Li Huang's time. After all, he is not the only person who wants to disrupt the restoration of Fate, we cannot fumble at this moment."

"Yes, Lord Duke Long." Fairy Zi Wei had regained her calm already.

Even though Duke Long was not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he was in charge of Heavenly Court, his disposition was extraordinary, he was like a huge pillar stabilizing and holding up the entire situation.

Let alone peak rank eight battle strength, even if Fang Yuan was a pseudo-Immortal Venerable with the same strength as Duke Long, so what?

Duke Long believed that with Heavenly Court's foundation, they would definitely be able to repair fate Gu. Even if Fang Yuan caused much trouble, as long as he was not a rank nine venerable, he could not change the situation!

Duke Long was most concerned about the progress of the Refinement Path Convention.

He looked at the other person in the hall, asking: "Lord Zheng Yuan, how has the activation of common enemy hatred killer move gone?"

The person in question was an old man, he had many wrinkles on his face, he was thin and dry like a stick, he was truly resembling a man about to step into his grave.

He sat on a stone bench and was curled up due to his hunchback. He breathed slowly and lightly, his aura was so weak that it would not be strange if he died now.

But his seniority surpassed Duke Long, even though he had rank seven cultivation level, he was a member of Heavenly Court.

He was Old Man Zheng Yuan.

Because of fate Gu's restoration, he had woken up from the immortal graveyard.

Normally speaking, Heavenly Court only recruited rank eight Gu Immortals, and those had to be elites among elites. But Old Man Zheng Yuan only had rank seven cultivation level, yet he was acknowledged and recruited into Heavenly Court.

The most important reason was because Old Man Zheng Yuan cultivated a special path — human path!

The concept of human path had existed from very long ago.

It originated from the person who everyone living in this world knew, Ren Zu.

The <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> left behind by Ren Zu could be said as the greatest, oldest, and most mystical inheritance in human history.

<<The Legends of Ren Zu>> contained the profundities of human path, many great geniuses were able to gain some sort of comprehension from reading it, these gains were usually spectacular and shocking to everyone.

Heavenly Court thought of itself as humanity's leader, they had accumulated countless human path methods, these were one of Duke Long's greatest sources of confidence.

Old Man Zheng Yuan spoke in a weak voice: "Back then, when the eighteen variant human demonic immortals attacked Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, he was invincible in the world. After the eighteen variant human demonic immortals lost terribly, they were unresigned and tried to deceive the Immortal Venerable. Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was troubled and sat in the formation for three days and nights, thinking deeply and unable to regain his senses. After reading <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, he broke through the confusion in his heart, creating many human path killer moves such as countless lifeforms, people's united hearts, and common enemy hatred."

"I am merely a key to activate Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's remnant methods, I do not deserve the title of 'Lord', please address me by my name, Duke Long."

Old Man Zheng Yuan was very humble: "Right now, countless lifeforms has already been activated, the killer move common enemy hatred is also effective in the whole of Central Continent, now, as long as we can gather enough human will to a certain degree, we will be able to use the killer move people's united hearts."

"Good." Duke Long smiled: "This is good, with common enemy hatred, Central Continent's people will be united in their anger and hatred, the Refinement Path Convention will definitely continue smoothly."

Central Continent, Mystical Body Sect.

This sect was created by a supreme elder of Wind Cloud Manor, Wu Fa, it was also a competition location of this Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

After the initial selection, those that could compete here were all experts in Gu refinement.

There were thousands of Gu Masters in the square, each had their own space as they refined Gu.

The entire square was covered in a thick wall of light, rank seven Gu Immortal Wu Fa was staying here, protecting the place.

Half the time had passed, most Gu Masters had failed already.

Some people had soot on their face, some were pitiful and their arms were blown to bits, bloody holes appeared in their chest…

Gu refinement was a dangerous process, any distraction and they would suffer huge injuries.

Another Gu Master faced an accident during Gu refinement as he fainted on the spot.

The formation below the square's floor tiles activated, this Gu Master was teleported outside as healing Gu Masters gathered and quickly treated him.

This person had made a mistake while handling the Gu materials, the poison from the materials seeped into his body, causing him to faint.

Soon, he was saved and managed to wake up.

"Even though you woke up, your limbs are weak and your mind is fuzzy, you cannot continue with the competition." The healing Gu Master felt pity for him, he was not weak, many people thought he would succeed.

This person laughed: "So what if I failed? According to the great immortals, even if I fail in the competition, it will still benefit Central Continent! It will benefit the righteous path! Those demonic path immortals are trying their best to ruin our Refinement Path Convention, they killed so many innocent lives! Even though we are mortals, we cannot give up on resisting them. Participating in the Refinement Path Convention and keeping it going is our revenge against them!"

Even though his voice was weak, his content was firm, it felt like clashing swords.

"Good lad!" The healing Gu Master gave a thumbs up: "I think so too, those murderers are no immortals, they have no empathy at all. We must resist, we cannot let them win!"

Right at this moment, a change occurred in the square.

Two young Gu Masters stood up, holding a Gu worm in their hands.

One of them was Hong Yi, he shouted: "I succeeded!"

"Good, both of you succeeded, you will share the ranking of number one. According to the rules, you can get a small reward from our sect." Gu Immortal Wu Fa's voice resounded in the square, everyone started to envy them.

The two young Gu Masters looked at each other, they were neither too far nor too close to each other, one was at the center of the square while the other was at the north-east corner.

"Report your names." Wu Fa said, he did not show up, but upon inspecting these two winners, his opinion of them increasingly grew, they were both very handsome and had great cultivation levels.

"I am Hong Yi." Hong Yi said.

"My name is Ye Fan." The other young man also spoke.

Chapter 1703: Avoiding The Limelight Temporarily

White clouds moved beside him, winds howled by his ears, Fang Yuan flew rapidly in the sky.

A trace of blood was still at the corner of his lips, in the intense battle against rank eights earlier, he did not leave unscathed.

Especially at the end, after his plot succeeded in killing Zhou Xiong Xin, the remaining three rank eights decided to escape, they cooperated and broke Fang Yuan's formation.

This formation was not made by Fang Yuan, Shadow Sect had created it long ago using the natural dao marks of the area, it was a natural super formation.

This super immortal formation had great power, it was similar to the one that Fang Yuan used to capture Xia Cha and the rest.

This immortal formation was usually concealed without any exposed traces, Shadow Sect created it so that the organization Defy could have a base camp when the time was ripe.

Central Continent's ten great ancient sects occupied their own territory, they had the most resources. The righteous path, lone immortals, and demonic immortals were all desperately trying to survive between the cracks of these ten great ancient sects.

But the sect system was different from the clan system, they only focused on talents. Many cultivation geniuses did not lack talent, they lacked cultivation resources, it was the cause of their stagnation.

As time passed, these people naturally developed lots of conflict with the Central Continent ten great ancient sects.

Shadow Sect thought of this and secretly gathered the Gu Immortals who were unhappy with the ten great ancient sects, creating a loose organization that was very secretive, known as Defy.

Defy was similar to Zombie Alliance, it was a branch of Shadow Sect. This was similar to the ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court.

Shadow Sect had placed some hope in Defy, but unfortunately, it was not Fairy Zi Wei's match even though it tried to hide.

Right now, Defy was no more, Fairy Zi Wei held great credit in completely eradicating it.

Since Fang Yuan showed up and destroyed the competition locations of the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, he had also thought about possible Heavenly Court pursuers.

This super formation was his trump card.

When he realized something amiss, he escaped to this location without going anywhere else.

Zhou Xiong Xin used rumor cage killer move and trapped Fang Yuan, feeling overjoyed, but he did not think that this was Fang Yuan's ambush from the very beginning.

The super immortal formation did not let down Fang Yuan's expectations, when he used it, he immediately broke rumor cage's connection with the outside world, before completely crushing this immortal battlefield.

Next, the immortal formation even stopped three rank eights for a breath of time, so that Fang Yuan had the crucial time to kill Zhou Xiong Xin.

Finally, using the immortal formation, Fang Yuan fought against the remaining three rank eights, but the immortal formation had already expended itself, this kind of immortal formation created using natural dao marks had a weakness as well, the environment could be destroyed.

The three Central Continent rank eights knew this and managed to destroy the immortal formation.

The immortal formation was destroyed, Fang Yuan also suffered a backlash like Zhou Xiong Xin.

Immortal killer moves were like this, the stronger they were, the greater the backlash when they got broken, they were simply double-edged swords.

But Fang Yuan was mentally prepared, he was not caught unguarded like Zhou Xiong Xin.

The three Central Continent rank eights did not use this chance, they were bent on retreating.

Fang Yuan did not have an immortal battlefield or an immortal formation to obstruct them, they were able to escape.

He had peak rank eight battle strength, he could defeat these three people, but killing them was too hard. Unless he could trap them or make use of a rare opportunity like how he killed Zhou Xiong Xin.

Normally, Fang Yuan relied on Luo Po seal, spring scissors, winter coat, five finger fist heart sword, and other methods to maintain his upper-tier rank eight battle strength.

He worked hard to raise these many Immortal Gu, it was not for fun.

But when he became the immemorial year monkey, his battle strength would rise to peak rank eight.

The difference was because of his dao marks!

In the contest for the Red Lotus true inheritance, Fang Yuan neither won nor lost. In the Dragon Palace contest, Fang Yuan lost. But afterwards, heaven form did not disappoint, it finally found the hidden location of the crucial Immortal Gu inside Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

Fang Yuan had also used the dream realm to raise his transformation path attainment level during this period.

He first used familiar face to disguise himself before entering the grotto-heaven and using his theft path methods to steal all of the Immortal Gu inside.

Even though that Beast Calamity heavenly spirit was clear-minded, how could it compare to the crafty Fang Yuan?

At this point, Fang Yuan no longer had any concerns, he changed his identity again and inherited the Beast Calamity true inheritance.

The pitiful Beast Calamity heavenly spirit was completely deceived, even when Beast Calamity grotto-heaven got annexed, it did not discover Fang Yuan's true identity.

This Beast Calamity grotto-heaven was a crucial turning point.

Normally speaking, an earthly calamity gave a Gu Immortal two hundred and fifty dao marks, heavenly tribulation was seven hundred and fifty, grand tribulation was seven thousand two hundred and fifty, while myriad tribulations were even higher, at eighty-six thousand seven hundred and fifty.

These were just the average numbers, some calamities and tribulations were more ferocious and Gu Immortals would gain more dao marks for passing them.

Rank seven Gu Immortals faced an earthly calamity every ten years, while rank eight Gu Immortals faced a heavenly tribulation every ten years.

Rank seven Gu Immortals faced a heavenly tribulation every fifty years, while rank eight Gu Immortals faced a grand tribulation every fifty years.

Rank seven Gu Immortals faced a grand tribulation every hundred years, while rank eight Gu Immortals faced a myriad tribulation every hundred years.

One myriad tribulation gave eighty thousand dao marks, it was more than ten times of a grand tribulation, this was also the reason why rank eight Gu Immortals often suppressed rank seven, the difference in their dao marks was just too high.

Fang Yuan annexed Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, which had already passed one myriad tribulation. Even though the grotto-heaven's original owner, Beast Calamity Immortal died after the first myriad tribulation, the Beast Calamity grotto-heaven that he left behind passed many calamities and tribulations afterwards, it was not far from its second myriad tribulation.

That was to say, forget about all the other dao marks in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, just in terms of transformation path dao marks alone, it had more than a hundred thousand!

And Fang Yuan himself already had nearly a hundred thousand transformation path dao marks! He originally had fifty thousand, but he killed many Heavenly Court rank seven experts in the River of Time, he annexed a lot of blessed lands and gained a lot of dao marks from various paths.

Thus, after annexing Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, his transformation path dao marks reached two hundred thousand!

This number was terrifying.

Rank eight Gu Immortals who cultivate transformation path would need to pass two myriad tribulations in order to obtain so many transformation path dao marks.

Bo Qing was a rank eight Gu Immortal who had passed two myriad tribulations, Duke Long was too.

When Fang Yuan transforms into the immemorial year monkey, these transformation path dao marks would turn into time path dao marks.

Don't forget, after annexing Xia Cha's grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan had seventy thousand time path dao marks. In the River of Time, he killed the three Xunzi and annexed their immortal apertures, his time path dao marks surpassed a hundred thousand.

Two hundred thousand added with a hundred thousand, after becoming an immemorial year monkey, Fang Yuan would have a total of three hundred thousand time path dao marks!

What did that imply?

If a rank eight Gu Immortal cultivated time path without any special fortuitous encounters, they would need to pass a third myriad tribulation.

But after passing a myriad tribulation, they would be a rank nine venerable.

Of course, rank nine Gu Venerables would definitely have more than three hundred thousand dao marks, this was just a starting point.

Even so, in terms of time path dao marks, Fang Yuan had reached pseudo-Immortal Venerable level. Along with his rank eight time path Immortal Gu and many useful rank eight time path killer moves, his battle strength was to the extent of peak rank eight.

Earlier, when Fang Yuan fought against Li Huang, he used Luo Po seal and could not break through Luo Po seal's verdant sun flame cloak. But now, Fang Yuan became the immemorial year monkey, he was looking forward to the clash between spring scissors and verdant sun flame cloak!

"But against Duke Long, it will still be difficult." Fang Yuan's gaze was deep.

There were many things that influenced battle strength, dao marks were one aspect, Immortal Gu were also another aspect, the immortal aperture's foundation was another, and number of methods was also one.

Fang Yuan did not lack dao marks. He had three time path Immortal Gu, it was just passable. But in terms of killer moves, he was too weak, even though he modified spring scissors killer move multiple times and raised its strength, the core was unchanged. He only had these few moves.

As for Duke Long, Fang Yuan had witnessed his fight against Purple Mountain True Monarch, be it transformation path or qi path dao marks, he had at least three hundred thousand dao marks.

Duke Long also had more than three rank eight Immortal Gu for sure.

Duke Long's immortal killer moves were numerous and profound, especially moves like triple qi retraction, it was a divine technique that could not be guarded against.

Because of all these elements, Duke Long had pseudo-Immortal Venerable battle strength!

Pseudo-Immortal Venerable had the word 'venerable' in it, it was not easy to achieve.

Precisely so, Duke Long was able to obtain Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace in front of all the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, this showed how powerful he was.

Even though he got injured in the process.

Pseudo-Immortal Venerable was still not an Immortal Venerable, the difference between the two was night and day.

Fang Yuan did not lack confidence, he was filled with confidence in himself, but this was built upon his self-awareness!

He knew very clearly how strong he really was.

Thus, Fang Yuan was wary of Duke Long simply because his battle strength was not on par with the latter!

"This human path people's accusation killer move is getting stronger. Even though I have little understanding of human path, I can see that the situation is getting worse."

Fang Yuan frowned lightly.

He had deep wisdom path attainment that even Fairy Zi Wei did not dare to underestimate. The emotions of wisdom path Gu Immortals were usually not without reason, they were mostly premonition.

"I cannot resolve people's accusation using emperor yama. The more times I show up in Central Continent and the longer I stay, the stronger this people's accusation killer move becomes."

"But now, the real fight has not started yet, even though many incidents have occurred in Central Continent, they are just small scuffles."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan made up his mind: "Raising a troop just for a single battle, it is time to let them out!"

In the battle against Zhou Xiong Xin earlier, Fang Yuan waited patiently but did not get to meet Duke Long.

Now that the super immortal formation was destroyed, Fang Yuan had no confidence of facing Duke Long alone.

To be honest, Duke Long's refusal to show up was giving Fang Yuan immense pressure and threat, he had to conceal his traces and reduce the risks involved.

"Next, I will let Bai Ning Bing and the rest cause havoc everywhere. I should try and lay low now, this great battle has just begun!" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a cold light.

TL Note: This chapter is speculation from Fang Yuan's point of view and understanding, not necessarily established facts.

Chapter 1704: Chaos in Central Continent

Central Continent.

There was an untroubled island floating in the sky, Carefree Island, this was the territory of Grand Pavilion Sect.

A round of the Gu refinement competition was about to end.

The three Gu Immortals defending Carefree Island also relaxed.

One looked outside at the clouds as he stretched his body: "It is finally over, this is the most tiring experience I've ever had in guarding the Refinement Path Convention."

"Haha, that's true. But there is no helping it, that demon Fang Yuan is too vicious, many people from other regions are also holding ill intent."

"After this mission is over, I will treat you guys to wine."

"Oh? Your nine flow wine is very famous, to think that I would get to taste it."

"Hahaha, it is an exaggeration." The Gu Immortal who was praised quickly waved his hand but suddenly, his expression froze.

"Guh!" He had a shocked expression as his body turned stiff, he fell down onto the ground, dead.

"Be careful!"

"Enemy attack! His soul has dissipated!"

The remaining two rank seven Gu Immortals were shocked, they activated their defensive methods.

Next, they saw that the Gu Masters in the competition fell one by one, they had all died.

The two Gu Immortals staring with a furious expression as they watched, right when they were about to complete their mission, they were attacked.

"They are so vicious, to be actually attacking mortal Gu Masters!"

"Quickly come out, which demonic coward is it, you only dare to sneak attack?"

The two Gu Immortals shouted.

The competition grounds were in chaos, people continued to fall.

"You want to see me?" A smile resounded: "I will grant you your wish."

Amidst his laughter, Ying Wu Xie appeared.

"Demon, go and die!" The two Gu Immortals gritted their teeth, they moved and attacked.

Ying Wu Xie stood on the spot without moving, he smiled as he looked at the two with a mocking gaze.

The two Gu Immortals were still moving when their expressions suddenly changed, their speed fell drastically.

"We… we are already hit?!"

"But earlier…"

"What move is this?"

The two rank seven Gu Immortals fell on the ground, watching as Ying Wu Xie walked towards them.

Ying Wu Xie smiled, keeping the three Gu Immortal corpses.

"Lord sect leader wants your immortal apertures after all."

He gave a final glance at the competition ground, there was nobody standing anymore, it was a field of corpses.

A moment later, Ying Wu Xie flew out of Carefree Island, the entire island was filled with dead silence, not a single living being remained.

At the same time, at the upper stream of scale light river.

Hei Lou Lan shouted: "Obstructing me with a mere immortal formation?"

Before she finished her words, her aura surged and filled the world, radiating towards her surroundings, causing huge winds to gather and blow.

Boom!

An immortal formation was unleashed, the immortal formation that had its maximum defense put up was shattered.

Puff puff puff.

The Gu Immortals defending this place spat out blood as they suffered a backlash.

Hei Lou Lan laughed sinisterly as strength path phantoms appeared around her, charging towards the Gu Immortals.

Hundred segment forest.

Bai Ning Bing stepped on the snow as she walked slowly.

The green and lush bamboo forest had been frozen entirely, it was like a bug trapped in amber, unable to move at all.

The grassland was covered in thick snow, there was no vitality left.

On the competition stage at the center of the bamboo forest, hundreds of mortal Gu Masters were frozen into statues, not a person survived.

Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and Ying Wu Xie had been cultivating on the stone lotus island, after future self killer move was used on them, they could use their future self's battle strength, they became elites among rank seven Gu Immortals, ordinary characters were not their match.

Seeing this result, Fang Yuan was pleased. Having the help of future self, these three grew rapidly and had the qualifications to join this huge battle.

"These three are geniuses with exemplary talent, once their battle strength rose, they immediately made other rank sevens look weak. Now, it will depend on Heavenly Court's response."

Heavenly Court.

After getting the new information, Fairy Zi Wei's expression turned grim again.

She commanded Heavenly Court and spent a huge price to collect time path immortal materials from treasure yellow heaven. In the end, she did not manage to restrict Fang Yuan's growth, even his three subordinates had such great strength now.

After the information got to Duke Long, he looked at the scene of the battle as bright light shined in his eyes, he was visibly moved.

Fairy Zi Wei could not tell, but Duke Long knew at once.

He was silent for a while before saying: "Fang Yuan! I actually underestimated you."

Fairy Zi Wei was confused: "Lord Duke Long, what do you mean?"

"The reason why these three gained a huge burst in strength is because of killer move — Future Self." Duke Long said in a deep tone.

"Future self?"

"This was created by my first disciple. Back then, he used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth and lost his venerable cultivation level, to make up for this problem, he invented future self killer move." Duke Long answered.

It was now Fairy Zi Wei's turn to feel shocked.

Her brows were tight, she was in disbelief: "I have already inspected Spectral Soul's memories, the Red Lotus true inheritance that he obtained does not contain future self. This means that Fang Yuan already has one Red Lotus true inheritance? Otherwise, how could he obtain future self? The River of Time was clearly locked down by us."

Duke Long shook his head: "There is no point in discussing this anymore. It seems we need to pay close attention to Fang Yuan now, he might have some special methods in his possession…"

Duke Long no longer looked down on Fang Yuan.

Or rather, he did not dare to look down on Red Lotus Demon Venerable!

At once, Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan felt a heavy emotion.

The trauma that Red Lotus Demon Venerable created enveloped them again.

But next, Fang Yuan vanished completely, only Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and Ying Wu Xie attacked with countless victories, causing chaos in Central Continent.

"What is Fang Yuan doing?"

"Is he secretly saving up strength for a huge commotion?"

Fang Yuan did not act, it made Heavenly Court feel terrible. This was the same feeling as facing a notched arrow, they were worried about when he would shoot.

Fang Yuan was waiting.

But Duke Long never showed up personally.

"The situation is getting worse." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, feeling that the situation was bad.

Duke Long did not show up, even though Central Continent's Refinement Path Convention met with lots of obstacles, regardless of sacrifices, it still continued.

Especially when the competition was ongoing with fewer and fewer Gu Masters left, the number of locations also shrunk, Central Continent's members were no longer as dispersed, the strength at each location grew evidently.

Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan and the rest had to work together now, if they were alone, they could not destroy the competition grounds.

Longevity Heaven also did not show up in time for Fang Yuan.

At the start of the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, Bing Sai Chuan had contacted Fang Yuan, he wanted them to work together and destroy this Refinement Path Convention, to thwart Heavenly Court's plans.

But until now, Longevity Heaven had not responded.

"Shadow Sect and I alone are not able to stop this competition, unless another strong force joins us!"

Fang Yuan knew clearly.

Even though Shadow Sect killed many and obstructed the progress of the convention, as long as Duke Long remained unmoved, this competition would still continue with firm determination.

And because Duke Long remained unmoved, the other four regions' Gu Immortals felt threatened, they did not dare to act.

This was Duke Long's wisdom.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to be the vanguard. Even though he seemed to be winning greatly, the truth was that the situation was still under Duke Long's control.

From Fang Yuan's perspective, Central Continent's situation had not turned around.

What should he do?

After thinking over it for a long time, Fang Yuan decided to change his tactic, he stopped Bai Ning Bing and the rest from attacking competition locations, instead, they started to plunder resource points.

Central Continent had abundant resources and even more resources in storage.

For each location that Bai Ning Bing and the rest plundered, Fang Yuan would put up the video in treasure yellow heaven, for all other Gu Immortals to see.

This tactic did not work well for the first few days, even though Bai Ning Bing and the rest had great gains, Fang Yuan was not happy.

But days later, more chaos ensued.

Northern Plains' Sleeping Lady suddenly moved and attacked Combat Immortal Sect's formation, plundering a resource point completely.

Gu Immortals that resembled Xiao Hu Chi and Xiao Shi Rang attacked glass mountain range, completely emptying out the super force's territory. The three Gu Immortals that were stationed there died.

An immemorial immortal material that was en route to Immortal Crane Sect was attacked by a bunch of mysterious Gu Immortals midway, the immemorial immortal material was stolen.

…

Several days passed, more and more chaos broke out, it was truly a scene of raging flames.

All sorts of famous resource points were plundered, some were about to be robbed, Gu Immortals could be seen all over Central Continent, moving actively at every corner.

"Hahaha, the people's hearts are finally moved!" At a secret location, Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

His scheme was vicious, he made good use of others' greed. If he incited forces or Gu Immortals to attack forcefully and destroy the Refinement Path Convention, they would be hesitant.

But if he pushed them to attack and rob resource points, avoiding conflict with Heavenly Court in the process, it was hard for them to resist the temptation.

At the same time, these resources obtained would tempt the Gu Immortals further, their greed and desire would be amplified as time passed.

As for those Gu Immortals watching on the fence, how could they sit by and watch others plunder this many resources? Could they not feel anxious? After all, there was a finite amount of resources, if others got them first, they would not be able to obtain anything later.

Fang Yuan changed his tactic and gained great results immediately.

The whole of Central Continent fell into chaos, Western Desert, Southern Border, Eastern Sea, and Northern Plains Gu Immortals appeared consecutively, even lone and demonic immortals from Central Continent were also trying their luck.

"Fang Yuan… I want you to die a terrible death!" Fairy Zi Wei gritted her teeth in anger.

Duke Long sighed deeply: "People's hearts are not longer as they used to be."

Even so, Duke Long did not give up his plan, he continued to push for the Refinement Path Convention's progress.

Those competition locations were heavily guarded by many Gu Immortals.

It was because Heavenly Court gathered their forces around here that their resource points were relatively weaker now, people could plunder them easily.

It could be said that Fang Yuan's change of plans had been tailored to Duke Long's own tactic, it was a direct counter.

Duke Long's determination did not waver, even though Central Continent was a complete mess, he still defended the Refinement Path Convention.

His tactic had Fang Yuan grit his teeth, there was nothing he could do.

Duke Long refused to react to any of the interferences, it forced Fang Yuan to attack. But Fang Yuan would not act rashly, because he knew that he was not Heavenly Court's match, and right now, other forces had not entered the battle yet, if he acted too quickly, he would just end up as their stepping stone.

Thus, Fang Yuan continued to wait silently.

Chapter 1705: People's United Hearts

Central Continent, earth qi rock forest.

Poof poof poof…

A huge gush of earth qi surged out from the cave below the rock forest.

Rock pillars were erected one by one, some were small as bamboos while others were as large as ancient trees.

Western Desert earth path Gu Immortal Shi Gan Dang assessed the earth qi rock forest from afar, having a complex expression.

This earth qi rock forest produced a vast amount of earth path cultivation resources, one of which was round kun stone, it was something that Shi Gan Dang desperately needed.

It was a pity that this round kun stone had never been sold in large numbers before in treasure yellow heaven. Because this was the territory of one of Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, they needed this round kun stone themselves.

"In treasure yellow heaven, I had to raise the prices but the Gu Immortals still refused to sell it, they even made fun of me. Hehe, now now I can destroy this place and take all of the round kun stone away, I will be taking revenge!"

Shi Gan Dang breathed in deeply, his aura surged as he charged towards the clouds.

Immortal killer move — Heavenly Descending Triple Mountains!

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Three mountains crashed down from the sky, landing on the formation protecting the rock forest. A large amount of trees were directly crushed by these huge mountains.

Shi Gan Dang did not feel pity at all, he took several deep breaths as he ran around the area with a pale face, he kept all of the immortal materials in this forest including round kun stones in his immortal aperture.

Central Continent, spirit bank spring.

"Which rat dares to come after this place? I have already discovered you, why don't you show yourself?" The one guarding this place was an expert rank seven Gu Immortal from Ancient Soul Sect — Yang Feng.

He had broad shoulders and a thin waist, his spine was straight as a spear, his body was emanating a strong manly aura.

He had long green hair that stood right up, looking like it was piercing the heavens. His black pupils carried sharp piercing light in them, people could not look at him in the eye.

He wore a martial uniform and there was a brown belt around his waist, his wrists were also protected by two jade braces.

Spirit bank spring was not an ordinary resource, it was quite unique, Ancient Soul Sect sent Yang Feng here because they did not want to lose it.

Yang Feng shouted, a Gu Immortal slowly walked out.

He was an old man with a hunched back, he slowly walked while holding a cane.

Yang Feng snorted: "Old man, you are already so old, you should treasure your remaining days. Why are you courting death now?"

The old Gu Immortal chuckled: "I can't help it, I need some spirit bank spring water."

Yang Feng snorted coldly: "There is not even enough spring water for our Ancient Soul Sect's own supreme elders, how can we give you any?"

The old Gu Immortal sighed deeply: "In that case, I can only snatch some for myself."

Yang Feng raised his head and laughed loudly: "Old man, you are quite daring, you have the guts to fight me! Tell me, what is your name!"

The old Gu Immortal smiled as he said with deep meaning: "I have long forgotten about my name. But others like to call me Forgotten Daoist."

"You are Forgotten Daoist?!" Yang Feng's body shook, deep shock was expressed in his eyes.

Next, his expression became dazed as he asked: "Wait, what was your name?"

The old man was silent and did not move, he only smiled at Yang Feng.

Yang Feng was dazed as he frowned while looking at the old Gu Immortal: "Who are you? Why are you here?"

A moment later, after Forgotten Daoist took away the spirit bank spring water, Yang Feng watched as he left, before reacting: "Who are you? You are acting so suspicious, stand right there!"

After Forgotten Daoist vanished, Yang Feng looked at the dried spirit spring as he said with deep anger, shock, and suspicion: "Damn it, who stole the spirit bank spring water? I guarded it so deeply, how did anyone even steal it?!"

"Oh no, I need to report to the sect." But at the next moment, Yang Feng was dazed again: "What am I doing here?"

"Oh right, I took a mission to defend this spirit bank spring, I cannot let outsiders in!"

"Hmph, with me around, I want to see who dares to come here and court death."

Central Continent, within a mountain range.

A huge battle ended, Central Continent's Gu Immortals from the ten great sects left with deep hatred: "You better remember this!"

"Scram, loser." Xiao Hu Chi laughed coldly, turning to look at the person beside him with a cold gaze.

Beside him was a Northern Plains Gu Immortal.

He was so thin his bones could be seen, his skin was wrinkled and dry, sticking close to his bones. Veins could be seen on his skin, they were everywhere.

He was Northern Plains' demonic path rank seven Gu Immortal — Pi Shui Han.

Not long ago, Xiao Hu Chi and him both went after this resource, they collaborated and forced the Central Continent Gu Immortal who was guarding this place away.

Only the two of them were left, the atmosphere became very peculiar.

"Friend, how should we split the resources?" Xiao Hu Chi pretended to be polite.

Pi Shui Han snorted coldly, he said without hesitation: "You can also scram now."

Xiao Hu Chi was dazed before laughing from anger: "I am a rank seven expert of Western Desert's Xiao clan, who are you, you are truly shortsighted but your nature is very arrogant."

"You talk a lot of crap." Pi Shui Han had a look of disdain, he directly attacked Xiao Hu Chi.

Xiao Hu Chi's expression sank but he also attacked Pi Shui Han without any fear.

The two fought for over ten rounds, Xiao Hu Chi was slowly losing the edge, but at this moment, Xiao Shi Rang appeared from the horizon.

Xiao Hu Chi was overjoyed, he joined up with Xiao Shi Rang and fought Pi Shui Han together.

But after a moment, Xiao Shi Rang and Xiao Hu Chi were forced to retreat, they left with deep anger.

"Who is this person? For just this little amount of cultivation resources, he is fighting as if his life depends on it?" Xiao Hu Chi gritted his teeth, he was also a courageous person, a general of Western Desert's super force Xiao clan, but in battle, he saw how crazy Pi Shui Han acted, he was completely suppressed.

"If I am not wrong, he is Northern Plains' demonic path Gu Immortal Pi Shui Han." Xiao Shi Rang said plainly.

Xiao Hu Chi was dazed: "So it was a Northern Plains brute! No wonder… forget it, Central Continent has so many resources, we do not need to compete with such maniacs."

Time passed, earth vein tremors occurred, the five regions' regional walls continued to dissolve.

The fusion of earth veins caused much less commotion in Central Continent than the Gu Immortals that were going around plundering resources.

The huge Central Continent was originally filled with beautiful mountains and rivers, but now, it was filled with fire and smoke.

People like Forgotten Daoist who only took resources were still fine. But when most Gu Immortals acted, they would be like Shi Gan Dang, directly destroying the resource points, they were very vicious.

Several days later.

Heavenly Court.

"Okay, we have accumulated enough human will now." In the hall, Old Man Zheng Yuan spoke.

Fairy Zi Wei heard this and let out a sigh of relief, she became quite energetic again.

These days, bad news had been reaching her one by one, Central Continent suffered huge losses everywhere, Fairy Zi Wei felt immense pressure weighing on her.

"Oh? Then use it now, Zheng Yuan." Duke Long said with a plain expression.

Old Man Zheng Yuan nodded, he stood up shakily as a grand and vast aura surged out of his body!

Immortal killer move — People's United Hearts!

The accumulated human will was expended rapidly, almost none was left.

At the same time, the entire Central Continent's Gu Immortals, Gu Masters and even mortals became enveloped in a halo of light.

The halo flashed for a moment, it was like an illusion.

But Central Continent's people soon found something special.

"What is the meaning of this?"

"Such a mystical feeling!"

"I seem to be connected with the people around me, I can sense what they are feeling directly?!"

After the initial shock, people soon found out the profundity of people's united hearts, it could connect everyone's hearts together and allow them to feel each other's emotions.

The fear of being attacked, the sadness and hatred of having friends and family die, the worry towards one's own life, and the aspirations towards one's future…

Never had Central Continent's people been so tightly connected before in history.

"Who are you? Why do you hold such animosity towards us?!" At a competition location, a Northern Plains Gu Immortal was suddenly exposed.

He was like a torch in the darkness, his true feelings could not be concealed, everyone found out about him.

He had a handsome face and wore a white robe, he was thin and had a scholarly aura.

It was Northern Plains' rank seven demonic path Gu Immortal — Unfettered Scholar!

"Such an amazing human path killer move! Even though I concealed myself, I was exposed!" Unfettered Scholar suppressed his shock as he smiled viciously towards the people around him.

There were multiple rank seven experts guarding this place, they surrounded Unfettered Scholar tightly.

"You disguised yourself to attend the refinement convention, you must be after the success dao mark? Leave, if you leave now, we will not find trouble with you." The Gu Immortal leader said.

Unfettered Scholar laughed, saying to the leader: "So you really were here, I did not come in vain." He said so with deep killing intent.

The Gu Immortal leader was confused: "Who are you? Do we have any grudges?"

"Hmph, so you forgot already. I have not forgotten it! Back then, you exterminated my clan, today, as the last person remaining, I will take your life!" Unfettered Scholar burst out with his killer move, it was his signature method — Thousand Disintegrations.

An hour later, Unfettered Scholar left with an injured body, he flew into the sky while laughing and shedding tears of joy.

Nobody in the competition ground was left alive.

At another competition ground.

"Friend, please show yourself." The defending Gu Immortal spoke politely and warmly.

"Found me huh…" Southern Border secluded immortal Zheng Qing shook his head as he walked out of the square.

"I have no ill intentions, I just want to experience the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention. After all… this is likely the final one." Zheng Qing smiled bitterly.

He was a secluded cultivator in Southern Border, he had obtained a Genesis Lotus true inheritance by chance, he did not hold much animosity towards Central Continent.

The defending Gu Immortal nodded: "Through people's united hearts, we can sense your intentions. It is a pity that you cannot continue with this competition anymore."

"I understand."

"If you don't mind, you can stay here and we can interact with each other."

"It's fine." Zheng Qing shook his head, leaving quietly.

Some people wreaked havoc, some left peacefully, but no matter what, people's united hearts was very profound, it allowed them to discern who were the enemies.

The unstable elements hidden in the competition were eliminated, Central Continent no longer had any internal threats.

Duke Long affirmed his tactic, as he continued to press forward with it, the finals of this Refinement Path Convention started at long last.

"This is the final chance, why is nobody acting? What are they waiting for!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, he could not help but watch as Heavenly Court got closer to success.

But Longevity Heaven did not respond.

"It is time, let's move out!" At a certain corner of Central Continent, Wu Yong suddenly appeared.

Behind him were many Southern Alliance Gu Immortals.

Wu Yong looked around as he said: "Everyone, I do not need to explain the situation. We cannot let fate Gu be fully restored, otherwise, Heavenly Court's advantage would be too huge!"

"Follow me, let us destroy Infallible blessed land, let's take all the success dao marks and make Heavenly Court taste failure!"

"We will follow Lord Alliance Leader!!" The Southern Alliance immortals said together, they had high morale.

Chapter 1706: Southern Immortals' Aspirations

"Oh no, Wu Yong is leading a band of Southern Border Gu Immortals, they suddenly appeared near Infallible blessed land!" In Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei's expression suddenly turned to shock.

"Oh? They finally showed up." Duke Long said plainly, he still sat in his seat without any change of expression.

Fairy Zi Wei breathed in deeply, she frowned deeply, feeling a different kind of pressure.

Because Southern Border's Gu Immortals were very united in this expedition, they were different from those Gu Immortals from the other four regions that caused chaos. And most importantly, they targeted an important place, it was Infallible blessed land!

If Infallible blessed land fell, it would be a disaster to Heavenly Court. The huge price they paid to forcibly hold the Refinement Path Convention would be wasted as Southern Border's immortals intercept and steal their gains.

"Don't be flustered. We already expected Infallible blessed land's location to be leaked, for this reason, we have already set up a super immortal formation nearby. Right now, the initiative is in our hands, everything will progress smoothly." Duke Long instructed.

Fairy Zi Wei nodded respectfully, she used her method as the scene of Infallible blessed land showed up in the hall.

Next, she hesitated before transmitting to Wu Yong: "Wu Yong, don't forget that we had cooperated last time. If you want to continue being the Southern Border Alliance Leader, you should know what to do."

Wu Yong received news and snickered, he felt a sense of disdain in his heart: "The great Zi Wei, even as a wisdom path great expert, is nothing much in the end."

He did not even bother to reply to Fairy Zi Wei.

His entire concentration was placed on his killer move.

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Wind!

A dark green wind started to blow, sweeping everywhere.

Soon, the wind grew to become a huge tornado pillar, it charged forward with a thunderous roar, along the way, trees were uprooted, rocks were sent flying, it was truly unstoppable with unparalleled might!

Seeing that the wind was approaching with great power, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals defending the area sighed as they activated the super immortal formation.

Creak creak.

The halo created by the immortal formation was constantly eroded by the unlimited wind, it soon made creaking sounds, it was sharp and piercing.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals used the methods inside the immortal formation, but any move that tried to weaken unlimited wind showed little effect.

"It is useless, I have never used this move easily before because it would expend ten thousand of my wind path dao marks. But after paying this price, this wind is long lasting and can only be resisted by specific techniques." Wu Yong spoke, his expression was plain but his eyes flickered with a sharp and cold light.

"Such determination, such will…" Seeing this, Fairy Zi Wei who was inside Heavenly Court sighed from the bottom of her heart.

Wu Yong paid such a huge price to use unlimited wind, it showed his unwavering determination, nothing could change his mind.

Wu Yong had an ordinary appearance of a middle aged man, he had a strong body and sharp eyebrows, giving him a dark and hazy aura. Right now, he was standing in front of the immortals, he stood tall and proud, being a leader that had great disposition.

Fairy Zi Wei memorized his appearance in her heart, she realized that she had underestimated him.

Southern Border's Wu Yong!

A truly formidable person!

He had Wu clan's bravery and courage, but he was also able to control his own emotions and conceal them deeply. When Wu Du Xiu was around, he kept a low profile and reputation, even Wu Du Xiu underestimated him, only on her deathbed did she realize that her son had such methods.

When he first took her position, Southern Border was in chaos, other clans pressured Wu clan and they lost a lot of territory. Using his strength and Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, Wu Yong turned the situation around.

After the battle of the dream realm, Wu Yong took a risk and worked with Heavenly Court, he took back the Immortal Gu of the Southern Border immortals, he returned all these Immortal Gu and that action gave him great reputation!

In the Five Regional Mountain Range, he wanted to kill Fang Yuan but failed time and again. After that, even though Lu Wei Yin had the title of Paradise Earth's inheritor, he could not take down Wu Yong, he still remained as the Alliance Leader of the Southern Alliance.

Right now, Heavenly Court was at a crucial moment in restoring fate Gu, Wu Yong led all the Southern Alliance elites in this battle, he disregarded Fairy Zi Wei's threat.

Because he knew what the big picture was!

They could not allow Heavenly Court to obtain the complete fate Immortal Gu once more!!

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Unlimited wind continued to attack, eroding the formation, the defending Heavenly Court Gu Immortals tried all ways to stop it but they failed. This move was too powerful, it was Wu Yong's trump card, this was the first time he had used it. Not just Heavenly Court, even when Southern Border's Gu Immortals saw it, they were shocked and under their joyful expressions were wariness and fear.

Soon, a hole opened in the formation as Wu Yong waved: "Everyone, now is the time to risk your lives, charge in with me and kill!"

Southern Border's immortals entered as the defending Heavenly Court Gu Immortals became nervous: "They're in, quick, activate the second layer formation!"

Southern Border's immortals felt that the scenery changed, jade blue light appeared and turned into countless flying pink flowers, they flew rapidly and rotated all over the place, enveloping the Southern Border immortals.

A rank seven Gu Immortal stood up, he had a halberd-like beard, he was heroic and brave, his name was Tie Gan Ge, a pillar of support for Tie clan.

He had peak rank seven battle strength, against such a strong force, he felt no fear, he shouted loudly as golden light flickered on his body, a dense number of golden halberds formed.

"Go." Countless halberds rained down furiously and crashed into the torrent of flying flowers.

As they collided, the flying flowers and golden halberd both disintegrated into powder and fragments.

The formation's attack was rank eight level, but Tie Gan Ge actually held up against it, he did not fall into a disadvantage.

Formation path great expert rank eight Gu Immortal Chi Qu You was standing beside him, trying to deduce the weakness of this formation. In this attack, Chi Qu You was bound to be the most useful person.

A few breaths of time later, the golden halberds were slowly suppressed by the endless flowers, rank seven Gu Immortal Shang Que stood out.

He stretched out his palm as a bloody hole opened up, the strong suction force absorbed many flowers.

Yi Hei Ting growled, blue lightning sparks appeared on his body as he helped Tie Gan Ge with the situation.

Meanwhile, rank seven wisdom path Gu Immortal Xia Liu Pei stood behind Chi Qu You, placing his palm on Chi Qu You's back, using wisdom path methods to help accelerate his deduction speed.

After a while, Chi Qu You acted!

Professionals were specialized in different fields, using his methods, the formation became slow, the weaknesses that were exposed were evident even to Gu Immortals not in formation path.

Boom boom boom!

Southern Border's Gu Immortals did not intend to hold back, they immediately attacked with many powerful killer moves, destroying the second formation.

Southern Border's immortals progressed into the third formation.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were deeply shocked!

"With friend Chi here, what formation can stop us?" Wu Yong laughed loudly.

The remaining immortals had high morales.

Chi Qu You smiled bitterly: "My deduction method cannot be used easily, it expends my lifespan. But in this battle, I cannot hold back!"

Southern Border's immortals shook.

Wu Yong could not help but look at Chi Qu You, both could see each other's determination!

But soon, Chi Qu You started frowning: "I do not need to deduce this third formation, it is very simple and easy, the formation core is that largest tree at the center of the forest."

The formation was easily understood, Heavenly Court purposely did this, it was very difficult to destroy.

Because this forest was very special, it could eliminate the power of any killer move.

Each tree was made of holy burial wood, the most central formation core was immemorial desolate plant level.

If Southern Border's immortals wanted to destroy these trees, they would need to use their physical bodies. However, there were countless vines on these trees, they were not simple. Some were green dragon vines, some were lightning vines, and some were chainsaw heart vines.

The third formation was made using the dao marks of this forest. To destroy this formation, attacking other areas was useless, they had to destroy this holy burial forest.

Southern Border's immortals thought about it, they released the ancient desolate beasts and immemorial desolate beasts in their immortal apertures.

The beast groups charged into the forest and attacked the vines, blood splattered all over. A while later, half of the beasts were sacrificed, the remaining were dazed in the forest, while the last portion fought among themselves.

Southern Border's immortals had grim expressions.

"So this place also has seven star internal conflict grass, it makes these ancient desolate beasts fight each other."

"Even though immemorial desolate beasts are unaffected, they are obstructed by this beast digesting rotten qi."

This beast digesting rotten qi had dense poison path dao marks, it did not affect desolate plants, variant humans, or pure humans. It only affected wild beasts, it could make immemorial desolate beasts turn thin, their skin and internal organs would dissolve.

Southern Border's immortals failed in their attempts, Wu Yong was about to take out his Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building when someone stood up.

"Let me try."

The immortals looked over, this Gu Immortal had a bald head, he had muscular shoulders and body, it was Ba clan's rank seven Gu Immortal Ba Xiong!

"Even though I am not a strength path Gu Immortal, I cultivate transformation path, let me charge in and destroy the holy burial wood."

"However, I only have peak rank seven battle strength, I would like Lord Yi Hao Fang to support me." Ba Xiong said expressionlessly.

The immortals were slightly moved.

Ba Xiong only had peak rank seven battle strength, he was not a rank eight Gu Immortal, yet he was willing to take a risk that would kill him with any slight carelessness.

Yi Hao Fang looked towards Ba clan's first supreme elder Ba Shi Ba, seeing that the latter nodded, he used his method on Ba Xiong.

His reinforcement method was not just famous in Southern Border, it was renowned in the world, Ba Xiong immediately felt an unparalleled strength flowing in his body.

He flew out and used his killer move, turning into a giant as he charged rapidly towards the center.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were naturally not going to ignore him, they started to attack him.

Southern Border's Gu Immortals quickly helped to assist Ba Xiong's advancement.

Eventually, Ba Xiong was bathed in blood, his skin was torn and countless wounds could be seen as his bones became exposed, he had exerted himself in destroying the central holy burial wood at long last.

In just a few minutes, Southern Border's Gu Immortals had broken three formations!

"Next, it will depend on the rest of you." Ba Xiong was heavily injured, he had lost his strength to continue in this fight.

"Friend, you were courageous and fought a dangerous battle, no matter how this battle ends up, you will gain huge merits in our Southern Alliance, we will definitely reward you handsomely when we return!" Wu Yong said with certainty.

Ba Xiong smiled lightly: "I risked my life because I was moved by Lords Wu Yong and Chi Qu You, Heavenly Court had already gone overboard many times when they invaded our Southern Border, if they truly repaired fate Gu, what would we do?"

"That is exactly right." Wu Yong nodded.

He looked at the immortals around him, his confidence surged to ten times that of earlier!

Central Continent had people's united hearts, while Southern Border's immortals were unified in their objective, with such a grand force, what fortress could they not take down?

Chapter 1707: Heavenly Court's Crisis

Central Continent, Hidden Dragon Cave, grand formation.

Myriad dragons flew around, encircling Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortal Song Qi Yuan like a huge ball made of dragons.

"These ancient poison dragons are clearly made from the formation's power, yet they are so agile and act as if they are real!" Song Qi Yuan defended himself as he pondered.

He wanted to kill these ancient poison dragons, there was no issue with that, but even if he got rid of them, there were other obstacles awaiting him.

The tens of thousands of ancient poison dragons were formed using the formation's power, Song Qi Yuan had to destroy this formation to target their root source. Otherwise, even if he killed the ancient poison dragons, he would not be able to break out of the formation.

"It is a pity my formation path attainment is too low, even until now, I have not found any flaws." Song Qi Yuan gritted his teeth.

Immortal killer move — Perfect Round Light.

He used his defensive method as his body became shielded by a ball-shaped yellow barrier.

Regardless of how ferocious the ancient poison dragons were, they could not break this thin light barrier.

From this, one could see how deep Song Qi Yuan's light path foundation was. Unfortunately, his opponent was this super formation, he needed formation path understanding instead.

There were many Gu Master paths, like earlier when Fang Yuan was countered by Heavenly Court's human path and information path methods, Song Qi Yuan was also countered by formation path.

Even though rank eight Gu Immortals could usually mimic other paths, and Song Qi Yuan could use light path to mimic the effects of formation path, he was facing against a super immortal formation that Heavenly Court had paid a huge price to create, it was the grand formation that could seal legendary immemorial desolate beast Di Zang Sheng!

Song Qi Yuan, who could not find any flaws, could only defend himself while waiting for a chance to appear.

Inside the formation's control area, Old Man Bei Feng manipulated the super immortal formation as he observed the situation of the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

A young looking rank six Gu Immortal was beside him, it was Old Man Bei Feng's grandson Feng Chan Zi.

Feng Chan Zi looked at the images as he cheered: "Grandfather, this is great! These rank eight Gu Immortals are all trapped and unable to escape. We have made a huge contribution, we can definitely atone for our mistake and leave this cursed place. Grandfather, you can also become a true member of Heavenly Court!"

Old Man Bei Feng shook his head, he had a solemn gaze: "Grandson, you are not clear of the true situation. These rank eight Gu Immortals have not exhausted their means, most of them are unharmed. They are unable to break the essence of this formation so they chose to observe for now, waiting for reinforcements. Once they find any flaw, they would attack with unparalleled and shocking might."

Feng Chan Zi was stunned and frightened: "Then, then what do we do? Grandfather, didn't we seek reinforcements long ago? Why have Heavenly Court's reinforcements not arrived yet?"

Old Man Bei Feng was silent for a moment before he said: "How can we know what Heavenly Court is planning? We can only guard this place to the best of our abilities now."

After Old Man Bei Feng said that, the formation started to shake.

"What is going on? A rank eight Gu Immortal found out a flaw of the formation?" Feng Chan Zi was shocked.

"No, it is that Evil Dragon!" Old Man Bei Feng's expression turned pale all of a sudden.

Hidden Dragon Cave, it was renowned for sealing Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng. Right now, Di Zang Sheng was struggling, it wanted to get up, Old Man Bei Feng could not help but resist bitterly.

Di Zang Sheng was not ordinary, it was created from endless hatred, anger, and grudges, all these negative emotions in Central Continent's earth veins.

It was originally sealed and constantly struggled, if it succeeded, there would be a huge earthquake.

Old Man Bei Feng was guarding it, one of the reasons was to stop the Evil Dragon from causing huge earthquakes in Central Continent.

But now, Fang Yuan and the other regions' Gu Immortals rampaged in Central Continent, attacking countless lifeforms, a vast amount of grudges, hatred, and fear were generated.

Di Zang Sheng absorbed these emotions and gained a huge boost in strength.

When the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals attacked the formation, it was already alerted.

The crafty Di Zang Sheng held its patience and gathered strength, by causing a scene now, Old Man Bei Feng was caught off-guard.

Old Man Bei Feng quickly reacted and tried to use the formation's power to suppress Di Zang Sheng.

"After that old man Duke Long used this formation, it weakened by thirty percent. Right now, my strength has secretly risen by at least fifty percent, Old Man Bei Feng, if you escape now, you might survive. Otherwise, when I destroy this formation, I will tear your corpse to pieces!" Di Zang Sheng roared, its voice was thunderous and caused tremors in this huge Earth Trench.

"Don't even think about it!" Old Man Bei Feng had a grim expression but his determination did not waver.

"I found a flaw!" In a formation space, Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Yue An stared with opened eyes as his aura burst out like a volcano.

Immortal killer move — Mountain Suppression!

Bam.

A huge phantom mountain appeared out of nowhere, it struck towards the formation's loophole while creating loud sounds resembling wind and thunder.

Hidden Dragon Cave's super immortal formation had already reached its limits facing Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals and Di Zang Sheng, now that Qing Yue An attacked it, it was like a broken bowstring.

Puff!

The formation collapsed, Old Man Bei Feng suffered a backlash and spat out mouthfuls of blood, his face turned pale as paper and he was on the brink of death.

Crack…

Sounds of glass cracking could be heard, a huge portion of the immortal formation was destroyed, only the control area was left, it was still pitifully defending the final bit of territory.

Eastern Sea's immortals felt their vision shifting as they were all released.

"I can sense it, the rank eight Immortal Gu House is outside the immortal formation's core!" Shen Cong Sheng's eyes shined with bright light.

"Charge!" Song Qi Yuan laughed loudly as he moved.

Qing Yue An stayed behind to heal himself, he had suffered injuries in trying to destroy the formation. He was not a formation path Gu Immortal, he could not resolve it through formation path means, he had used brute force instead.

Di Zang Sheng roared in excitement, its voice was loud as thunder, it made all the Eastern Sea immortals' expressions change.

"Quick, destroy the control area!"

"I am about to regain freedom, hahaha!"

"Old man Duke Long, after I get out, I will tear apart your tendons and eat you piece by piece!"

Di Zang Sheng's voice was filled with hatred and rage, it sent a chill down all of the immortals' spines.

"Grandfather, grandfather, you must hang on!" In the tattered formation control area, Feng Chan Zi cried as he held onto Old Man Bei Feng. He shuddered as he screamed: "Why have Heavenly Court's reinforcements not arrived yet?!"

Old Man Bei Feng was still spitting out blood, there was a pool of blood beneath him now.

Both of them fell into a desperate situation.

Central Continent, Emperor City.

This huge city was made of Gu worms, it was known as the number one mortal Gu House in the world.

At the same time, it was also the largest mortal gathering spot in the whole of Central Continent.

The finals of Central Continent Refinement Path Convention would be held here.

Fang Yuan was high in the sky, covered by layers of auspicious clouds, this was a luck path method meant to conceal his traces.

Other than that, there were more than ten immortal methods used by Fang Yuan on himself, he could barely defend against the investigative power of people's accusation.

He did not have human path methods after all, this effect was already satisfactory.

Right now, his gaze was focused on Emperor City.

"Nobody else has acted yet?"

"Longevity Heaven has yet to respond, damn it!"

Fang Yuan frowned deeply.

He did not know that Southern Border's immortals were already attacking Infallible blessed land with great morale. Meanwhile, in Hidden Dragon Cave, Eastern Sea's immortals had also broken the formation, only the core was left.

"I cannot let Heavenly Court repair fate Gu fully. I will destroy this Emperor City and kill all of the Gu Masters that are in this final competition!"

Fang Yuan ordered, an Immortal Gu House crashed down like a meteor.

The Immortal Gu House contained Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, Ying Wu Xie, and Qi clan's Gu Immortals. It could be said to contain almost all of Fang Yuan's subordinates now!

"Who dares to attack us, I will kill all of you!" Li Huang's voice resounded, he was the rank eight expert tasked to guard this place!

As he said that, Immortal Gu Houses started to appear, revolving around Emperor City like planets moving around the sun.

Fang Yuan sighed to himself: "My Immortal Gu House was made using Bai Xiang grotto-heaven's Thirty-three Heavenly Halls, along with the place where the killer move heaven form was stored, I also added in some Gu worms to barely assemble it, it is likely not the match of these Immortal Gu Houses!"

Even so, Fang Yuan did not ask them to retreat.

He had expected this situation, but there was no choice, time was tight, he had to do something!

Fang Yuan made up his mind, when Bai Ning Bing and the rest are unable to continue, he would show up personally.

As expected, Bai Ning Bing and the rest were attacked by many Immortal Gu Houses, they were suppressed from the start of the battle.

Heavenly Court placed a huge line of defense here, it was simply ridiculous.

A moment later, the Immortal Gu House that Bai Ning Bing and the rest were in became extremely damaged, they were soon to be defeated.

Fang Yuan sighed, he was about to enter the battle when his expression froze, he looked towards another direction.

Several rank eight Gu Immortals appeared, they were followed by several Immortal Gu Houses.

"These are Western Desert's rank eight Gu Immortals, and the Immortal Gu Houses of super forces!" Fang Yuan's heart jumped, he showed joy on his face.

Heavenly Court.

"Western Desert and Southern Border's main forces have arrived." Fairy Zi Wei sighed: "Actually, if not for the fusion of earth veins, the regional walls would still be thick, our Heavenly Court will definitely not face a coordinated attack of this degree!"

She was right.

Precisely because the great era was impending, the five regions were becoming one as the regional walls vanished, these four other regions felt a strong sense of threat.

Central Continent had the greatest strength, this was publicly recognized since ancient times.

Right now, Heavenly Court wanted to repair fate Immortal Gu, this was adding fuel to the fire, the other four regions' Gu Immortals had to stop them.

"The strongest group has not arrived yet." Duke Long said plainly.

"Yes." Fairy Zi Wei frowned: "Only several people from Northern Plains have arrived, their main force has not shown up at all. Fang Yuan is also not present, considering the battle in the River of Time earlier, he might likely join forces with Bing Sai Chuan again!"

Saying so, Fairy Zi Wei gritted her teeth: "Let me deduce with all of my strength again."

Duke Long was about to nod when his expression suddenly changed, he looked afar: "No need, they have arrived."

At the next moment, Fairy Zi Wei looked with deep anger as a rainbow fog appeared in the sky of Heavenly Court, rank eight Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar burst out of it.

"These Northern Plains brutes! They, they are too daring, how dare they attack my Heavenly Court directly?!" Fairy Zi Wei was so angry her body was shaking.

Old Man Zheng Yuan who was at the side became speechless.

Duke Long laughed loudly, standing up: "Indeed, this is the character of Northern Plainsmen."

Chapter 1708: Emperor City Battlefield

Central Continent, Emperor City.

"This is the Immortal Gu House that master told me about?" Ye Fan had made it to the finals competition, he looked at the sky with deep shock.

The other participating Gu Masters were mostly the same.

"These Immortal Gu Houses are usually the foundation of a super force, to think that so many would appear. I'm afraid that even after the regional walls vanish and the earth veins become one, during the five regions chaotic war, there would not be such a battle." Ye Fan had a realization.

At this time, a voice sounded beside Ye Fan: "Brother Ye, we can finally compete this time and determine the winner!"

Ye Fan diverted his gaze as he smiled and thought: "Master ordered me to join this Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, to think that I would meet such a talented person. Even if I lose in the competition later, it would be a great experience. This sworn brother is my greatest gain!"

Friends are often made after a fight, Hong Yi and Ye Fan had emerged victorious in the previous few rounds, they naturally became acquainted.

After some conversations, both developed a bond with each other, after a drinking competition, they decided to become sworn brothers.

Hong Yi continued: "This Refinement Path Convention is unprecedented, let those Gu Immortals fight in the sky, we have our own business to attend to."

"Thank you for the concern Brother Yi, I understand." Ye Fan knew about Hong Yi's kind intentions, he expressed his gratitude before concentrating on the final competition.

Outside Emperor City, Central Continent had many Immortal Gu Houses of varying ranks, they were distributed around Emperor City, surrounding it and forming a three layered defense line.

Outside the defense lines, there were many Western Desert rank eight experts and Immortal Gu Houses.

Other than that was the one controlled by Bai Ning Bing and the rest, Fang Yuan had not even named this Immortal Gu House that he assembled in a rush.

Fang Yuan originally wanted to show up, but after Western Desert's Gu Immortals appeared, he decided to stay hidden again.

Western Desert's Gu Immortals flew down along the Immortal Gu Houses, they continued to shorten their distance, causing huge pressure to form on Central Continent's side.

Even Li Huang who was commanding the situation felt a little pressured.

Even he who had great battle experience had not participated in a battle of such a huge scale.

Li Huang had participated in many chaotic battles involving Gu Immortals, but he had never seen so many Immortal Gu Houses in one fight.

Immortal Gu Houses were much rarer than Gu Immortals, normally speaking, very few Gu Immortals had their individual Immortal Gu Houses, only super forces had them.

A Gu Immortal alone could not gather enough wealth, ability, and time to create an Immortal Gu House. And an Immortal Gu House was not the most feasible for a single person's use.

For super forces, they needed a rank seven Immortal Gu House, in crucial situations, it could act as their rank eight battle strength!

Rank eight Gu Immortals were not common, the first supreme elder of many forces were only rank seven. At this time, a rank seven Immortal Gu House could help to stabilize the situation.

Immortal Gu Houses had their flaws of course, the methods were fixed and easily countered.

Thus, even though most rank seven Immortal Gu Houses could rival rank eight, they could not truly fight against a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Right now, the Immortal Gu Houses here were at least rank seven, they all had rank eight battle strength.

From a certain perspective, this was a battle that involved more than ten rank eight battle strength existences!

Both sides felt nervous and pressured.

But this was an unavoidable battle!

The atmosphere became heavier, when the distance between both sides shrunk to a certain degree, an Immortal Gu House that was in Central Continent's second layer defense line attacked.

This Immortal Gu House was small and delicate, it was an exquisite and small pavilion, there were countless bird cages hanging on it as birds chirped continuously.

It was one of Heavenly Lotus Sect's five Immortal Gu Houses — Canary Pavilion.

A large number of cages were unlocked in Canary Pavilion, flaming birds flew out rapidly, shooting out like a rain of flames.

These birds expanded midway and regained their original size.

They were large as horse carriages, their bodies were red and their feathers were flaming with great heat. Their eyes resembled molten magma, their chirping was quite unique, it sounded like flowing lava.

Ancient desolate beast — Molten Flame Bird!

"Be careful, these birds can self-detonate, they have great power!" Among the Western Desert group, a Gu Immortal immediately warned.

"Fire path ancient desolate beast, hahaha, let us face them." Amidst the laughter, an Immortal Gu House that resembled a waterwheel rolled out itself using those gigantic wheels.

A huge red light shot out of the wheel, it seemed to resemble ribbons that tangled the bird group.

The molten flame birds shrieked and tried to struggle but most were suppressed by the red light. A few self-detonated, turning into lava that were absorbed by the red light to become even stronger.

"What Immortal Gu House is this?" Central Continent's side was shocked, to think that the molten flame birds were so easily countered.

Western Desert's side was also shocked, a few rank eight Gu Immortals paid slight attention to this weirdly shaped Immortal Gu House, they had no information regarding it.

"Oh? Dong clan's Red River Wheel." Fang Yuan's eyes shined.

This Immortal Gu House was obtained by Dong clan from a mysterious inheritance, in Fang Yuan's previous life, it had displayed its great power and gained huge fame.

Normally speaking, if a super force wanted to research and create an Immortal Gu House, the process would take a long time. And in this process, a lot of clues would be obtained by other forces.

Only Immortal Gu Houses that were suddenly obtained like this would shock people.

Dong clan's Gu Immortals felt a little proud, they had made a great gain, obtaining these molten flame birds. With them, Dong clan's Red River Wheel would become even stronger, especially in terms of speed.

"Tit for tat." Fang clan's Gu Immortal shouted in the Immortal Gu House, releasing a large number of ancient desolate beasts, most were dogs and chickens.

Fang Yuan was even clearer regarding this Immortal Gu House.

It was Fang clan's Chicken Dog Coop, it looked like two buildings side by side, the left building was yellow and had a round plaque that had 'chicken' written on it, the right building was red and had the word 'dog' on its plaque.

Every Immortal Gu House was comprehensive in all aspects but also contained its own specialty.

Chicken Dog Coop and Canary Pavilion were both focused on enslavement path, the former enslaved chicken and dogs, while the latter raised canaries.

Both were also the same at rank seven.

The advantage of enslavement path was to engage in a battle of attrition.

A large group of chickens and dogs charged out as Central Continent's outer layer of defense reacted, using all sorts of killer moves on these chickens and dogs, a large number died.

But Western Desert's group also followed after and attacked.

At once, Immortal Gu Houses unleashed thunderous sounds and collided into each other, killer moves were unleashed as space was torn, loud sounds caused continuous tremors in this area.

Western Desert's advancement was very ferocious, soon, Central Continent's first layer of defense was broken, the second layer was also almost broken, but it barely held on.

"Western Desert's side has less manpower and Immortal Gu Houses than Central Continent after all."

Western Desert was different from Southern Border, Northern Plains, and Eastern Sea.

Southern Border had the Southern Alliance, the super forces were working very closely now. Right now, the whole of Southern Border had Beacon Towers everywhere, this was proof of their cooperation.

Northern Plains had Longevity Heaven leading them, in the recent years, Longevity Heaven had been recruiting lone immortals and demonic path members, they were trying to unify the entire Gu Immortal world of Northern Plains.

Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals had almost lost all their face because of Duke Long's actions of taking the Immortal Gu House. Because Duke Long offended all of these people which were all arrogant overlords of their own territory, this event caused them to band together instead.

Over at Western Desert, even though they knew that the issue of Heavenly Court repairing fate Gu was severe, only super forces participated in this. Fang Yuan did not see any Western Desert lone immortals or demonic path members.

"And Western Desert's super forces have reserved a lot of strength in this battle too."

"Fang clan is the one that has brought the most force."

"They brought Chicken Dog Coop, Inquiry Dock, and Fallen Flower Hall, I wonder if Divine Bean Palace has been repaired, did they bring it?"

Fang Yuan pondered rapidly.

Divine Bean Palace was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, if they brought it, this would be interesting.

But Fang clan knew that the chances were slim, even if Fang clan had control of Divine Bean Palace now, there was a good chance that they would leave it in their base.

In this Refinement Path Convention, even though Western Desert and Eastern Sea mobilized their forces, they were quite conservative, they were wary of each other.

"You go this way." Fang Yuan watched from above as he commanded Bai Ning Bing and the rest.

Bai Ning Bing and the rest moved the Immortal Gu House according to Fang Yuan's instructions and passed the second layer of defense, going straight for Emperor City under everyone's shocked gazes.

But Emperor City was protected by Central Continent's third layer of defense.

Two Immortal Gu Houses charged toward Bai Ning Bing and the rest from the left and right.

The palace at the left was grand and imposing, it was Heavenly Lotus Sect's Immortal Gu House — Yue Yang Palace.

The right garden was exquisitely built, it was grand with white jade tiles and oozing with cold air, there were faint dragon roars heard occasionally, this was Ancient Soul Sect's Immortal Gu House — Frost Dragon Manor!

Bai Ning Bing and the rest used the Immortal Gu House's killer move, the move was not powerful, it was destroyed by Yue Yang Palace and Frost Dragon Manor, they arrived in front of Bai Ning Bing and the rest.

Bai Ning Bing and the rest knew that their Immortal Gu House was inferior, they could only retreat.

"You can't retreat!" A Western Desert rank eight Gu Immortal shouted, if they retreated, this gap that was painstakingly created would be mended, their chance would be lost.

"Retreat!" Fang Yuan's orders were very direct.

This Immortal Gu House was not Frost Dragon Manor and Yue Yang Palace's match, Fang Yuan needed to preserve them. If it was destroyed now at the start, it would be a huge waste.

However, it was not so easy to retreat.

At the crucial moment, intense winds restrained Bai Ning Bing and the rest.

It was a seven-story tower, curtains were fluttering in the building, it was rank seven Immortal Gu House — Wind Sweeping Building!

This was one of the two signature Immortal Gu Houses of Wind Cloud Manor, it was paired with Cloud Passing Building.

Wind Sweeping Building and Cloud Passing Building were able to combine into rank eight Immortal Gu House Wind Cloud Manor, it had extraordinary power. In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, Wind Cloud Manor was once ranked as the number one Immortal Gu House for some time!

With Wind Sweeping Building restraining them, Yue Yang Palace moved rapidly like a meteor, crashing into Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu House.

Next, Frost Dragon Manor's killer move also landed.

Instantly, a portion of Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu House broke, pillars broke and a huge gap was created. A vast number of mortal Gu was destroyed, he also lost several Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan snorted as he showed up.

Emperor yama killer move!

With the use of great thief ghost hand, he directly took a bunch of Gu worms and three Immortal Gu!

Chapter 1709: Wu Yong Versus Chen Yi

Boom!

With a loud sound, huge changes occurred.

Wu Yong led the group of Southern Alliance immortals as he broke the fifth layer of the formation, arriving at the sixth.

In the sixth formation, there was complete darkness, there were no boundaries as far as one could see.

The Southern Border immortals were as small as ants in comparison to this huge space.

"This is a space path formation!" A Luo clan Gu Immortal suddenly spoke.

He wore a traditional Southern Border clothing, his skin tone was white and he had a cold expression, he was a Luo clan general famous in Southern Border, having peak rank seven battle strength.

His name was Luo Ran, he cultivated space path and had incredible attainment.

"Indeed, this is a space path formation." Chi Qu You nodded in agreement: "Let me make some deductions."

The immortals held no disagreements.

After entering a formation, using brute force was not wise. The best way was to let formation path Gu Immortals deduce the profundities of this formation, to target its weaknesses and achieve a greater result in doing so, saving effort in the process.

After some deductions, Chi Qu You said plainly: "I've already deduced most of this formation, it is likely the spaceless formation."

Luo Ran listened and frowned: "Even though I do not cultivate formation path, I've heard of spaceless formation, it is one of the most classic immortal formations of space path, it was created during the Remote Antiquity Era. Nobody knows who the creator was, this formation only has one ability, it can extend space and increase distance. After entering the formation, the distance of one step can be turned into a hundred steps."

Chi Qu You laughed: " Friend Luo Ran is wise, that is correct. But this formation had already been modified, there is a variation hidden inside it."

Someone asked: "What variation?"

Chi Qu You shook his head: "I have not deduced it yet, I can only sense it. But we can set off first, I can deduce along the way. In this situation, we can move ahead without concern, the spaceless formation does not have offensive power, it can only trap enemies and increase the distance between enemy and ally, to stall for time."

"Give me some time, I will be able to deduce the variation formation and find its weakness. During this period, if Heavenly Court attacks, as long as we can defend ourselves, whatever changes we observe will help me in my deductions."

Chi Qu You's suggestion was good, the immortals quickly set off and chose to move forward together.

Spaceless formation had no light, it was completely dark and endless.

The Southern Alliance immortals protected Chi Qu You who was at the center of the group, while Wu Yong remained as the vanguard.

"Look, there's something in front!" Yao clan's Gu Immortal Yao Tian Ze suddenly spoke.

The immortals quickly slowed down and got closer, taking a clearer look.

There was a huge green and white radish, it was large like a house, floating in the air as it remained motionless.

"What is this? It seems to be an immemorial desolate plant!" Yao Tian Ze asked.

Everyone frowned, this was not a common sight after all.

Wu Yong was silent, a flash of inspiration appeared in his mind, he seemed to have heard of that immortal plant but he could not recall it in a short time.

"If I am not wrong, this should be the great profound ice light radish, it is an extinct immortal plant from the Immemorial Antiquity Era. To think that Heavenly Court still kept it till now." Qiao Zhi Cai said.

He was the first supreme elder of Qiao clan, even though he had rank seven cultivation level, he cultivated wood path.

Wu Yong's eyes shined: "That's right, this is the great profound ice light radish. Everyone be careful, if anyone gets close, this radish will burst out with countless ice lights, it will pierce every muscle and skin in your body, you will instantly freeze to death."

Qiao Zhi Cai added to the explanation: "That's right, do not underestimate the ice lights, these ice lights are the dao marks of the great profound ice light radish. After it shoots out, the great profound ice light radish will no longer have any dao marks, it will become a mortal material. Thus, the ice light storm will have the power of a rank eight Gu Immortal's immortal killer move."

The immortals heard this and stepped back, they became very alert.

However, a change occurred right at this moment.

Ripples appeared in the air, the formation suddenly activated as a huge space path force erupted on a Southern Border Gu Immortal.

The Southern Border Gu Immortal had already activated his defenses long ago, but the space path force did not attack him, instead, it teleported him away.

The location was none other than beside the great profound ice light radish!

The great profound ice light radish was like a frightened little girl, it quickly shrunk until it was one-third of its original size.

Afterwards, boom!

Countless ice needles shot out in all directions.

The Southern Border Gu Immortal had already activated his strongest defensive method, but in just half a breath of time, he was pierced thoroughly.

Next, he became frozen, becoming an ice statue.

The Southern Border immortals were all deeply shocked.

The spaceless formation suddenly activated and teleported the Gu Immortal away, it was clearly the variation that Chi Qu You had spoke of earlier. Together with the great profound ice light radish, it was a perfect combination.

Wu Yong's expression turned ashen.

He led the Southern Alliance immortals in this battle, at this moment, they had finally lost their first member.

Wu Yong was quite anxious to find a way to deal with the situation.

At this moment, a change occurred again.

Ripples appeared in space again as a formless space path force erupted, trying to teleport another Southern Alliance Gu Immortal.

"With me around, don't even think about it!" At the crucial moment, Luo Ran shouted, activating an Immortal Gu.

The power of the Immortal Gu spread out as the surrounding space instantly froze like ice.

Southern Alliance's immortals felt a strong restrictive force, as if they were sealed in an ice coffin.

Rank seven Immortal Gu — Suppress Space!

A rank seven Immortal Gu could not deal with this Heavenly Court formation, but it was not without effect.

Suppress space Immortal Gu helped the Southern Alliance Gu Immortal to gain a few crucial seconds to escape.

The formation's spatial ripples were like a beast's mouth that failed to devour its target, it could only vanish in vain.

Luo Ran dispelled the effect of suppress space Immortal Gu, Southern Alliance's Gu Immortals felt the pressure lifting as they regained their freedom.

"The situation was urgent, I had to activate suppress space Immortal Gu, it had a wide range that cannot be controlled, my apologies for implicating everyone." Luo Ran quickly apologized.

Wu Yong laughed loudly: "Well done!"

"This is suppress space Immortal Gu? It is a good Gu worm that counters this formation." Chi Qu You nodded, feeling glad.

Luo Ran smiled: "I obtained this Gu from an Earth Trench recently, to think that it would work here, this shows that somehow, heaven's will truly exists."

Everything in this world had its weaknesses and counters, there was no strongest Gu worm, only strongest Gu Immortal.

Heavenly Court created this spaceless teleportation formation, it was made of several rank seven Immortal Gu and a vast number of mortal Gu, but it was countered by one suppress space Immortal Gu.

With suppress space Immortal Gu, Southern Alliance's immortals no longer had any concerns when moving in this formation space.

And because Heavenly Court's teleportation formation was activated, Chi Qu You's deductions became faster.

A moment later, Chi Qu You pointed out a loophole of the formation.

He said to Wu Yong: "Heavenly Court's spaceless formation is too troublesome to break from the inside. Lord Alliance Leader, why don't you use this loophole to link with the unlimited wind outside and break the formation there, it should be easier."

Wu Yong used the loophole and easily detected the unlimited wind outside.

Immediately, wild winds blew and broke the formation through the loophole.

The Southern Alliance Gu Immortals returned to the outside world.

After breaking six formations and only losing one member, the Southern Alliance immortals had surging morale.

This battle result made the formation's controller feel extremely heavy hearted.

This person was dressed in a green robe, emitting an aura of a scholar. From his appearance, he looked young, but his eyes were deep and wise, he was already some thousands of years old.

It was none other than the wood path rank eight great expert, Heavenly Lotus Sect's previous first supreme elder, the current generation Genesis Lotus inheritor — Chen Yi!

"To think that the enemies are so ferocious! There are only three formations left." Chen Yi pondered for a while and said to the person beside him: "Why don't we work together and fight them, we can gain some time for the formation to be set up."

The female immortal beside him, Bai Cang Shui, was a Heavenly Court member, she had participated in the previous Refinement Path Convention to restore Fate. She did not hesitate, agreeing immediately.

The two walked out of the formation, Wu Yong and the rest were still attacking the seventh layer of the formation, they tried to break it directly.

Chen Yi cupped his fists at the Southern Border immortals: "Southern Border friends, I am Heavenly Court's Chen Yi, does anyone dare to fight me alone?"

Wu Yong's pupils shrunk, he waved his hand as Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was taken out.

In a fight between rank eights, rank seven Gu Immortals could not interfere, but if they went inside an Immortal Gu House, they would be able to join the battle, barely.

Ba clan's first supreme elder Ba Shi Ba laughed loudly: "Old man Chen Yi, it was not wise for you to come out of that tortoise shell. Let me face you."

"Wait, don't let him stall for time, we will attack together!" Wu Yong snickered and ordered.

If Wu Du Xiu was here, she would definitely accept Chen Yi's challenge and fight him alone.

But Wu Yong was a different type of person, why would he give up on a chance to attack him as a group?

Immediately, Wu Yong moved forward with multiple rank eights from Southern Border behind him, along with Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building carrying rank seven Gu Immortals, they charged ahead.

Chen Yi and Bai Cang Shui were attacked by the group but they did not fluster.

Bai Cang Shui pushed with her hands as huge white waves appeared and moved forward.

Wu Yong's body flickered as his afterimage remained, his true body had vanished on the spot.

Ba Shi Ba faced the huge waves as he shouted, his aura surged as a profound light shined on the waves.

Next, the wings on Yi Hao Fang's back waved, countless arrows shot out, the arrow rain pierced the waves, approaching Bai Cang Shui and Chen Yi.

"Come," Chen Yi smiled, he did not make any movements but the phantom images of huge trees appeared around him.

Yi Hao Fang's arrow rain pierced into the forest, it only caused some shaking in the trees, a large number of leaves fell.

Chen Yi's aura grew stronger, he was about to retaliate when his expression suddenly changed.

Wu Yong appeared right behind him unknowingly.

"He has such concealment methods?! The concealed person that I detected was actually an illusion that he made!" Chen Yi was deeply shocked by Wu Yong's methods.

At the moment of crisis, he did not even have time to turn around.

Next, he felt that Wu Yong had lightly patted his shoulder.

"We became friends at first sight, yet you have to go now. This is farewell my good friend, let me send you off." Wu Yong smiled lightly.

Hearing this, even with Chen Yi's thousands of years of life and abundant experiences, his expression became pale.

He shouted in his heart: "This is immortal killer move — Farewell Friend Wind!! My Heavenly Court had not been able to find it even after extensive search, to think that it was in Wu Yong's hands!"

Next, Chen Yi lost control over his body, he slowly floated towards the front.

While floating, his hair, clothes, and limbs started to disintegrate.

"Save me!" Chen Yi shouted in his heart but he could not make any noise.

He could not move at all, none of his methods could be used.

Even karma divine tree killer move was unable to be activated!

Chapter 1710: Limitless' Left Path

Heavenly Court.

The originally white sky became covered in seven colored rainbow lights.

A huge Immortal Gu House was floating in the sky.

It was truly an incredible Immortal Gu House!

It had three floors of altars, grand and magnificent. There were multiple pillars holding each floor up, having white jade railings and shining aurora.

It was the rank eight luck path Immortal Gu House — Calamity Luck Altar.

In the past, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had personally constructed it, it was one of his three Immortal Gu Houses that he used.

Originally, Calamity Luck Altar was left as Longevity Heaven's foundation, but this time to attack Heavenly Court, they actually brought it along.

Such an act showed Longevity Heaven's confidence, many of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals felt very worried.

Fairy Zi Wei frowned deeply.

Even Duke Long had a solemn gaze in his eyes.

However, his attention was not on Calamity Luck Altar, but the rainbow lights in the sky instead.

Duke Long said in a low tone: "Calamity Luck Altar and the Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals alone cannot break in here easily. This seven colored rainbow light is of rank nine level, it must be the work of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!"

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?" Fairy Zi Wei was dazed before realization shined on her face: "According to Heavenly Court's records, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was once invited to tour Heavenly Court. Did he create this backdoor secretly at that time?"

"That should be the case." Duke Long said.

Fairy Zi Wei's expression turned grim: "This Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is truly crafty. He had already planned to invade Heavenly Court so long ago, his scheme was so deep."

"All past venerables have great wisdom, they cannot be underestimated. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable possessed luck path methods, he secretly set this arrangement and we could not discover it until it was used now." Duke Long sighed as he shook his head, having a complex feeling.

Back then, when Giant Sun became venerable, he did it through luck path, it was a huge obstruction to fate Gu. Back then, Heavenly Court's leader, Golden Hooped Great Immortal, made a plan and specially invited Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to tour Heavenly Court, telling the world that they were inviting Giant Sun to join Heavenly Court openly.

After considering it, Giant Sun agreed to the invitation and went on to look around Heavenly Court.

Golden Hooped Great Immortal personally led Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as they went to look at the important places in Heavenly Court, especially the places that Limitless, Reckless Savage, and Red Lotus stopped at when they attacked.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a suggestion, he wanted to see fate Immortal Gu.

Golden Hooped Great Immortal did not reject him, they went up Heaven Overseeing Tower and saw fate Gu.

After Giant Sun left the tower, he remained silent along the way.

After leaving Heavenly Court, he said that he had to reconsider the matter of joining them.

This experience and the conversation between Giant Sun and Golden Hooped was clearly recorded in Heavenly Court's history with great precision.

"The power of rank nine is truly unfathomable, we only saw Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangements today, that is not strange at all. After all, he cultivated luck path, and we have little understanding of this path. However, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who managed to plant spies in Heavenly Court is in our captivity now. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable has died long ago, only his Calamity Luck Altar and a bunch of Northern Plains Gu Immortals are here to attack us now, how can my Heavenly Court fall so easily?" The hall resounded with Old Man Zheng Yuan's voice.

Fairy Zi Wei nodded but she still frowned: "Calamity Luck Altar is not an ordinary rank eight Immortal Gu House, it was once owned by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. It is a pity that Prince Feng Xian did not join this invasion, otherwise we would have gotten information about Longevity Heaven's sneak attack in advance."

"But most importantly, how much force is hidden in Calamity Luck Altar?"

"Hmm… wait, I think there isn't a lot. Because we did not get any news of this invasion by Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven. They were able to keep it hidden so well, they must have kept it to a very small number of people."

Fairy Zi Wei analyzed rapidly.

"You are not wrong, that is likely so." Duke Long nodded, even though he stood up from his seat, his arms were still behind his back, he did not join the battle, as if he was waiting for something.

At the next moment, the whole of Heavenly Court shook.

Swoosh, like the howling of the wind, this sound was etched deep into everyone's hearts.

Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, and Old Man Zheng Yuan felt no surprise, they showed faint smiles on their faces.

"The killer move that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable left behind has activated!"

Within Calamity Luck Altar, Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals felt no surprise either.

The information that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind already described this. In fact, even without Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's information, Longevity Heaven had a number of true inheritances of the few Demon Venerables. Be it Reckless Savage or Limitless, they were Northern Plainsmen, the intel of their attack on Heavenly Court was in Longevity Heaven's hands.

"This is the killer move qi wall?"

"Qi wall killer move is very ordinary, but when Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was at a young age, he was very skilled at it and enjoyed using it."

"When Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable became invincible in the world, this qi wall killer move was also elevated to rank nine!"

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals discussed as they manipulated Calamity Luck Altar, attacking the surroundings.

The surrounding air started to produce ripples like a formless fortress, only after facing a lot of attacks did it burst back into normal air.

But soon, it gathered again into a formless fortress wall.

The whole of Heavenly Court was reinforced by this air, resisting the invasion of Longevity Heaven. But for Heavenly Court's members, when they moved, the qi wall around them would return to normal air, they would not be obstructed.

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals made some attempts as they expressed shock on their faces.

"Indeed worthy of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!"

"The ordinary qi wall killer move has the power of rank nine in Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's hands, it is even stronger than the heavenly wind qi wall."

"What do we do now?" Five Elements Grandmaster had an ugly expression, he was very worried. He had just joined Longevity Heaven recently, he had only learned of the invasion several days ago.

Five Elements Grandmaster's worry was very reasonable, if they could not get past this move, they would need to destroy all the qi walls along their path.

The expenditure would be too high, they might not even make it to Duke Long before their immortal essence dried up, they would be extremely tired.

But it was too difficult to unravel this move.

Firstly, it was a rank nine killer move, only methods of similar level would be effective. Unless they possessed an extremely effective rank eight killer move, it would not be useful.

Secondly, after the changes of eras, qi path had already fallen out of common use, almost nobody from Longevity Heaven in this trip cultivated qi path.

What could they do?

"Don't worry, we have our method!"

"Even though this move is made by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, so many years have passed, eras have changed, after the invasions of three Demon Venerables, it already possessed flaws."

"That's right, back then, Limitless, Reckless Savage, and Red Lotus could not unravel this qi wall killer move even though they attacked Heavenly Court. They merely used their incredible strength to break through by force."

"They carved out three roads on their own, these three paths are the places where the qi wall is at its weakest and cannot regenerate. As long as we destroy a small area, we will be able to enter one of these three paths and follow the Demon Venerable's road to fight our way in!"

Five Elements Grandmaster let out a sigh of relief: "So that's it."

Next, he asked: "Which path do we choose?"

At the same time.

In the Central Great Hall, Duke Long and Fairy Zi Wei conversed: "Even though qi wall is powerful, it had been exposed long ago. Since Longevity Heaven is attacking now, they must be aware of its weaknesses, they will use the paths that the Demon Venerables created."

Fairy Zi Wei nodded, recalling: "The left path was created by Limitless Demon Venerable, it passes Central Heaven Gate, Name Plaque Palace, Sun Palace, Five Deity Hall, Central Great Hall, Heaven Overseeing Tower, Forgotten Dao Lake, and finally, it stops at the Imperfection Regret Pavilion on the peak of Star Zone Mountain."

"The central path was created by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable. It passes Immortal Emperor Court, Hidden Space Pavilion, Sumeru Lake, Eternal Sand Cave, Million Heavenly King Gallery, Embroidered Tower, Central Great Hall, and ends at Heaven Overseeing Tower."

"The right path was made by Red Lotus Demon Venerable. He first went past Lotus Fairy Pond and Bright Moon Treasure Light Hall, followed by Twelve Spiritual Pass, Separation Flame Pavilion, Magnetic Star Hill, Water Wood Clarity Court, Central Great Hall, and ends at Heaven Overseeing Tower."

"As long as they make their choice, we will be able to know their route and set up our defenses."

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with the sparkles of wisdom.

"That is right." Duke Long had no objections.

Boom boom boom!

Calamity Luck Altar brought the few Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals as they attacked the weak spot of the qi wall and went in.

Once they entered, Longevity Heaven's group felt that the pressure was greatly lifted, the qi wall was barely existing here!

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals also saw what happened.

Fairy Zi Wei and Duke Long looked at each other: "They chose the left path."

Chapter 1711: Heavenly Court Battlefield

Left path!

This was the path that Limitless Demon Venerable created a million years ago during the Olden Antiquity Era!

The left path passed Central Heaven Gate, Name Plaque Palace, Sun Palace, Five Deity Hall, Central Great Hall, Heaven Overseeing Tower, Forgotten Dao Lake, and finally, it stopped at the Imperfection Regret Pavilion on the peak of Star Zone Mountain.

The huge Heavenly Court was shining in glorious light, it had countless palaces and pavilions, it was a grand sight.

Calamity Luck Altar charged ahead with an unstoppable momentum.

Heavenly Court, which had been silent for a long time, finally met with an unavoidable attack.

Within Calamity Luck Altar, Five Elements Grandmaster watched and observed the situation.

He was tongue-tied and deeply moved: "If I was not seeing this personally, I would not believe that all these buildings here are Immortal Gu Houses! Even though most are just rank six Immortal Gu Houses, Heavenly Court's foundation is still too terrifying."

Flower Lady of the Northern Desolation Immortals chuckled: "Five Elements, this is Heavenly Court after all. It was created three million years ago during the Remote Antiquity Era, it had remained standing until today. Even though fate Gu was damaged, it remained as the number one force in this world. With such an accumulation, this is not a surprising sight."

"Look at these palaces, they are all the creation of famous rank eight immortals from the Remote Antiquity Era. After modifications from future experts like Statue Deity, Aunt Orchid, Yellow Court Monarch, Uncle Feng, and Concubine Quan Miao, they continued to develop and improve upon them, until they were completed today."

"All of the palaces and Immortal Gu Houses are considered one entity, they can help each other. At the same time, these palaces can be separated and elevated on their own, it is very convenient."

"However, there is no need to overestimate Heavenly Court, these Immortal Gu Houses are mostly just rank six. And most importantly, they are only specialized in one aspect, they are not as comprehensive as the Immortal Gu Houses outside."

Five Elements Grandmaster nodded: "I understand, if it is comprehensive, even more Immortal Gu will need to be used, as well as a vast number of mortal Gu. Heavenly Court is very proud, other than the three Demon Venerables who attacked, nobody dared to invade them. Thus, there was no need for such investments in their opinion, after all, these Immortal Gu Houses are kept in Heavenly Court most of the time, they are not too useful."

Saying so, Five Elements Grandmaster suddenly laughed loudly: "So that's it! We attacked Heavenly Court and caught them unguarded at this moment. This is their weakness, interesting, interesting. Other than three Demon Venerables, to think that I will also attack Heavenly Court. Even if I die here, with this experience, my life was not in vain."

Five Elements Grandmaster was filled with grand aspirations. He was a Northern Plainsman, even though he was rank eight, his nature was that of a Northern Plainsman, it had never changed.

The people of Northern Plains sought glory through combat, it was a shame to live as a loser.

For them, dying in the battlefield was the greatest honor and recognition.

Calamity Luck Altar forced its way through, finally arriving at Central Heaven Gate.

This huge gate was like a mountain adorned with beautiful golden ornaments, it was held by tall and thick pillars, there were shining pearls and gems on its frame.

"This is Central Heaven Gate?"

"It looks like an information path Immortal Gu House?"

Five Elements Grandmaster looked around as he pondered.

"Indeed, Heavenly Court only recruits new members who are elites of the ten great ancient sects. These rank eight elites would have to pass the test in Central Heaven Gate before they join Heavenly Court." Bull Demon said.

Central Heaven Gate was shut tight, it blocked Calamity Luck Altar from advancing further.

In Central Great Hall.

Duke Long asked: "Central Heaven Gate is a rank eight information path Immortal Gu House but it has weak defenses, it cannot stop them for long. How many golden pearls do we have in the storage?"

Fairy Zi Wei replied immediately: "Three thousand six hundred."

Duke Long nodded: "Take them all out and use them to help Central Heaven Gate defend against the enemy. I am certain that Longevity Heaven has trump cards up its sleeves, Northern Plains has courageous people but they are not without wisdom. We need to remain calm and deal with them without panicking, we will stall for time and wait until fate Gu is restored, all our hard work and sacrifice will pay off in the end."

"Yes, sir." Fairy Zi Wei answered as she manipulated the Central Great Hall.

The Central Great Hall was the control area of all the Heavenly Court Immortal Gu Houses, using it, Fairy Zi Wei opened Heavenly Court's treasury and took out all of their golden pearls.

Cling cling cling…

There was a sharp noise as golden pearls fell down like rain, there were golden sparkles as they poured down.

Calamity Luck Altar crashed into Central Heaven Gate as it started to crack from the pressure.

The golden pearls landed on Calamity Luck Altar and created continuous sharp noises.

Calamity Luck Altar remained unaffected, there were no cracks on it.

However, the golden pearls started to show their true effect, as the peals turned into huge soldiers that were armored all over their bodies. Under the shadows of their helmets, only their two eyes were shining with piercing golden light. They had weapons like axes, blades, and spears in their hands.

Soon, these golden pearl soldiers surrounded Calamity Luck Altar. Countless blades and spears slashed and stabbed at Calamity Luck Altar, causing many sparks to appear.

Calamity Luck Altar shook intensely, in order to defend from the attacks, immortal essence was rapidly expended.

"What is this?" Five Elements Grandmaster was shocked: "Each soldier has the strength of an ancient desolate beast but possesses no life force, this looks like an immortal killer move?"

"These are golden pearls. During the Medieval Antiquity Era, there was a metal path great expert in Heavenly Court, he was known as the Golden Pearl Immortal King. These golden pearls were his signature killer move, a method unique to him." Bull Demon said plainly.

Flower Lady giggled as she covered her mouth: "Heavenly Court is only tossing these golden pearls while Fairy Zi Wei and Duke Long are not showing up, it seems that they are trying to stall for time until fate Gu gets restored."

Bull Demon nodded: "This is a wise decision, even though Heavenly Court is huge, there are only a few rank eight Gu Immortals who are awake. The battlefield outside is depleting and splitting up Heavenly Court's current force."

"Then we need to make use of this time." Flower Lady's eyes shined.

Bull Demon said in a low tone: "Let me do it."

Saying so, he concentrated and started to manipulate Calamity Luck Altar.

A method was activated by Bull Demon as Calamity Luck Altar started to shine in a blinding light.

Within the light, auspicious clouds formed and pushed all the golden pearl soldiers away.

At the next moment, with a loud bang, Calamity Luck Altar broke through Central Heaven Gate.

Longevity Heaven's group did not slaughter these golden pearl soldiers or attack the heavily damaged Central Heaven Gate, they only pushed forward.

This was a battle that was determined by time.

Since Heavenly Court wanted to stall for time, Longevity Heaven's group had to make use of that and prevent them from succeeding.

Along the way, golden pearl soldiers continued to obstruct them but could not stop Calamity Luck Altar's advancement.

Soon, Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals arrived at Name Plaque Palace.

But what they saw was that Name Plaque Palace flew high up into the sky.

"Heavenly Court actually moved this Name Plaque Palace away!" Five Elements Grandmaster was happy but suspicious.

Bing Sai Chuan said in a low tone: "This is also an information path Immortal Gu House, there are name plaques inside, each has a person's name. These people form a huge information network for Heavenly Court, they are all over the five regions."

Five Elements Grandmaster was shocked: "So that means, if we destroy it, Heavenly Court's information network will be exposed? No wonder they had to move it away at any cost."

Five Elements Grandmaster felt that it was a pity.

Heavenly Court's information network was huge, it covered all five regions. Even though other regions were trying to get information on other regions, their scale and reach could not compare to Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court had the ten great ancient sects as their subordinate forces, they had ruled over Central Continent for many eras, they were naturally able to select suitable people to nurture as elites and send to other regions secretly.

As for the other four regions, Longevity Heaven and Southern Alliance had only surfaced recently, trying to unify their own regions. As for other super clans, even if they sent people out, compared to Heavenly Court, they were too small and insignificant.

"Forget it, we had already anticipated that Name Plaque Palace would fly away. Without its obstruction, we can save a lot of time and advance faster!" Bing Sai Chuan ordered.

Sun Palace.

Calamity Luck Altar soon arrived at the third obstacle.

Sun Palace gave out a heated light, it was too blinding.

The surroundings of the palace were distorted from the warm air, intense heat assaulted everyone.

Even though Longevity Heaven's members were inside Calamity Luck Altar, they still felt immense heat that burned them endlessly.

The immortals tried to move Calamity Luck Altar to charge through but even without getting too close, the surface of Calamity Luck Altar started melting, a vast number of mortal Gu were charred and incinerated.

Sun Palace was so strong that Calamity Luck Altar could not get close.

It controlled the illumination of the whole of Heavenly Court, it had multiple light path rank eight Immortal Gu as the cores, even though it was very weak in defense, even lower than Central Heaven Gate, Calamity Luck Altar could not approach it.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Calamity Luck Altar stayed in the air as killer moves were activated, attacking Sun Palace from afar.

But all sorts of killer moves melted from the heat and light of Sun Palace before they even landed.

"This obstacle is too hard, we do not have any light path or dark path experts helping us." Five Elements Grandmaster frowned deeply.

"No need to worry." Bull Demon spoke: "Sun Palace is strong on the outside and weak on the inside, as long as we can get in, we will be able to destroy it. I will go."

"Okay, let's go together." Flower Lady chuckled as she lay on his shoulder, feeling no nervousness at all.

Five Elements Grandmaster was greatly shocked.

He knew how dangerous that was, the light was too intense, without proper defense, even rank eight Gu Immortals could not last long, they would melt like candles.

"Isn't that too dangerous, we can think of other ways." Five Elements Grandmaster said cautiously.

Bing Sai Chuan shook his head: "Speed is the key, go."

He controlled Calamity Luck Altar as it attacked, paving a way for Bull Demon and Flower Lady.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady shot out with incredible speed, they were about to get into Sun Palace in just an instant.

"Wishful thinking!" Fairy Zi Wei who was in the Central Great Hall smiled coldly as Sun Palace's intensity surged.

"Oh no." Five Elements Grandmaster shouted in dismay.

At the crucial moment, Flower Lady shouted as her tiny body jumped, turning into a pink light that shielded Bull Demon.

Bull Demon cried out in pain, he charged into Sun Palace without stopping.

Fairy Zi Wei's expression turned grim, she said bitterly: "Sun Palace has been taken down."

After ten breaths of time, Sun Palace was destroyed.

Without Sun Palace, the whole of Heavenly Court's sky became dark.

In the rubble, Bull Demon carried Flower Lady's corpse as he returned to Calamity Luck Altar with an expressionless face.

Sun Palace was destroyed, Longevity Heaven also paid a price.

Flower Lady died!

Looking at the silent Bull Demon, Five Elements Grandmaster wanted to console him but no words came out after he opened his mouth.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady were together known as the Northern Desolation Immortals, they were usually extremely close and never left each other's side. Now that one was sacrificed while the other survived, this pain was truly deep and heavy.

Even though Flower Lady died, she had a smile on her face.

Bull Demon looked at Flower Lady's corpse for a long time, she eventually turned into scattering flower petals, only a tiny delicate flower remained.

Bull Demon placed this flower on his head carefully and gently, it was completely different from his usual cold and tough appearance.

"Continue." Bull Demon turned around and looked towards the front.

Under Bing Sai Chuan's manipulation, Calamity Luck Altar continued to move ahead.

Chapter 1712: Battle of Legendary Desolate Beasts

Once Sun Palace was destroyed, the next was Five Deity Hall. And after Five Deity Hall, it would be the Central Great Hall that Fairy Zi Wei and Duke Long were in.

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals came with determination, they attacked ferociously without concern for sacrifices, Heavenly Court's immortals felt deep pressure.

"We cannot let them continue with this any farther." Duke Long turned to Fairy Zi Wei: "Have you deployed all of them already?"

Fairy Zi Wei's expression was quite ugly: "Only two came."

Duke Long was dazed before he spoke: "Cang Xuan Zi didn't come? So be it, when it agreed to join Heavenly Court back then, there was already an agreement with Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. The two that came should be able to block Calamity Luck Altar for some time with their strength."

Five Deity Hall was already in sight, suddenly, a sandstorm brewed, waves of sand blocked Calamity Luck Altar.

Roar—!

A tiger's roar resounded in the surroundings.

The sand waves spread apart as a hill-like tiger was exposed from within.

The fierce tiger had overwhelming aura, its body seemed to be made of metal, it had golden skin and silver teeth, its eyes resembled sparkling rubies, emanating fierce light. On the tiger's forehead, the marking was not '王' but '沙[1]'.

Five Elements Grandmaster took a glance and expressed his shock: "Heavenly Court also has legendary immemorial desolate beasts?"

"Of course." Bing Sai Chuan had a plain expression: "Heavenly Court has a total of three legendary immemorial beasts. This huge tiger looks like a tiger but it is actually a Shabi. This is a type of monster that is formed in the fiendish qi sea spring. Right now, qi path is going extinct, the fiendish qi sea spring is already extinct, this is the only Shabi left."

"During the Olden Antiquity Era, Heavenly Court's qi path great expert Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch nurtured it. After he became rank eight and traveled the world, he purposely looked for the fiendish qi sea springs and created the Shabi from them. He refined a total of ninety-nine Shabi, he formed a grand army with them. These Shabi were compatible with his immortal killer moves, he could use them extremely well, during that era, almost nobody could rival him."

"But now, this is the final one. This Shabi was one of the last few created, it was number ninety-five. Thus, it had been named as such, but after Ancestor Giant Sun got invited to Heavenly Court and saw this Shabi, he named it Shabi Ninety-five[2]."

"So there was such a backstory. No wonder lord has such a deep understanding of it." Five Elements Grandmaster sighed in admiration.

He looked behind him, only to see that Shabi Ninety-five had whipped up a sandstorm, fighting against 'Calamity Luck Altar' with a grand commotion, displaying peak rank eight battle strength!

Bing Sai Chuan analyzed closely: "Shabi Ninety-five resides in Eternal Sand Cave, it was deployed by Heavenly Court to come here. Green jade crane Ruan Dan will likely come here too, while Cang Xuan Zi is probably not coming."

Five Elements Grandmaster asked: "Ruan Dan, Cang Xuan Zi, are they the remaining two legendary immemorial beasts?"

At the same time, he felt puzzled inside: Why was Bing Sai Chuan so certain that Cang Xuan Zi would not join the battle? Did they have spies in Heavenly Court?

Bing Sai Chuan answered: "Indeed. Ruan Dan is an immemorial green jade crane, it was nurtured by Immortal Crane Sect and created pill path, it resides in Heavenly Court to cultivate in normal times. As for Cang Xuan Zi, it is that vast heaven vine. This vine has incredible power and abilities, it sprouts in three hundred years, blossoms in three hundred years, and bears fruits in three hundred years. The fruits that it create are called vast heaven fruits, if used in a grotto-heaven, it can expand the size of the immortal aperture's sky. Thus, this vast heaven vine is also known as the tenth heaven of this world!"

"Tenth heaven of this world…" Five Elements Grandmaster shook, he suddenly realized as he pointed left: "That huge vine pillar that extends towards the limits of the sky?"

Heavenly Court had countless palaces, there was a huge vine that connected heaven and earth, it was even taller than the Heaven Overseeing Tower behind the Central Great Hall, it was very eye-catching. When Five Elements Grandmaster invaded Heavenly Court, he noticed it immediately.

"That's right, the vast heaven vine was brought in by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable personally, it had an agreement with him, it is a unique existence in Heavenly Court, it does not need to follow orders, but only has to provide a batch of vast heaven fruits every thousand years."

Five Elements Grandmaster heard this as he felt his horizons broadening, he had never thought that there would be a legendary immemorial desolate plant in this world that could ignore Heavenly Court's orders.

But thinking about it, he knew why.

The vast heaven vine's ability was too unique and special. With these vast heaven fruits, Heavenly Court could continue to increase the skies of the immortal aperture and increase its foundation. Rather than saying that the vast heaven vine could ignore Heavenly Court's orders, it was more like Heavenly Court was making use of it and allowing it some degree of freedom.

At the moment, in the Central Great Hall.

"Oh no!" Fairy Zi Wei frowned: "This Calamity Luck Altar is fake."

"What?" Duke Long looked over.

Fairy Zi Wei was in control of Central Great Hall, she had been using the palaces and countless Immortal Gu Houses to observe Central Continent, she obviously kept a high amount of concentration on Heavenly Court's situation.

Heaven Overseeing Tower could not be moved normally, Fairy Zi Wei mobilized the other Immortal Gu Houses, shooting out a crystal rainbow light.

The rainbow light tore through the skies, landing on 'Calamity Luck Altar'.

"Calamity Luck Altar' shook before it returned to its original form.

This was a four legged beast with purple fur.

Its body was huge, even larger than the Shabi.

It was like a ferret, its body covered in shiny purple fur, its eyes were shining with a purple crystal-like color, there was a dog tail on its back.

"Oh! You finally realized, you fools from Heavenly Court! Hahaha…" The purple ferret laughed loudly, mocking its enemies.

"You are… Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu?!" Shabi Ninety-five was very shocked, it spoke human words.

The purple ferret's expression sank, it quickly moved out like a purple flash of lightning.

Boom.

Sand splattered, the dog tail life extending ferret pressed down on the Shabi as it opened its mouth, saying with a fierce expression and low tone: "Remember, call me Grandpa Mao!"

Shabi Ninety-five was furious, growling: "In terms of age, I am your grandfather instead!"

It struggled to get up but the dog tail life extending ferret did not budge.

Shabi Ninety-five was secretly shocked: "This beast has such great strength? But how can I be suppressed like this?"

"Hahaha, stupid cat and silly ferret, you two are a good couple, this is such an interesting fight." Right at this moment, laughter resounded above the two beasts.

Dog tail life extending ferret looked up and saw a Gu Immortal sitting on a cloud, looking at them with a smile.

The dog tail life extending ferret's expression froze for a second before it realized: "Oh, so you are that green jade crane, why are you posing as a human? Come down, let your Grandpa Mao teach you how to be a proper bird again!"

The laughter stopped, the green jade crane was furious: "You insolent ferret, I am going to tear your skin apart."

The green jade crane was about to descend when it stopped all of a sudden, Fairy Zi Wei had given it orders secretly, instead of fighting with dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu, it was supposed to head to Five Deity Hall.

The true Calamity Luck Altar had not shown itself but the route it could take was fixed.

The green jade crane acknowledged the order and was about to leave when a huge shadow appeared in front of it.

It looked up and its pupils shrunk.

Mao Li Qiu had jumped into the sky and its huge form was crashing down while causing a vacuum behind it.

The green jade crane shrieked before it returned to its true form, it flapped its wings and quickly got out of the casted shadow's range.

But at the next moment, Mao Li Qiu's claws grabbed onto the green jade crane's leg.

"Come down here for your Grandpa Mao!" The dog tail life extending ferret snickered as it pulled with its strong limb.

The green jade crane flapped its wings furiously, but it soon discovered to its despair that any effort ended in vain.

Slam, the green jade crane landed on the ground, causing a huge pit to form.

The green jade crane's ears were buzzing, it only had one thought in its mind now: "This Northern Plains brute has such great strength!"

The green jade crane struggled to get up but Mao Li Qiu pounced once again.

Dust clouds rose as rocks were sent flying.

The green jade crane continued to shriek ——

"Ahh! You thug, don't pull my feathers."

"Ahh, you mindless beast, don't bite my leg!"

"Don't touch my elegant neck you scumbag!"

"My neck is breaking, it's breaking!"

"Ahhhh, my leg is breaking, my leg is breaking!"

Duke Long: "…"

Fairy Zi Wei: "…"

Five Elements Grandmaster: "…"

Bing Sai Chuan: "…"

Eventually, the green jade crane's screaming reached its limit: "Stupid cat, what are you doing, why aren't you coming here and helping me?!"

"Hahaha, weren't you having a good time watching earlier? You two can play, I'm leaving." Shabi Ninety-five laughed as it flew towards Five Deity Hall.

"Where are you going?" Mao Li Qiu snickered as a clone flew out of its body, pouncing at Shabi Ninety-five with great speed.

"We are both males, why are you lying on top of me now?!" Shabi Ninety-five was furious.

The green jade crane agreed with these words wholeheartedly, it shrieked amidst the dust clouds: "That's right! Let us go if you have guts… ahhh, stop kicking between my legs, your evil scumbag!"

Shabi Ninety-five was very angry, it liked the action of pouncing on others, but it liked to be at the top, being at the bottom was a disgrace and humiliation.

Shabi Ninety-five was struggling on the ground below Mao Li Qiu, it was furious and its teeth were exposed as it growled: "A mere clone, you want to obstruct me, you are simply looking down… hmm?"

At the next moment, Shabi Ninety-five's expression became dazed, it was a little fearful: "Is this the main body or a clone? Why does it have such great strength?"

In the Central Great Hall, Duke Long seemed to have realized something: "This is…"

Because of Mao Li Qiu's actions, Calamity Luck Altar obtained some crucial time, it finally arrived at Five Deity Hall.

"I have already explained the details of Five Deity Hall to you, it will depend on you now." Bing Sai Chuan said to Five Elements Grandmaster.

Five Elements Grandmaster looked behind worriedly: "Can Grandpa Mao do it? How long can it last?"

"Don't worry, it is using the killer move perfect pair, this was the method of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable that my Longevity Heaven had searched for with great effort! It can summon a clone with the same battle strength as the main body." Bing Sai Chuan's lips curled up.

"Understood!" Five Elements Grandmaster's eyes shined with bright light, staring at Five Deity Hall.

Five Deity Hall shook intensely, a giant spirit made of the five elements, metal, wood, water, fire, earth, formed and attacked Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar burst out with profound light, Five Elements Grandmaster was directly sent into Five Deity Hall.

The five elements giant spirit was furious, it wanted to defend but Calamity Luck Altar shot out an incredible attraction force that restrained it.

[1] The tiger represents the masculine principle in nature and is king of all the animals, as shown by the four stripes on his forehead, which form the character Wang (王), or King. The second Chinese character means sand. Back

[2] TL Note: This creature is derived from the Bi'an, one of the nine sons of the dragon. The sha in front refers to the fiendish qi, it also has the same pronunciation as sand. As for Shabi itself, you can google to see the meaning. Back

Chapter 1713: Battle Between Venerables

Bam bam bam…

With a chain of explosions, Five Deity Hall was blown to smithereens amidst a huge fire.

Five Elements Grandmaster stepped on thin air as he walked out, even though there was some soot on his face, he was unharmed.

Next, he went inside Calamity Luck Altar.

Five Elements Grandmaster laughed loudly: "Even though this Five Deity Hall is extraordinary, I am very familiar with its concept, my methods directly counter it. This was much easier than I had expected it to be!"

As he said that, a sense of pride emerged in him.

Bing Sai Chuan looked at him and said plainly: "Of course it is, the formation path methods that you use are part of my Ancestor Giant Sun's arrangements."

Five Elements Grandmaster was stunned, his expression changed as he looked at Bing Sai Chuan: "What do you mean?"

Bing Sai Chuan gave him a glance, showing a smile full of deep meaning: "Why do you think you managed to enter Longevity Heaven when you attacked? Do you remember the most important words of your inheritance? Do you find them nonsensical? Try reading them in reverse, but only the last word of each sentence."

Five Elements Grandmaster was immediately suspicious.

He was a lone cultivator from birth, his turning point was the mysterious lone immortal formation path true inheritance that he found, it led to his achievements.

"Ever since I obtained the true inheritance, I cultivated non-stop and had never spoken of it to others. How does Bing Sai Chuan know that my true inheritance has those important sentences? I have never understood what it was saying… reverse the order and read the last word of each line…."

"Hmm? Listen to Bing Sai Chuan and attack Heavenly Court?!" Five Elements Grandmaster was lost for words, he stared at Bing Sai Chuan in disbelief.

Bing Sai Chuan controlled Calamity Luck Altar to move forward while saying slowly: "Even if a rank nine venerable does not cultivate wisdom path, at their level, they have already gained a deep understanding of the path, it is not hard to set up arrangements that will affect future generations."

"Back then, after Ancestor Giant Sun visited Heavenly Court, he made plans for today's invasion. The method to destroy Five Deity Hall was part of his arrangements."

"But if he displayed his research results so openly, traces would be left behind and Heavenly Court would notice them. Thus, he secretly left an arrangement that was independent of Longevity Heaven, he allowed it to develop on its own and be cultivated by a lone cultivator. Because you are not of Giant Sun's bloodline, even if you become a rank eight, Heavenly Court would not expect your methods to counter Five Deity Hall. They would not think of you and link it to our invasion of Heavenly Court!"

Saying so, Bing Sai Chuan paused and continued: "Grandmaster, the climatic battle involving fate Gu is far more complex than you can ever imagine. Rank six and seven Gu Immortals are not even qualified to join. As for rank eight Gu Immortals, we are merely pawns. Some rank eights refuse to join in, that is because they sensed something and understand their own self-worth. Some joined but are ignorant of the true situation."

"The truth behind this great battle is the fight of past venerables across time and space!"

Five Elements Grandmaster was stunned from hearing this, he muttered: "Fighting across time and space, a battle between venerables?"

In human history, there were ten venerables. Each one was invincible in their own era, they were at the apex of history, the greatest pride of humanity.

Bing Sai Chuan revealed the truth, Five Elements Grandmaster was deeply shocked.

He could not help but feel his own insignificance, his pride from earlier vanished without a trace.

Bing Sai Chuan glanced at Five Elements Grandmaster's look of shock as he consoled: "But don't worry, among the venerables, Ancestor Giant Sun is the most caring towards his descendants and subordinates. He gained a nickname back then because of this."

"The venerables all have their own arrangements, they want to exert their influence at this crucial moment, But after the merciless tides of history, most of these arrangements have been altered in some way. Rank nine venerables are not all-knowing, they would make mistakes too, many arrangements have been completely changed due to the passing of time."

"A large number of them were discovered by future venerables and got modified."

"Ancestor Giant Sun came after Genesis Lotus and Thieving Heaven, he was succeeded by Spectral Soul and Paradise Earth. The venerables who appear later would naturally have an advantage in setting up their arrangements, our attack on Heavenly Court succeeded to this extent, the reason is obvious."

Bing Sai Chuan's words made Five Elements Grandmaster go into a daze.

Bing Sai Chuan chuckled afterwards: "So what if there is Duke Long? Can he compare to Ancestor Giant Sun's arrangements? No need to worry so much, you must have confidence that we will succeed! In this expedition, our Longevity Heaven will definitely obtain fate Gu!"

"Obtain fate Gu?" At this moment, Five Elements Grandmaster finally realized Longevity Heaven's objective in attacking Heavenly Court.

"That's right." Bing Sai Chuan admitted openly, there was no need to hide anything now: "Heavenly Court came to snatch our fortune rivalling heaven Gu, why can't we come after their fate Gu?"

"Why is Heavenly Court the number one human force? Fate Gu played a crucial role in it. After getting it, our Longevity Heaven will definitely obtain the throne of the number one human force!"

In Central Great Hall.

Fairy Zi Wei looked as Calamity Luck Altar got closer, she had a serious expression: "They are coming!"

At her side, Old Man Zheng Yuan was also expressing his concern.

Even though the Central Great Hall was the control area of all the Immortal Gu Houses, it had low defense. After all ,who would think that Heavenly Court's Central Great Hall would be attacked by enemies?

Even though this Central Great Hall was once attacked by three Demon Venerables and even got destroyed, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals did not reinforce its defense later on. Because against venerables, no matter how strong Central Great Hall's defense was, it could not defend against a venerable, there was no point.

Now it seemed like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already noticed this flaw when he toured Heavenly Court. Longevity Heaven's assault caught Heavenly Court off-guard, Fairy Zi Wei and the rest were in a passive situation.

"It seems that the true flaw is not in terms of defense but mindset." Fairy Zi Wei had an understanding as she said: "I seem to have missed out something. Is it…"

"How long until fate Gu is fully restored?" At this moment, Duke Long asked.

Fairy Zi Wei was in charge of the Central Great Hall, she knew the situation of the refinement path formation, she had a heavy heart as she answered: "We need six hours."

"Six hours…" Duke Long was joyful: "My lifespan is almost used up, but heaven has taken pity on me, even though six hours is not a lot, I will be able to see fate Gu restored. Next, let me handle this."

Fairy Zi Wei asked worriedly: "Lord Duke Long, your injuries have yet to…"

Even though Heavenly Court tried its best to heal him, Duke Long's injuries still remained. This was caused by the joint attack of Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals, in the short time, even Duke Long could not heal himself fully.

Duke Long smiled plainly: "I am about to die anyway, these injuries do not matter. In any case, I have the killer move heavenly dragon's last stand, at the final moments of my life, in all five regions, is there anyone who can match me in battle?"

He had a plain expression but his words revealed utter confidence and dominance!

Calamity Luck Altar was like a huge beast as it charged down at the Central Great Hall.

Air was sliced apart, wild winds roared.

If it hit, the entire Central Great Hall would be reduced to shambles.

At this moment, a single small body appeared, blocking its path.

"Duke Long!" Five Elements Grandmaster shouted.

"Smash into him." Bull Demon said.

Boom!

The hill-like Calamity Luck Altar crashed down ferociously, but it was stopped in midair.

A dragon claw forced it to stop.

Duke Long floated in the air, his body did not move but his right hand had turned into sharp dragon claws, grabbing onto Calamity Luck Altar and preventing it from moving any further.

"This?!" Five Elements Grandmaster was deeply shocked.

Bull Demon was also in disbelief: "He alone managed to stop Calamity Luck Altar so easily? Unbelievable! If I was not seeing this personally, I would never believe it."

Crack…

The dragon claws exerted strength as they dug into Calamity Luck Altar, cracks started to form and spread around the dragon claws.

Calamity Luck Altar started to shine in a piercing light, immortal killer moves were used on Duke Long who was in close proximity.

Despite being bathed in explosions and impacts, Duke Long's body remained unmoved.

Roar…

An immense aura and qi burst out of his body.

The qi gathered and formed into dragons that coiled around Calamity Luck Altar, squeezing it.

"What method is this? Duke Long had not used it in the Eastern Sea battle!" Bull Demon squinted.

He suddenly had a flash of inspiration, uttering: "There is no invincible Immortal Gu, only invincible Gu Immortal."

Five Elements Grandmaster was shocked once again.

Dragon qi killer move had unparalleled might, Five Elements Grandmaster knew clearly that if he had to face the attack, he would not last long. Calamity Luck Altar was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, but it was still suppressed by Duke Long singlehandedly!

Longevity Heaven's members could already see victory in the horizons, Heaven Overseeing Tower was right ahead but Duke Long obstructed them, turning their hope of victory into an unattainable dream.

Duke Long was just one person, but he was an obstacle that they could not get past!

"He is just rank eight, how can our difference be this immense? Lord Bing Sai Chuan, what do we do?" Five Elements Grandmaster was out of ideas.

The difference in battle strength could not be made up for with courage.

Five Elements Grandmaster looked at Bing Sai Chuan, but he had already gone missing.

Where did he go?

At the next moment, Bing Sai Chuan appeared behind Duke Long.

His time path killer move that had been prepared for a long time landed on Duke Long's head.

"Success?" Bing Sai Chuan's pupils shrunk.

Duke Long did not move, instead a vast wave of dragon qi shot out with a loud roar.

The dragon mouth bit Bing Sai Chuan as it flew up, restraining him in the air.

Bing Sai Chuan relied on his defenses to hold on while he used killer moves to try and get out of the dragon qi's restraint.

But his actions were futile.

The dragon qi was not indestructible, but its speed of recovery was just too fast.

"You are clearly injured… this is definitely not your usual battle strength!" Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth.

"How can you possibly comprehend the profundity of my killer move, heavenly dragon's last stand?" Duke Long looked at Bing Sai Chuan plainly as he placed his focus back on Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar was filled with cracks, it was surrounded by countless dragon shaped qi that pressed down on it, a large number of Gu worms continued to die. Calamity Luck Altar could not break free, if this went on, it would definitely be destroyed.

Five Elements Grandmaster gritted his teeth: "Let me go out, I would rather die in combat by Duke Long's hands than die here without doing anything."

Bull Demon was silent.

Bing Sai Chuan suddenly snickered: "I am not your match, but so what? I have my trump card! I respectfully request — Limitless, please turn around!"

"What?!" This time, it was Duke Long's turn to be shocked.

Chapter 1714: Limitless Takes Action

A million years ago!

Olden Antiquity Era

Limitless Demon Venerable attacked Heavenly Court and moved unhindered, even though Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals tried to stop him, they were powerless.

Limitless Demon Venerable moved at a casual speed but none of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals could match him, they suffered huge losses and deaths.

Central Heaven Gate broke into shrapnel, Name Plaque Palace did not even have the time to fly away, in front of Limitless Demon Venerable, Sun Palace and Five Deity Hall were thin as paper, they were simply like a joke.

Eventually, when Limitless Demon Venerable arrived before the Central Great Hall, Heavenly Court shook, Star Constellation's will descended and activated Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangement — nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Limitless Demon Venerable landed in the formation and only managed to escape after destroying a hundred formations.

Below Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Limitless Demon Venerable looked at Star Constellation's will: "Star Constellation, we are both venerables, you spent so much effort to try and restrict me, even though I hate you, I also admire you. Right now, you are dead while I am alive, no matter how many methods you left behind, so what? You want to stop a living Gu Venerable? That is impossible. Rank nine venerables are invincible in this world, only other venerables can deal with them."

Star Constellation's will smiled bitterly, she opened a path to Heaven Overseeing Tower: "Of course I understand what you are saying. But how can I give up without even trying? Please enter."

Limitless Demon Venerable raised his eyebrows: "Not stopping me anymore?"

Star Constellation's will said expressionlessly: "Since I cannot stop you, what's the point? Limitless, since you want to destroy fate Gu, I will accompany you to see it."

Limitless Demon Venerable was stunned for a moment, a slight smile appeared on his flawless face.

"Interesting." He said softly as he walked up Heaven Overseeing Tower alongside Star Constellation's will, when they arrived at the top, they saw fate Gu.

Not long after, Limitless Demon Venerable left the tower, walking out.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals who were deeply injured became greatly surprised, because Limitless Demon Venerable did not destroy fate Gu. It was still in perfect condition at the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, nobody knew what happened inside the tower, or what Star Constellation's will and Limitless Demon Venerable talked about.

In the end, Limitless Demon Venerable still had a cold expression, but a slight anger could be felt from his gaze.

He looked around, wherever his gaze landed, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals felt a deep chill, their morale fell to rock bottom.

Finally, Limitless Demon Venerable looked at Star Constellation's will: "Hmph, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, you two definitely left many more methods in your lifetimes, are you looking down on me? Use them all, I want to see them myself."

Star Constellation sighed bitterly.

But Limitless Demon Venerable was bent on fighting, she could only entertain him.

Thus, a bloody battle continued.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were sacrificed in Limitless Demon Venerable's hands, countless died.

Wherever Limitless Demon Venerable went, pool of blood and corpses appeared. Star Constellation's will followed behind him, watching calmly as he slaughtered endlessly.

After a while, the water of Forgotten Dao Lake became blood red in color.

Limitless Demon Venerable squinted, the feeling of joy from slaughtering emerged in his heart.

At this moment, he looked at the lake's ripples as he asked: "What lake is this?"

"Forgotten Dao Lake."

"Forgotten Dao Lake? The lake suits the name, it is a good lake. It is too much of a pity if I destroy it." Limitless Demon Venerable suddenly became energetic: "Forgotten Dao, Forgotten Dao, but who can really forget their Dao?"

After some silence, Star Constellation's will said: "Since you already came to Heavenly Court, why don't you take a look around?"

Limitless Demon Venerable looked at Star Constellation's will with deep meaning: "Aren't you afraid that I will destroy Heavenly Court?"

Star Constellation's will was very calm: "You cannot destroy Heavenly Court. Not only will master's supreme methods activate when Heavenly Court faces a fatal crisis, even if you succeed in destroying Heavenly Court, can you destroy fate Gu?"

Saying so, Star Constellation's will showed a solemn expression: "And most importantly, the true Heavenly Court is not here, it is within our hearts. Even if Heavenly Court is destroyed, a new generation will rebuild it. Limitless, you can't live forever right?"

Limitless Demon Venerable stood silently on the spot, staring at Star Constellation's will as his gaze became icy cold.

Star Constellation's will looked straight at him with a calm expression.

A long while later, Limitless Demon Venerable nodded: "As expected of Star Constellation, you are absolutely right."

Star Constellation's will felt no surprise: "Let's continue the tour?"

Limitless Demon Venerable went up Star Zone Mountain, he saw a pavilion at the peak.

It was naturally an Immortal Gu House.

Limitless Demon Venerable stepped into the pavilion, looking down at the whole of Heavenly Court, other than the bloody road that he created through his slaughter until now, the other areas were still grand and elegant.

Limitless Demon Venerable breathed in deeply, he was revitalized: "This is a good pavilion, what is its name?"

"Imperfection Regret Pavilion." Star Constellation's will answered.

Limitless Demon Venerable's eyes shined, this rank eight Immortal Gu House had no secret in front of him, he could understand the profundity and structure of the construct at first glance.

He nodded: "Imperfection Regret Pavilion, it is a good name, it is quite appropriate."

"Regret, regret, I could not accomplish my goal in this trip, it is truly a great regret. But whose life can be perfect without imperfection or regrets?"

He seemed to be asking Star Constellation's will, but he also looked like he was mumbling to himself, his tone was quite complex.

Star Constellation's will was silent.

Limitless Demon Venerable suddenly laughed as his expression vanished, he became cold and aloof again.

He clapped: "Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, these are truly impressive arrangements. However, my interest is piqued again."

Star Constellation's will had a change of expression.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangement was not just the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, in truth, Forgotten Dao Lake and Imperfection Regret Pavilion were also part of her meticulous set up.

Limitless Demon Venerable was invincible in the world, he could not be blocked, the only way to preserve Heavenly Court was by eliminating his killing intent and fighting spirit.

In this aspect, wisdom path Gu Immortals were the most proficient.

Even though Limitless Demon Venerable was affected by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, his fighting spirit only fell for a moment before it returned.

Limitless Demon Venerable did not attack again, he looked at Star Constellation's will: "I was born in the wrong era, it is a pity that I cannot be part of the great era a million years later. Star Constellation, the same applies for you, in that case, I have a suggestion."

"Please go ahead."

"Why don't we play a game of chess in this pavilion."

"Chess?" Star Constellation's will was stunned: "Sure, both of us need this chessboard after all."

For the next few days, Limitless Demon Venerable stayed inside Imperfection Regret Pavilion as he played chess with Star Constellation's will.

When Limitless Demon Venerable left, Star Constellation's will also vanished within the pavilion. Imperfection Regret Pavilion thus became a forbidden area of Heavenly Court.

During normal times, Imperfection Regret Pavilion would have no commotion. But at times, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals would be able to see two vague figures inside the pavilion.

Regardless of what angle they were at, they could only see the sides of these two people. One was male and the other was female, they resembled Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Limitless Demon Venerable.

But any Heavenly Court Gu Immortal who saw this sight would usually die days later. The lucky few who survived would feel an absurd increase in their strength.

Years later.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable went to Imperfection Regret Pavilion and wanted to get rid of this threat, but in the end, he shook his head as he left Star Zone Mountain.

Many years passed again.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was invited to tour Heavenly Court. He saw Embroidered Tower, he saw the three pieces of bloody skins left by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, he entered Heaven Overseeing Tower and saw fate Gu. Finally, he came here but did not ascend the mountain, he only took a look at Imperfection Regret Pavilion before he left.

These records flashed by Duke Long's mind in an instant.

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is very crafty, he must have noticed something back then. Why is Bing Sai Chuan able to mobilize the power that Limitless Demon Venerable left behind?"

Duke Long thought about it rapidly, he wanted to stop Bing Sai Chuan but he had no method to do so.

He acutely sensed that a profound aura had emerged from Bing Sai Chuan's body before it vanished without a trace.

Far away, at the peak of Star Zone Mountain.

Two shadows that were playing chess appeared on the empty Imperfection Regret Pavilion, along with their chessboard.

Even though only their sides could be seen, it was still possible to see that the female had unparalleled beauty, while the male had a cold expression.

It was the scene of two venerables plotting against each other!

Ripples appeared in the air, the still image of the two venerables started to turn bright.

Star Constellation had a complex gaze, raising her head to look at Limitless: "The person you are waiting for is here?"

Limitless Demon Venerable shook his head, sighing: "He is not here yet, but there is someone from my homeland who has inherited one of my true inheritances, I have to help him."

Saying so, he lifted a chess piece from the board and flicked it.

In the entire process, Limitless Demon Venerable did not even take a look at the battlefield, much less turn around.

The chess piece flew out of Imperfection Regret Pavilion as the image of the two venerables faded away, only an empty Imperfection Regret Pavilion was left.

The chess piece flew at a shocking speed, it landed on Duke Long almost instantly.

Duke Long's body shook intensely, shock expressed all over his face.

Plop.

At the next moment, Duke Long fell from the air, crashing on the ground.

The power of the chess piece materialized as illusory silver-white chains, tying him up and stabbing into his phantom aperture, sealing all of his Gu worms.

Duke Long's eyes were wide opened, he could breathe normally but could not move an inch.

He found that even though his strength was still around, whenever he tried to break free, the chains would emit similar strength that canceled out all of his effort.

This was a rank nine immortal killer move!

Duke Long was forcefully restrained, the dragon qi he created also dispersed. Calamity Luck Altar and Bing Sai Chuan regained their freedom.

Bing Sai Chuan shouted loudly as he charged at Duke Long, but the strongest killer move that he used was easily blocked by the silvery chains the moment it reached Duke Long.

Duke Long was unharmed.

Bing Sai Chuan's heart sank: "This rank nine killer move restricts Duke Long but also protects him. Because this is a battle between venerables, even though there is Limitless Demon Venerable's strength, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's will is also involved?"

Since he could not kill Duke Long, Bing Sai Chuan gave up that idea immediately.

He jumped into Calamity Luck Altar and at the next moment, Calamity Luck Altar moved and the Central Great Hall was smashed to bits!

Fairy Zi Wei could only bring Old Man Zheng Yuan away as they escaped rapidly.

Chapter 1715: Heavenly Court Awakens

Fairy Zi Wei's expression was grim.

The Central Great Hall was the control area of Heavenly Court's palaces, now that it was destroyed, Fairy Zi Wei's control fell drastically! She would need to expend a lot of time and effort to mobilize them now.

But in intense battles like this, every breath of time was precious.

The Central Great Hall became a pile of rubbles, ahead of Calamity Luck Altar was a tall tower.

"Heaven Overseeing Tower!" Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan had a heated gaze.

Heaven Overseeing Tower was famous in the world, all Gu Immortals in the five regions knew about it. Right now, it was still and motionless, a refinement path immortal formation was shining in bright light, enveloping it.

"Fate Gu is at the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, it is being repaired using the refinement path formation!" Bing Sai Chuan frowned.

Heavenly Court's defenses were very tight, Heaven Overseeing Tower was actually the final line of defense.

The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was not over yet, but only the finals were left. Because countless Gu Masters failed in their Gu refinement, there was already many success dao marks inside Infallible blessed land.

These dao marks were taken by Heavenly Court, they used them to repair fate Gu, ensuring that nothing went wrong in the process.

"We cannot directly destroy this refinement path formation, otherwise, fate Gu's recovery might be ruined due to the backlash, it will return to its originally injured state. We need to go in and snatch it!" Thinking of this, Bing Sai Chuan gave orders to Five Elements Grandmaster and Bull Demon.

Bull Demon acknowledged the order while Five Elements Grandmaster became hesitant: "Lord Bing Sai Chuan, there might be a slight problem. If we gain a good chance to snatch fate Gu but it has not been repaired fully yet, what do we do?"

This was a problem indeed.

Heavenly Court had methods to restore fate Gu, they were relying on human path killer moves, the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, and a vast number of failures to create the success dao marks in Infallible blessed land that could be used to repair fate Gu.

Longevity Heaven did not have such methods.

Bing Sai Chuan looked at Five Elements Grandmaster, at this point in time, there was no need for any concealment, he said the truth: "We want fate Gu in such a state. It had been repaired by Heavenly Court for countless years, it is near complete recovery now. This is the fate Gu that we want."

"A fully repaired fate Gu cannot be used by anyone. Even Heavenly Court can only use it through Immortal Gu House Heaven Overseeing Tower, to look at the fate of all lifeforms in this world. If anyone can truly control fate Gu, they will be able to decide the traces of fate, they will be able to manipulate the lives of all beings. It is a pity, even though the venerables of past generations tried so, none of them have ever succeeded."

Five Elements Grandmaster was curious: "In that case, what is the point of snatching an incomplete fate Gu?"

Bing Sai Chuan smiled lightly: "We cannot control fate Gu, the reason that the past venerables came up with was that the activation of fate Gu has a high requirement, only heaven's will can control it. But this does not mean that we cannot use fate Gu itself."

"Heavenly Court's Heaven Overseeing Tower is the best example. They are able to make use of fate Gu, even though it is a minor usage."

"Other than that, Heavenly Court has another method, that is to use fate Gu as an immortal material to refine it with a luck path Immortal Gu and create destiny Gu!"

"Destiny Gu?" Five Elements Grandmaster's pupils shrunk.

Bing Sai Chuan's smile widened: "That is the reason why Heavenly Court invaded Northern Plains to try and snatch fortune rivalling heaven Gu for themselves."

"So that's it." Five Elements Grandmaster realized.

Bing Sai Chuan continued: "But they do not know that the so called destiny Gu was first conceptualized by Ancestor Giant Sun. Heavenly Court wants to refine rank ten destiny Gu in one go, they are too ambitious. We are different, we only want a rank nine destiny Gu, thus, the fate Gu that we use does not need to be fully restored."

"As long as we have rank nine destiny Gu, my Longevity Heaven will be able to contest Heavenly Court. In the following great era, we will dominate and replace Heavenly Court, we will reign over the five regions, we can even become the supreme rulers of all beings in this world!"

Five Elements Grandmaster was tongue-tied, Longevity Heaven's ambition was shocking, but he was also in deep admiration towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's plan: "So Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already planned for Heavenly Court's invasion long ago, Longevity Heaven only used the arrangements today!"

Hearing Bing Sai Chuan's explanation and encouragement, Five Elements Grandmaster hesitated no more, he went with Bull Demon as they flew out towards the refinement path formation.

Heaven Overseeing Tower was at the center of the formation, they had to charge up to the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower to take away fate Gu.

"They've entered the formation!" Old Man Zheng Yuan watched from afar, he had a worried expression.

Fairy Zi Wei was not too worried: "This refinement path formation was specially set up, it is not the Refinement Cauldron formation from earlier, not only is Yuan Qiong Du inside, there are two other rank eights helping with the Gu refinement."

Even though the Refinement Cauldron formation was effective in repairing fate Gu, because it was a copy of Lang Ya blessed land's Refinement Cauldron, Heavenly Court stopped using it.

After all, Longevity Heaven had already annexed Lang Ya Sect, they already had information of the Immortal Gu House Refinement Cauldron.

Inside the refinement path formation, Yuan Qiong Du was the main person in charge, he had to concentrate and could not leave. The two Heavenly Court rank eights helping him could temporarily stop their work and help protect Yuan Qiong Du.

Thoughts flickered in Fairy Zi Wei's mind continuously: "Since Longevity Heaven sent people to invade the formation, they must be trying to snatch fate Gu and not destroy it, that's why they are acting so cautiously. Only otherworldly demons can destroy fate Gu, while Fang Yuan is at Emperor City now, we still have time."

Thinking of this, Fairy Zi Wei did not join the battle, instead, she placed Old Man Zheng Yuan under protection.

Old Man Zheng Yuan only had rank seven cultivation level, he could not participate in the fight. But he had a crucial use, he was the key to using Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's human path methods!

After making sure Old Man Zheng Yuan was safe, Fairy Zi Wei returned to the battlefield.

Calamity Luck Altar was floating in the air, blocking the entrance to the refinement path formation.

Within the formation space, Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster were already fighting against the two Heavenly Court rank eights.

With a cry, Fairy Zi Wei had countless thoughts rain down like a meteor storm, crashing towards Calamity Luck Altar.

This was an extraordinary immortal killer move, with the amplification of Star Constellation Chessboard, even Calamity Luck Altar could not ignore it.

Bing Sai Chuan healed his injuries while he controlled Calamity Luck Altar to resist Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei's Star Constellation Chessboard was also a rank eight Immortal Gu House created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, while Calamity Luck Altar was created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The fight between two Immortal Gu Houses was also akin to the fight between Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

At once, the scene was intense.

Both sides went all out with their abilities, rank eight immortal killer moves had incredible power, but thankfully Heavenly Court was defended by past venerables' methods, it was not destroyed.

As the battle went on, Fairy Zi Wei's breathing became heavier.

Even though she controlled Star Constellation Chessboard, it was tiny and could be held in one hand. Compared to it, Calamity Luck Altar was huge and blocked the formation entirely, it had an advantage.

During this time, Fairy Zi Wei also wanted to save Duke Long.

But Duke Long was bound by silvery chains made by Limitless Demon Venerable's method, once Fairy Zi Wei got close, she felt a strong repulsion force. Any immortal killer move she used was also dispelled by the chains.

Thankfully, this was a form of protection for Duke Long, even though he was in the battlefield, he was completely unharmed. Meanwhile, the palaces around him were turned into ruins, there were many crevices and pits all over the area.

"Damn it, damn it!" Duke Long gritted his teeth, he continued to struggle but there was no effect.

"This is not going well." Fairy Zi Wei had a heavy heart, she was engaged in a long fight, she could not help Yuan Qiong Du who was inside the formation.

Even though Longevity Heaven did not bring many Gu Immortals, all of them who came were rank eight elites, they had their respective roles.

At this rate, they might really be able to take fate Gu away.

Right when Fairy Zi Wei felt helpless against the situation, a corner of Heavenly Court shook intensely, auras started to grow from nowhere, rapidly expanding.

"That is… the immortal graveyard!" Fairy Zi Wei was overjoyed.

Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard had countless rank eight experts. It was unfathomable, not even Fairy Zi Wei knew how many rank eights were sleeping there.

At the critical moment, Heavenly Court finally expended its foundation, the slumbering Gu Immortals sensed it and awakened from their slumber!

"You dare attack my Heavenly Court, you are courting death!" With an explosive voice, a muscular Gu Immortal with a bear head jumped up, his body flying into the sky as his cold gaze stared at Calamity Luck Altar.

While he said that, his figure vanished on the spot.

"Such speed!" Bing Sai Chuan was shocked.

At the next moment, with a loud crash, Calamity Luck Altar fell like a toppling mountain, it was sent flying by a huge force.

A huge black bear that was even larger than Calamity Luck Altar stood at where it was blocking earlier.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes shined brightly: "This is Senior Zhang Fei Xiong, a transformation path great expert of Heavenly Court! He is most skilled in bear-type transformations, his strength can rival mountains, his power can move the earth."

"The juniors are too useless, outsiders actually managed to attack Heavenly Court so deeply, hmm? Central Great Hall was destroyed?" A voice resounded again.

An old Gu Immortal appeared in the air.

He had a pale face and thin body, he looked like he was sick. Right now, he sat on a wheelchair, his body seemed weak but his eyes shined with cold light, it made people feel fear and worry.

"Ah." Fairy Zi Wei gasped: "Lord Gu Liu Ru. Sigh, he is a time path great expert, if he had woken earlier to defend the River of Time, taking the place of Senior Li Huang, Fang Yuan would not have escaped!"

Calamity Luck Altar flew into the sky again, as Gu Liu Ru pointed his finger at it.

The entire rank eight Immortal Gu House started to move several times as slowly!

Zhang Fei Xiong laughed loudly as he pounced, crashing into Calamity Luck Altar as he pressed down on it, suppressing it.

"Who woke me up? Sigh, I am so old, if I sleep any less, I will get more wrinkles, I will be ugly! Little sister, don't you agree?" A beautiful figure appeared beside Fairy Zi Wei all of a sudden.

Fairy Zi Wei was taken aback, she did not sense anything.

"Junior greets Senior Wan Zi Hong." Fairy Zi Wei bowed respectfully.

"Don't call me senior, call me sister. Look, are there more wrinkles near my eyes now?" This newly awakened female immortal got close to Fairy Zi Wei as she asked with deep concern.

Fairy Zi Wei looked at the snow-white, beautiful and flawless face, she was speechless but her expression became very polite: "There are no wrinkles, Wan… sister, you are too worried."

She was very cautious.

Because this female immortal Wan Zi Hong did not have an ordinary background.

Most of Heavenly Court's members were chosen from Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, but this Wan Zi Hong was once a great demon that wreaked havoc in Western Desert, she was absorbed by Heavenly Court to become one of its members.

Zhang Fei Xiong, Gu Liu Ru, Wan Zi Hong… one by one, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals woke up from the immortal graveyard.

At once, the numbers on each side became tilted, the situation changed drastically.

"So many reinforcements at once? Are there more?" Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly.

In this dangerous situation, he was still able to laugh.

Fairy Zi Wei had a bad feeling, since Longevity Heaven was attacking Heavenly Court, how could they not expect the situation in the immortal graveyard?

"Do you know why I bought Calamity Luck Altar? Because the killer move of a former Demon Venerable is in it." At this moment, Bing Sai Chuan's gaze became deep and unfathomable.

But what method gave him such confidence?

Chapter 1716: Number One Battle Strength Among Legendary Immemorial Beasts

Hidden Dragon Cave battlefield.

The super immortal formation suppressing Di Zang Sheng was broken by Eastern Sea's rank eights, it was half collapsed, only the central core area was still active.

Old Man Bei Feng was heavily injured, he could barely hold down the situation. His grandson Feng Chan Zi was beside him, waiting for Heavenly Court's reinforcements to no avail. The despair on Feng Chan Zi's face became increasingly deep.

Outside the central area, Eastern Sea's rank eights completely surrounded this formation.

Hua clan first supreme elder Hua Cai Yun let out an immemorial cloud beast, it continued to dwindle away at the formation's core.

"This is Heavenly Court's creation after all, even just the core of the formation can resist my cloud beast's corrosion." Hua Cai Yun sighed.

Roar—!

At this time, a loud dragon roar could be heard from deep within the abyss, it was ground shaking.

Sound waves reverberated, causing the entire Earth Trench to tremor, countless rocks started to fall off the Earth Trench's cliffs.

Eastern Sea's rank eights looked at the abyss below them worriedly, Shen Cong Sheng urged: "The formation is half destroyed, it cannot suppress Di Zang Sheng anymore, to avoid problems, we need to act now."

Di Zang Sheng was a very unique legendary immemorial desolate beast. Because it was created from the power of Central Continent's earth veins, it was born from endless hatred, anger, and grudges.

Thus, it bore natural hatred and killing intent towards humans, and most importantly, unless its source was destroyed, it would never die. It had once caused great trouble to Heavenly Court, Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals did not want to fight Di Zang Sheng for no reason. They wanted to take away Dragon Palace to regain their reputation, if Di Zang Sheng was released, it would continue to find trouble with Heavenly Court and Central Continent.

"It is ready." Song Qi Yuan nodded.

"Puff." He muttered lightly.

Immortal killer move — Broken Mirror Shard Light.

Crack!

With a loud sound resembling a mirror falling on the ground and shattering into countless pieces.

The entire formation core area's light halo also shattered like a mirror, exposing Old Man Bei Feng and Feng Chan Zi who were inside.

"No!" Feng Chan Zi was so scared he quickly screamed and moved back.

Song Qi Yuan's killer move was very special, it created no commotion when used at first, only after a long period of nurturing would it catch people off-guard and create an unexpected result.

This broken mirror shard light was Song Qi Yuan's proud method, it was mostly used against stationary enemies like formations.

The formation broke, Di Zang Sheng growled loudly, the sound waves created shook the entire Earth Trench.

"Quick, make use of the time!" Eastern Sea's rank eights attacked.

"I am going to die!" Feng Chan Zi fell backwards, he was so scared he shut his eyes, shivering with a distorted expression, awaiting his death.

Old Man Bei Feng sighed deeply, he could not fight anymore, the difference in strength was too big, he could only wait for his death.

"Don't kill him, let me capture him alive." Shen Cong Sheng suddenly said.

Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals halted their attacks, they were quite surprised, did Shen Cong Sheng have a method to capture a rank eight Gu Immortal alive?

"Everyone, take a good look." Shen Cong Sheng smiled confidently: "Go."

The Eastern Sea immortals saw that countless threads appeared around Old Man Bei Feng's body, he was wrapped up like a cocoon.

"This is a new killer move that I created recently, it is called lingering sound!" Shen Cong Sheng explained.

Old Man Bei Feng had a furious expression, he was already prepared for death, but these Eastern Sea Gu Immortals actually wanted to capture him alive, it was a great humiliation.

Eastern Sea's immortals were quiet.

It seemed like Shen Cong Sheng could really capture rank eight Gu Immortals. Even though Old Man Bei Feng was defenseless at the moment, Shen Cong Sheng's method was still quite threatening.

Rank eight Gu Immortals had very deep foundations, it was evident from seeing Shen Cong Sheng's method.

Old Man Bei Feng could not resist, as for Feng Chan Zi, he was already shivering from fear, Eastern Sea's immortals did not even bother with this cowardly rank six immortal.

Shen Cong Sheng used his immortal killer move to its limit and captured Old Man Bei Feng. The value of a living rank eight Gu Immortal was much higher than a dead one. Forget about the rest, just the reputation gained from capturing a great expert of the same rank was enough for Shen Cong Sheng and the entire Shen clan's reputation to soar in Eastern Sea!

The other immortals started to look for Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace.

They had come here together for this rank eight Immortal Gu House.

Soon, Zhang Yin found something.

"Over there!" He pointed with an excited expression, before using an investigative immortal killer move.

After using the killer move, an Immortal Gu House appeared, it floated above everyone's head, it was several tens of meters on top of Old Man Bei Feng.

The Eastern Sea immortals were overjoyed, what else but Dragon Palace could this be?

Other than Shen Cong Sheng, the other Eastern Sea immortals quickly gathered with an excited expression.

Shen Cong Sheng concentrated on dealing with Old Man Bei Feng, he felt no anxiety. Before coming here, the Eastern Sea immortals had already set an alliance agreement, it had quite the binding force. The rule was: If Eastern Sea's immortals obtain Dragon Palace, everyone would get a share. As for the share, it would depend on how much effort they put in.

Since Dragon Palace appeared, Song Qi Yuan and the rest started to try and capture it.

But after using several killer moves, Dragon Palace only shook, it did not acknowledge a new owner.

"This Immortal Gu House is really extraordinary!" Dragon Palace's fierce resistance made the Eastern Sea immortals even more excited, their desire for Dragon Palace rose even more.

Gradually, while trying to capture it, they realized a huge secret.

"So that's it."

"Heavenly Court placed Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace here to try and tame Di Zang Sheng!"

"Even though Di Zang Sheng was born from the earth vein and negative emotions, it is still considered a dragon, it is countered by Dragon Palace, thus there is a possibility of subduing it."

"Duke Long has a good plan indeed! Now that the five regions' earth veins are becoming one, and Di Zang Sheng's power comes from the earth vein, once they combine, Di Zang Sheng's power will rise by at least five times!"

"Don't forget, when the earth veins become one and the five regional walls vanish, the world would be in chaos and conflict, by then, there will be a great amount of fear, hatred, jealousy, and other emotions. With that, Di Zang Sheng's strength will rise again."

Eastern Sea's immortals conversed as some gasped.

At this rate, among the legendary immemorial desolate beasts, Di Zang Sheng might become the number one among them.

It already had peak rank eight battle strength to begin with, after the boost, it might even be able to reach pseudo-Immortal Venerable!

"No wonder Duke Long paid a huge price to obtain Dragon Palace, he wanted to subdue a pseudo-Immortal Venerable battle strength to suppress the situation."

"Thankfully we came to stop Heavenly Court's plan, otherwise, we will have trouble during the five regions chaotic war."

Eastern Sea's immortals were very glad.

"No wonder we could only hear dragon roars even though the formation broke, Di Zang Sheng has not escaped yet."

"Right now, Dragon Palace is suppressing Di Zang Sheng, we need to wait a bit more."

"That's right, after Dragon Palace subdues Di Zang Sheng, not only would we gain a rank eight Immortal Gu House, we will also gain an existence with great battle strength."

"If Heavenly Court finds out, they would probably puke blood."

"Hahaha, truly fantastic, fantastic."

Emperor City battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

Fang Yuan activated it in succession, Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses avoided them wherever the ghost hands went.

Great thief ghost hand could steal Gu worms, Fang Yuan could use this killer move to steal rank eight Immortal Gu, even if they were hiding inside the grotto-heavens of Gu Immortals.

The essence of Immortal Gu Houses was the combination of Gu worms to create a stable form. It could be seen as a combination of many killer moves, or a mobile immortal formation.

Be it immortal killer move, Immortal Gu House, or immortal formation, they were all ways to use Gu worms. Even though they appear different, the essence was the same.

Great thief ghost hand could even steal Gu worms inside immortal apertures, not to mention Immortal Gu Houses which were essentially mobile immortal formations that exposed their Gu worms on the outside.

Undeniably, great thief ghost hand countered Immortal Gu Houses!

Fang Yuan relied on great thief ghost hand to attack, managing to steal many Gu worms.

He had targeted Immortal Gu Houses before, but that was Great Space Temple which had a method that resisted great thief ghost hand. In truth, most Immortal Gu Houses did not have a way to counter Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand.

The Immortal Gu House defense line that Heavenly Court meticulously created became a huge mess because of Fang Yuan's interference and influence.

"Scoundrel Fang Yuan, accept your death!" At the critical moment, Li Huang shouted as he pounced at Fang Yuan with verdant sun flame cloak on him.

Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses could not deal with Fang Yuan, but their Gu Immortals could.

It was much harder for great thief ghost hand to steal Immortal Gu from immortal apertures than Immortal Gu Houses!

Especially when Li Huang had verdant sun flame cloak, it could defend against Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand.

Fang Yuan saw that Li Huang had approached him, he advanced instead of retreating: "Li Huang, you finally showed up at long last, I've been waiting for you!"

At the next moment, Fang Yuan turned into the immemorial year monkey and spitted.

Instantly, spring scissors killer move flew out, tearing through space as it targeted Li Huang.

Next, Fang Yuan breathed in deeply as the monkey grabbed empty space with both hands, pulling out a huge fan out of nowhere.

It was immortal killer move — Summer Fan.

Snip!

"What?!" Li Huang had a shocked gaze as the cloak on his back became torn, its defense was greatly lowered.

Fan!

Whoosh!

Intense winds blew, the world changed colors.

Li Huang was hit as he flew far away due to the wind.

"How did his strength rise so drastically?" Li Huang looked at the tiny spark left on his verdant sun flame cloak as he showed an ugly expression.

Because when he got attacked earlier, he saw that the situation was bad and activated verdant sun flame cloak once again.

This fire path defensive killer move had a great attribute, it could be used consecutively and stacked. The weakness was that the expended immortal essence would be twice as high!

Chapter 1717: Call of the Ancient

"Li Huang, don't tell me this is your full strength!" Fang Yuan roared, his body moved like a flash, rampaging in the battlefield, chasing after Li Huang.

Li Huang retreated as he activated verdant sun flame cloak again and again.

Spring scissors continued to fly around him, cutting up all of the flame cloaks on his back.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with sharp light, the immortal killer move's aura surged for an instant.

"Damn it!" Li Huang sensed something and became alert, he quickly changed directions.

Fang Yuan's time path killer move did not hit Li Huang, his battle experience was too rich.

"Lord Li Huang, let us help you!" At this moment, Wind Sweeping Building came to reinforce him.

It was surrounded by a wall of wind, it could resist great thief ghost hand to some extent.

Fang Yuan snickered with disdain: "Get lost!"

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Tornadoes swept all over the place, Wind Sweeping Building was forced to a halt. There was no choice, summer fan's wind was just an appearance, the true essence was time path's power. Wind Sweeping Building was a wind path Immortal Gu House, it was not good against such time path killer moves.

Li Huang could only continue to escape.

Fang Yuan's strength had risen absurdly, it was shocking to everyone.

Inside Emperor City, the Gu Masters continued with the final competition. The Gu Immortals guarding Emperor City had already isolated all of the noise outside, these Gu Masters could concentrate on refining Gu.

"To think that even Lord Li Huang is not this demon Fang Yuan's match!"

"This demon is too impressive, he had obtained many venerable inheritances, his demonic might is truly terrifying. But don't worry, even though Emperor City is a mortal Gu House, it contains human path methods, at the crucial moment, immortal killer moves will protect us all."

The Gu Immortals encouraged each other and raised their morale.

Emperor City was the number one city of humanity, it used a vast number of mortal Gu to build. Even though the city had relocated a dozen times and was no longer at its original spot, it had an immensely long history, it could be traced back to the era where humanity rose, this was the first Emperor City built as a result of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's decision.

"Fang Yuan, don't be too arrogant, face me instead!" Rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye saw that the situation was bad, he had to enter the battle.

Li Huang saw the chance and did not escape, he fought alongside Qing Ye.

Fang Yuan shouted loudly, he disregarded the immortal essence expenditure and activated killer moves targeting Emperor City.

Li Huang and Qing Ye blocked Fang Yuan from the front, but after his barrage of attacks, they were forced to move back.

This sight made the Western Desert Gu Immortals go into a daze.

"Fang Yuan is so ferocious!"

"No wonder he could oppose Heavenly Court for so many years and still remain unharmed."

"We will detour around him, try not to provoke this person."

"That's right, we will focus on destroying Emperor City!"

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

"Farewell friend wind! This is actually farewell friend wind!!" Seeing Wu Yong's move succeed against Chen Yi, the Central Continent Gu Immortals defending the immortal formation felt deep fear within them.

This farewell friend wind had an incredible origin, it was created by a peculiar genius.

This peculiar genius was named Daoist Black Heart, he cultivated wind path but gained a lot of insight from reading <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> during his later years. After nearly ten years of closed cultivation, he created farewell friend wind killer move.

This was a wind path method that had the profundities of human path, its power was extraordinary!

After creating this move, Daoist Black Heart started to make friends all over the place, he often sacrificed his own gains for his friends. Initially, the five regions' Gu Immortals did not know the reason, they were very friendly towards Daoist Black Heart who often gave them expensive gifts. Even those who did not want to befriend Daoist Black Heart were unwilling to antagonize him, they pretended to be friendly with him.

But it was all Daoist Black Heart's scheme!

Any killer move had a process of sensing the target.

Like Fang Yuan's lead soul into dream killer move, it needed the sense the enemy's soul. Otherwise, this killer move could not be used.

Even if many Gu Immortals cannot unravel immortal killer moves, they can target this process and defend themselves.

But farewell friend wind was special.

It could only sense friends and target them.

The 'friend' here did not refer to just true friends, even fake friends or superficial friends with ill intentions were detectable.

Using this move, Daoist Black Heart became renowned in the five regions, he was extremely famous and nobody dared to provoke him.

Afterwards, when many people got attacked by it, through the deductions of wisdom path Gu Immortals, the truth behind farewell friend wind was finally exposed.

Many Gu Immortals who learned of farewell friend wind's secret scolded Daoist Black Heart for his vicious heart. Countless people who once called Daoist Black Heart their friend started to shudder in fear and unease.

In this world, there were no invincible killer moves.

Soon, one of farewell friend wind's weaknesses was exposed. To activate it, the user had to directly touch the body of the target Gu Immortal.

Even though farewell friend wind was strong, with these two problems, it became easier to deal with.

Even though Daoist Black Heart became very famous and renowned, he became extremely lonely in his final years, everyone avoided him like the plague. Towards the end of his life, he was all alone, it was a bitter ending.

Wu Yong's possession of farewell friend wind shocked all of the immortals here.

But regardless, Wu Yong succeeded and Chen Yi was hit.

He was going to die!

Everyone realized this.

Bai Cang Shui shrieked as she charged at Wu Yong.

Wu Yong's body flickered as he vanished on the spot.

Bai Cang Shui grabbed onto Chen Yi, even though he was no longer floating, he could not move, even his eyebrows and skin started to erode.

Wu Yong appeared before the Southern Border immortals again.

This time, the Southern Alliance immortals looked at him with a complex gaze, there were wariness, fear, and respect all in their eyes.

"Wu Yong possesses farewell friend wind killer move, it is equivalent to Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal. This is a trump card that can change the situation around once it is used."

"Since when did Wu Yong become friends with Chen Yi?"

"How hard can it be? When doing business in treasure yellow heaven, wouldn't everyone call each other friends anyway? Compared to that, I am more worried about Wu Yong's schemes."

Wu Yong still stood in front of the Southern Alliance immortals, he looked at Chen Yi who was far away, praising: "As expected of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal, the former first supreme elder of Heavenly Lotus Sect. Your defense is incredible, this is the first time I've seen anyone disintegrate so slowly from my farewell friend wind."

He seemed to be praising the enemy but he was also flaunting his own battle strength.

The Southern Alliance Gu Immortals quickly responded.

"That's right, there had never been anyone who survived a hit from farewell friend wind!"

"Chen Yi is dead meat."

"With Lord Wu Yong around, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals are just a disoriented bunch after all."

Heavenly Court battlefield.

Inside the Gu refinement formation.

Two huge battles were underway.

"Spear!" Heavenly Court's rank eight Che Wei shouted.

Immediately, a gigantic black spear that was the size of an ancient tree shot towards Five Elements Grandmaster.

"Arrow." Che Wei shouted again.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Countless arrows appeared out of nowhere, they rained down and enveloped Five Elements Grandmaster.

But Five Elements Grandmaster remained standing, even though he was attacked endlessly, he still had the time to talk: "Impressive, Che Wei, you are about to create a new path, these killer moves are very interesting. But it is useless, you cannot break the protection of my five elements ring."

"Blade." Che Wei ignored Five Elements Grandmaster, he held a large blade and charged up to fight Five Elements Grandmaster in close combat.

At the same time, at another battle.

Bull Demon took the initiative to attack while Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal Cong Yan defended himself.

Bull Demon's attacks were ferocious, each movement created layers of phantom shadows. These shadows were able to attack and by cooperating with Bull Demon, he could often unleash terrifying attacks that were unexpected.

Each time Cong Yan was hit, his body would vibrate.

He cultivated rule path, there were countless blue lines on his skin, resembling tattoos. These lines were either thin or thick, some crisscrossed and formed a web that protected Cong Yan tightly.

"It seems that they can't get past for the time being." Yuan Qiong Du was still refining Gu, his heart eased slightly.

"Longevity Heaven's duo chose close combat, they are purposely restraining their attacks because they fear that they might destroy the refinement path formation and cause my efforts to be in vain."

"It seems that they want to snatch fate Gu, they have a certain requirement towards fate Gu's recovery."

Yuan Qiong Du was made a member of Heavenly Court, he was naturally very shrewd, he quickly analyzed Longevity Heaven's intention.

"Calm down, I must calm down, otherwise, if I make any human mistakes, even the success dao marks cannot help me."

"Persevere!"

"Gu Immortals are awakening in the immortal graveyard, our battle strength will continue to rise, Longevity Heaven will be forced to despair."

Yuan Qiong Du was thinking about that when suddenly, Bing Sai Chuan smiled coldly: "Do you know why I bought Calamity Luck Altar? Because the killer move of a former Demon Venerable is in it."

As he said that, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were already attacking Calamity Luck Altar together.

But soon, a golden light burst out of Calamity Luck Altar.

Next, the sound of waves emerged around the entire battlefield.

The phantom image of a segment of the grand River of Time appeared above Calamity Luck Altar.

Next, the immortal killer move activated as figures walked out of the River of Time.

The first person to emerge saw that Calamity Luck Altar was suppressed by a huge bear, he roared in anger: "Your bear guts are huge, eat my exploding lightning!"

Boom!

The giant bear that Zhang Fei Xiong transformed into was forced back by five to six steps, his face had suffered the impact of the explosion, his injuries were deep, blood was all over his face!

"Who are you? Report your name!" A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal attacked the person.

The person laughed maniacally: "You do not even know me, Nu Er Bao Xiong? Then let me show you my exploding lightning killer move, I will blow you to bits, remember my name."

Boom boom boom!

The savage power exploded continuously, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were like kites with their strings cut, they flew out uncontrollably.

Before they landed on the ground, they had already lost consciousness, it was unknown if they were still alive.

"To think that I can use this move to come to the future and participate in a huge battle, I am truly fortunate." The second Northern Plains Gu Immortal who walked out of the phantom River of Time smiled.

He pointed his finger at Calamity Luck Altar, dispelling the time path killer move that was used on it as it regained its speed.

"You broke my killer move! Who are you?" Gu Liu Ru who used the killer move had a dark gaze.

The Northern Plains Gu Immortal smiled as he looked at Gu Liu Ru: "What a coincidence, we both cultivate time path, let us fight. As for my name, it is quite common, I am called Hei Fan."

Next, the third person walked out of the phantom River of Time after Hei Fan.

"Wow! What a huge battle, oh my heaven, I better hide somewhere." The third Northern Plains Gu Immortal had a delicate white face, he had a crafty look.

Saying so, he vanished.

One by one, Northern Plains Gu Immortals walked out and joined the battlefield.

Fairy Zi Wei's heart pounded: "Nu Er Bao Xiong, Hei Fan, and that Liu Liu Liu who vanished, they are all rank eight experts of the Northern Plains Huang Jin tribes! What killer move is this, it can actually bring these people out of the past segment of the River of Time and into battle?"

This killer move was simply too unbelievable, Fairy Zi Wei felt like she was dreaming.

Fairy Zi Wei was confused, but Duke Long was not.

Seeing this, Duke Long's expression froze as his memories surfaced once more.

As the dust clouds settled, Red Lotus spit out blood from his severe injuries, while Duke Long remained standing.

"Red Lotus, are you still not attacking? Even though you have future self, after rebirth you only have rank eight cultivation level. Your current future self is also at rank eight, you are still some distance away from regaining your Immortal Venerable battle strength!" Duke Long had a cold expression, his eyes were spewing fire from rage, burning Red Lotus's heart.

"That's right, my future self killer move has some flaws, but even without flaws, how can I attack you master?" Red Lotus smiled bitterly.

"So that is the reason why you have been avoiding me since the start of the battle instead of attacking me?" Duke Long scoffed: "Red Lotus, if you truly respect me as your master, you should stop fooling around. Accept the arrangement of fate and become a Gu Venerable again, we can forget everything and start anew!"

"Master, I understand your intention, but you do not understand mine." Red Lotus sighed.

Duke Long was even more furious now: "Since you do not want to attack me, and yet you want to continue with this, are you forcing me to kill you?!"

"Of course not." Red Lotus shook his head, a faint smile appearing on his flawless face: "Master, after taking hits for such a long time, my killer move is finally ready, please critique it."

Saying so, the phantom image of the River of Time appeared behind him as Gu Immortals walked out one by one.

Duke Long's expression changed: "What killer move is this?"

"I created a pair of killer moves, they are known as 'call of the ancient, support of the future'. This move can summon Gu Immortals closely related to the user from the River of Time to come forward and battle. I am using the latter move, support of the future, now." Red Lotus smiled lightly.

Duke Long's expression was grim, he was shivering from anger: "Your action is defying heaven and earth, you are actually using the River of Time to interfere with the flow of history, your demonic nature is too deeply rooted! What about the first move? Go ahead and use it."

"No master, the first move, 'call of the ancient', will appear before you in the future at a certain timing." Red Lotus smiled as he said.

Chapter 1718: Heavenly Court's Chaotic Battle

Heavenly Court battlefield.

Figures danced in the sky or fought on the ground.

Intense explosions continued to resound, sparks were flying, bright lights were flashing.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortal experts fought against Heavenly Court's members.

Boom!

In an instant, a loud explosion occurred as the black bear that was large as a mountain lost its right shoulder, a huge piece of flesh went missing, even its shoulder bone was shattered.

The black bear had a painful expression as it shut its eyes, it had fainted from the explosion.

Rumble!

Next, its body fell like a mountain, in the end, a huge pit was formed on the ground.

Above it, a Northern Plains Gu Immortal was laughing in the sky: "The killer move twilight lightning that I, Nu Er Bao Xiong, possess is not so easy to deal with. Even if your transformation path grants you strong defenses, I have already killed so many transformation path Gu Immortals in my life, ahahaha!!"

He cultivated lightning path solely, he was once a brutal slaughterer that roamed Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world unhindered. When he was the first supreme elder of Nu Er tribe, it became the number one force of Northern Plains without doubt.

But Nu Er Bao Xiong's laughter came to a stop as a delightful female voice resounded: "Shameless words, I also cultivate transformation path on the side, come and kill me."

"Which stupid…" Nu Er Bao Xiong had just turned around and spoke when he saw a bright red light flash before him.

Before he reacted, he heard a loud explosion as flames scattered everywhere, dust clouds rose.

He fell from the sky, his body was still burning with blazing flames.

"The time is now, save Zhang Fei Xiong!" Gu Liu Ru who was sitting in a wheelchair shouted as he pointed.

Instantly, the black bear that Zhang Fei Xiong had transformed into flickered with a shining light, his life was preserved.

"Hmph, I like to kill people, not save them!" A shadow tore through the sky, rushing down and approaching Zhang Fei Xiong.

It was Wan Zi Hong, she was extremely beautiful and enchanting, she cultivated wood path and was originally a demonic path Gu Immortal, she had a deep killing nature but was recruited by Heavenly Court.

"This Zhang Fei Xiong is quite impressive, even though he fainted, his transformation did not vanish!" Wan Zi Hong had a look of alertness as she charged into Zhang Fei Xiong's right shoulder wound without stopping.

The moment she went in, Wan Zi Hong scattered into pink petals that landed on the bloody wound.

The flower petals had a dense fragrant smell, flowers started to grow on the bloody wound.

The petals of the flowers fell again on the surrounding flesh, more and more flowers grew as a sea of flowers was formed.

Zhang Fei Xiong's flesh and blood was quickly replenished, he was healing at an observable pace.

"Hmph!" In the sky, Nu Er Bao Xiong had a grim expression. Even though he had strong lightning path killer moves, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were not weak either. Wan Zi Hong's healing method actually got rid of the lightning path dao marks that he landed on Zhang Fei Xiong, he was healing rapidly and effectively. It was as if Wan Zi Hong's wood path dao marks and Zhang Fei Xiong's transformation path dao marks did not conflict with each other.

Nu Er Bao Xiong only took one glance but his enemy made use of that timing to find a weakness.

A flash of red light appeared as Nu Er Bao Xiong got hit again, his body was covered in flames.

Seeing this, Nu Er Bao Xiong gave up on chasing after Zhang Fei Xiong, he shook off the flames and looked at his enemy: "Who are you? As a Heavenly Court member, are you going to hide your appearance and act so shady?"

The red light that was flying in the sky laughed loudly as it flickered left and right without stopping, Nu Er Bao Xiong could only watch without having a chance to land an attack.

"It should be senior Zhu Que Er. She cultivates fire path and transformation path, her battle style counters Nu Er Bao Xiong." Seeing this, Fairy Zi Wei expressed joy on her face.

As time passed, more and more Gu Immortals woke up from the immortal graveyard, Zhu Que Er was one of them.

"But Longevity Heaven's time path killer move is too powerful, it is still summoning more people!" Fairy Zi Wei looked towards Calamity Luck Altar and the phantom River of Time as her heart shook with worry.

"This is likely Red Lotus Demon Venerable's killer move, Lord Duke Long might know something." Fairy Zi Wei had been searching for a chance, she wanted to enter the battlefield and save Duke Long.

But Duke Long's position was not good, he was quite near Calamity Luck Altar, below the phantom River of Time, there were Northern Plains Gu Immortals moving about constantly.

If Fairy Zi Wei charged in to save him, the risks would be huge, and she had her own job to do.

"Earlier, both venerables appeared in Imperfection Regret Pavilion, even though Duke Long was hit by the rank nine killer move and got restricted, his life is not in danger."

"I have an important mission, I need to provide Immortal Gu to the newly awakened Gu Immortals, I also need to protect Old Man Zheng Yuan, he is one of the most important elements of this battle!"

Fairy Zi Wei squinted, she stayed at the back and did not move out.

Duke Long had instructed her earlier before he left, she had to take charge of the situation.

Clang!

A golden light suddenly flickered before Fairy Zi Wei's eyes, when the light faded, a Northern Plains Gu Immortal was seen.

He had dark skin tone and sharp eyes, constantly emitting a brave aura, he was an expert of Ye Lui tribe, Ye Lui Kou, he cultivated metal path and was a great expert part of the second batch who left the River of Time!

When Ye Lui Kou was a youngster, he stood out with his ferocious nature and sharp foresight, he could often see the most important elements of a battle. During the Imperial Court contest, he often fought alone, charging towards an army singlehandedly, killing the enemy's leader under everyone's watchful gaze, he was unstoppable.

After becoming a Gu Immortal, he plundered many places and targeted the enemy's weakness, as a righteous path Gu Immortal, he had a terrible reputation on par with demonic path members. But his reputation changed after reaching rank eight. By that point, everyone in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world feared him, all of the accusations and grudges towards him turned into superficial reverence and slander in secret.

Fairy Zi Wei's heart jumped, facing Ye Lui Kou's gaze, she felt like a rabbit sprinting in the plains, while being targeted by a hawk.

She quickly retreated, her body vanishing among the palaces.

"This damned qi wall!" Ye Lui Kou had an irritated expression.

He had a keen sense towards any battle, he could detect the enemy's weakness and target it with great precision.

This was a talent that he was born with.

But his plan was ruined by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's qi wall killer move that was left in Heavenly Court.

This qi wall killer move could discern enemy and ally, it did not obstruct Heavenly Court's members. But against Longevity Heaven's side, it was a huge problem.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortals could only move around the road that Limitless Demon Venerable created to fight against Heavenly Court.

Precisely so, the fight between rank eights was fixed at a certain area. Heavenly Court had many important places like the Demon Judgment Board or the immortal graveyard, but these places were protected by the qi wall, Northern Plains' Gu Immortals could not go there.

But in the battlefield, Northern Plains' Gu Immortals had the obvious upper hand, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals needed to rely on the qi wall to retreat at times, allowing them to continue this battle.

"Our Gu Immortals had just woken up, they lack compatible Gu worms. Mortal Gu are still fine, but they are lacking many Immortal Gu, this prevents their battle strength from being displayed." Fairy Zi Wei was very worried.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals gave all their Immortal Gu to Heavenly Court while they slept in the immortal graveyard, on one hand, resources had to be optimized, while Heavenly Court also needed to feed the Immortal Gu.

These Immortal Gu were mostly used to construct Immortal Gu Houses, they created the countless pavilions and palaces in Heavenly Court. A small portion was handed out to certain people in the ten sects, for example, Feng Jiu Ge's fate armor Immortal Gu. There were very few Immortal Gu which were truly kept in the treasury on standby.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were all elites among rank eights, but because they lacked Immortal Gu, they could not use their full power, even with abundant immortal essence, they could not change the situation.

In contrast, Northern Plains' side had Red Lotus Demon Venerable's call of the ancient killer move, it was truly magnificent, they were able to go up against Heavenly Court's foundation that was accumulated over countless years.

Duke Long was filled with pain and anger.

At this crucial moment, he could not move, he could only watch as the battle unfolded.

And most importantly, the one who created this situation was the beloved disciple that he had entrusted hope to in the past — Red Lotus Demon Venerable!

Chapter 1719: Death in Formation

"This call of the ancient should be quite similar to support of the future. It is not truly bringing over Gu Immortals from the past or future, it contains profundity similar to future self, it summons certain individuals from the River of Time when they are at a particular state!"

"Precisely so, these Northern Plains Gu Immortals are all at their peak condition, they have all their immortal essence and Immortal Gu."

"To unravel this move, the method should be similar to how I dealt with 'support of the future' back then, you have to interrupt the person using the killer move! Right now, if we can cripple Calamity Luck Altar and accumulate enough damage, we should be able to stop this 'call of the ancient' killer move."

Duke Long was about to break his teeth from gritting, his deduction was not wrong. Unfortunately, he was restrained by the rank nine killer move, he could not communicate with anyone using any method.

"Wow, such a beautiful sight!" Another person walked out of the River of Time, he had a jade-like face, he was elegant and gentlemanly.

The life-and-death battle here was intense, it intoxicated him. He breathed in deeply as he spread his arms, sighing: "It seems that this is the stage for me, Dong Fang Yu!"

"Hmph, Northern Plains brutes will be brutes, why are you pretending to be a gentleman, fight me!" A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal who had just retrieved his Immortal Gu looked at Dong Fang Yu with a look of disdain, he charged over.

He had the appearance of a little boy, he had black hair with a cowlick on top, together with his round and cute face, his head resembled a peach, it was extremely appealing.

But the aura around him was overwhelming, it made Dong Fang Yu's expression change as he dodged.

The boy's killer move missed, seeing Dong Fang Yu's pathetic state, he giggled: "Do you know the power of Vortex Space Boy now?"

Dong Fang Yu was very angry: "My free-spirited nature is real, while you are just a disgusting old man pretending to be young even though you're half a step into your coffin!"

Vortex Space Boy's smile faded away as he charged at Dong Fang Yu.

Dong Fang Yu was merely caught by surprise earlier, now that he was on guard, he retaliated instead of escaping.

Boom!

The two fought and their moves clashed.

Powerful air currents shot towards another Northern Plains Gu Immortal who emerged from the River of Time.

"The wind is really strong, it almost blinded my eyes." This Northern Plains Gu Immortal looked like an old farmer, his pants were rolled up, his legs were covered in mud, his back was hunched, wrinkles covered his face, and there was tobacco in his mouth.

"Sigh sigh." The old farmer had no killing intent, he sighed deeply as he said: "I, Nian Er Nong Fu, cultivate earth path, I am most skilled in managing the immortal aperture."

Rightfully so.

Nian Er Nong Fu might not be the strongest rank eight Gu Immortal in Nian Er tribe history, but his influence was the deepest, he gave Nian Er tribe the greatest benefits.

Because he was skilled in managing immortal apertures, even though Nian Er tribe's territory did not grow, their cultivation resources grew by more than ten times, it was unthinkable!

"Ye Qiao Zi greets friend Nian Er." At this time, A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal appeared, he was also a thin old man.

"You know who I am?" Nian Er Nong Fu asked.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal smiled: "I cultivate wood path, I am also skilled in growing resources. When I was still young, friend Nian Er was one of my goals."

"So that's it." Nian Er Nong Fu smiled.

The two spoke in a harmonious tone, but they had already used their methods to fight, they were even fiercer than the other experts!

As the red light flew around, Nu Er Bao Xiong's expression became solemn, he continued to strike with his palms as lightning explosions occurred continuously.

The red light's aura suddenly expanded, Zhu Que Er had used a killer move, splitting into eight red lights that shot towards Nu Er Bao Xiong from different directions.

Nu Er Bao Xiong snorted coldly, he took a deep breath as a spherical shield resembling a lightning web surrounded and protected him.

Bam bam bam…

Seven red lights slammed into the lightning web shield, causing an intense explosion, the remaining red light was Zhu Que Er's main body.

"My turn." Nu Er Bao Xiong pulled at his own beard.

"Go." Strands of his beard shot out, raining down like a drizzle as they all turned into lightning spears, forming a tight formation as they shot towards Zhu Que Er.

Zhu Que Er shouted loudly, the red light turning back into her body as a rainbow light emerged, the temperature of the surrounding air rose.

Seeing that the two were about to use killer moves, the surrounding Gu Immortals quickly went away.

On the ground, Wan Zi Hong looked up with an expression of admiration, cursing in her heart: "Damn it, I lack most of my offensive Immortal Gu, I have no attacking methods now. To think that I would become a healing Gu Immortal one day, hmm?"

Wan Zi Hong's heart jumped with premonition, her pupils shrunk as she flickered, turning into countless petals and vanishing on the spot.

At the next moment, a golden light flashed past her original location.

Ye Lui Kou appeared on the ground as he snorted coldly, thinking: "Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals are truly elites, I actually missed my attack twice, but unless you escape into the qi wall, you cannot escape!"

Saying so, he pointed with his index finger towards an empty spot.

A golden ball first appeared at his fingertips before it exploded, a grand golden pillar shot out while pushing air aside, its speed was incredible.

"He actually discovered the location of my true body!" Wan Zi Hong wanted to retreat but it was too late.

The golden light was already right behind her, she had no choice but to turn around and defend herself desperately.

Ye Lui Kou snickered, his move was not so easy to block.

But at the next moment, his smile froze.

He saw that the golden light pillar shrunk and went inside a Gu Immortal's mouth.

The Gu Immortal ate Ye Lui Kou's entire killer move as he patted his belly with some lingering desire: "To think that I would get to eat right after waking up."

This Heavenly Court Gu Immortal was quite fat, he had light colored skin and smiled with a satisfied look.

"Who are you!" Ye Lui Kou's gaze was cold.

"Zhao Shan He!" The fat man smiled: "I will not let you kill our healing Gu Immortal so easily."

Ye Lui Kou did not speak, his aura surged as he prepared another powerful killer move.

Wan Zi Hong grunted in anger: "I do not want to bother with healing. If you give me all my Immortal Gu, I can fight five of them at once!"

At the other side, several Gu Immortals were instructed by Fairy Zi Wei as they charged towards Calamity Luck Altar together.

Duke Long who was lying on the ground felt happy upon seeing this: "Good, it seems that Fairy Zi Wei has already deduced the weakness of call of the ancient killer move, she is gathering troops to attack Calamity Luck Altar."

Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan was leading the Northern Plains' group.

Seeing the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, he snorted: "This call of the ancient killer move is powerful but it can only be used once. If Heavenly Court disrupts it, it will not be usable again. However, I've already saved some manpower to deal with your assaults."

Calamity Luck Altar similarly contained several Northern Plains Gu Immortals, they quickly flew outside and blocked the incoming Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Far away, Fairy Zi Wei let out a sigh of relief: "Thankfully, Bing Sai Chuan does not cultivate wisdom path, the situation has been stabilized."

Fairy Zi Wei chose the most optimal strategy!

Even though Heavenly Court's side was on the weak side, Fairy Zi Wei was still willing to gather forces to attack Calamity Luck Altar.

This way, to stabilize the situation, Northern Plains would have to gather more people to defend themselves.

The weaker Heavenly Court was attacking, while the stronger Northern Plains was defending.

It was obvious that the attacker had more initiative, this allowed the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals more time to recover.

If they got injured, they would retreat to the qi wall and recuperate.

When Northern Plains started to defend Calamity Luck Altar, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals felt their pressure lifting, they were more easily able to return to the qi wall for healing.

Boom!

Two time path killer moves collided, Hei Fan and Gu Liu Ru spit out blood as they flew behind respectively.

Gu Liu Ru wanted to retreat to the qi wall when a figure suddenly appeared.

"Just die." The figure appeared and disappeared instantly.

Gu Liu Ru was merely inches from the qi wall, but he suddenly fell on the ground in disbelief, losing his life.

The attacker was naturally Liu tribe's expert Liu Liu Liu.

This person was crafty and scheming, he was called the disgrace of Northern Plains when he was alive, because he never fought openly with people, he bullied the weak while fearing the strong, he enjoyed sneak attacking people. His enemies often suffered severe losses, but could not even find a glimpse of Liu Liu Liu, they would spit out blood in anger.

Gu Liu Ru's death made a great impact on the Gu Immortals of both sides.

Ever since Longevity Heaven joined the battle, this was the first sacrifice from Heavenly Court that had appeared!

Gu Liu Ru did not have all his Gu worms, and most importantly, more and more Gu Immortals were joining the battle, it was getting more intense, a certain threshold was reached.

Like a signal, soon, the second and third sacrifices appeared.

Ye Lui Kou finally succeeded in killing Wan Zi Hong, but he was also heavily injured by Zhao Shan He.

On Northern Plains' side, Hei Fan died.

He and Gu Liu Ru had fought too intensely, and most importantly, he lacked good defensive killer moves, he was suddenly attacked by several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals at once.

All in all, Heavenly Court's sacrifices were larger in terms of Gu Immortals.

"Damn it!"

"These Gu Immortals are the foundation of my Heavenly Court, they actually died like this."

"This was not worth it!"

Fairy Zi Wei sighed deeply, the enemy's sacrifice was merely part of a killer move. If they used the killer move again, these 'dead' Northern Plains Gu Immortals could show up in battle again.

These Northern Plains Gu Immortals were not summoned with their true body after all.

But Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were real lives even though their lifespan was limited.

"This time path rank nine killer move should be the work of Red Lotus Demon Venerable! Damn it, he is too vicious, he totally targeted by Heavenly Court's weakness." Fairy Zi Wei was furious but also helpless.

Bing Sai Chuan's expression was similarly ugly.

Because as time passed, he found that these summoned Northern Plains experts were falling in battle strength, and it was very evident.

Soon, Fairy Zi Wei also realized this.

"I understand, it is because fate Gu's recovery is increasing rapidly, it is reaching full recovery." Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with hope, she was very happy: "Even though Red Lotus Demon Venerable's move is powerful, it uses the River of Time and manipulates history, it goes against fate. When fate Gu is fully repaired, this move will also lose all effectiveness."

Chapter 1720: Through Branches and Leaves

Fairy Zi Wei's analysis was not wrong.

Because when fate Gu exists, ancient Gu Immortals cannot come to the present, and future Gu Immortals also cannot travel to the past.

But because of fate Gu's injuries, the restriction on time path was greatly reduced. Spring Autumn Cicada was the best example, even though it could not allow a Gu Immortal to return to the past, they could send their will back.

Future self, call of the ancient, support of the future, these killer moves were also making use of the past or future, projecting a person into the present from a certain point in time.

When fate Gu is fully restored, these killer moves would no longer work.

Fairy Zi Wei realized this, Bing Sai Chuan naturally knew this from the start.

But there was no choice.

The refinement path formation could not be destroyed, otherwise, Heavenly Court's attempt to repair fate Gu would fail entirely.

An overly damaged fate Gu was useless even if Longevity Heaven obtained it, they would need to repair it by mimicking Heavenly Court's methods.

But Bing Sai Chuan knew that Longevity Heaven did not have the deep foundation of Heavenly Court, they did not have human path methods or the Infallible inheritance, they did not have the ability to repair fate Gu!

They could not destroy the refinement path formation, Longevity Heaven could only break past the formation and enter Heaven Overseeing Tower to take fate Gu by force.

Regarding this, Bing Sai Chuan had already sent Five Elements Grandmaster and Bull Demon.

But that was his limit.

It was not like he did not want to add more people, the phantom River of Time also had many Northern Plains experts emerging continuously as well.

But this refinement path formation itself had its limit.

This formation was meant to repair fate Gu, it was not for combat. The formation space inside could only handle five rank eights.

Any more and the refinement path formation would be destroyed.

Thus, Bing Sai Chuan did not send more people, while Central Continent also watched the situation inside without sending more people.

The battle around Calamity Luck Altar involved countless historical experts, the battle was intense. But the most crucial battle was in the refinement path formation!

Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth, thinking about the situation: "Even though our side is strong, we need to focus on defense, but overall, we still have the advantage. In the worst case, we will have to destroy this refinement path formation, even if we cannot take fate Gu, we will make sure Heavenly Court's objective fails!"

Both sides did not want to destroy the refinement path formation, but if there was no choice, Longevity Heaven would have to destroy it and cause both sides to end up losing.

Of course, Bing Sai Chuan was leading Longevity Heaven to attack Heavenly Court, their main objective was to snatch fate Gu, if the formation was destroyed, they would have failed their objective.

"It is up to us now!" Bull Demon had a clear understanding of the situation outside.

Far away, Five Elements Grandmaster also nodded as his expression turned serious.

Suddenly, Five Elements Grandmaster's body shook as an intense aura surged out, a powerful killer move shining in five colored lights shot towards his enemy Che Wei.

Che Wei shouted loudly as he placed both hands in front of him, activating a killer move.

Countless large shields appeared in front of him, even though there were loud cracking noises, these shields formed a wall and blocked the five colored lights.

"Damn it!" Five Elements Grandmaster intensified his attack, the five colored lights grew in power and destroyed shields after shields.

But Che Wei's defenses were impenetrable, even though shields were broken, new ones quickly formed to replace them.

Che Wei had outstanding defensive methods, Five Elements Grandmaster felt a sense of helplessness.

Within the refinement path formation, be it Che Wei or Five Elements Grandmaster, they had to control their firepower, they could not destroy this refinement path formation recklessly.

On the other side, Bull Demon and Cong Yan's battle was also about the same.

Undeniably, it was much better to be on the defensive for this battle.

"What do we do?" Five Elements Grandmaster asked Bull Demon secretly.

Bull Demon only replied: "Attack, try and lure their attention!"

Saying so, Bull Demon charged at Cong Yan again, the two engaged in another fierce fight.

Five Elements Grandmaster's heart shook, Bull Demon's words had deep meaning, he did not think anymore, he trusted Longevity Heaven and went to engage in a long fight with Che Wei.

At the other end, Yuan Qiong Du was completely focused on manipulating the refinement path formation, putting his attention on repairing fate Gu.

While nobody noticed anything, a small flower resembling scattering petals landed towards Heaven Overseeing Tower inconspicuously.

"Hehehe." The flower landed into Heaven Overseeing Tower and turned into a little girl.

It was none other than the female immortal Flower Lady who had died earlier!

"Oh no, someone entered the tower!" Sensing this, Yuan Qiong Du was deeply shocked, he quickly shouted to alert the rest. He had to pay a huge price for this shout, his seven orifices were bleeding, his mind was heavily injured, it directly cracked into two and could not merge together.

Che Wei and Cong Yan quickly retreated, they wanted to enter Heaven Overseeing Tower and stop Flower Lady from getting close to fate Gu.

"Too late!" Bull Demon laughed loudly, he joined forces with Five Elements Grandmaster as they restrained their enemies.

Che Wei and Cong Yan became more flustered, they scolded Bull Demon for being so shameless and unscrupulous, they actually schemed this deeply.

This was Bull Demon and Flower Lady's biggest secret. They shared their lifespan together, if one of them died, as long as the other was still alive, they would revive after some time.

After Flower Lady revived, she flew into Heaven Overseeing Tower, there were only five Gu Immortals in the refinement path immortal formation, thus it did not break and was still operational.

"What do I do?" Yuan Qiong Du's vision turned dark, his head was hurting, this was the toughest decision of his life.

He controlled the refinement path formation, he could totally destroy fate Gu and ruin all of Heavenly Court's hard work.

If he did not do that, the enemy would obtain a nearly recovered fate Gu, this would preserve fate Gu and they might have a chance of getting it back. Of course, if they could not take it back, Heavenly Court's hard work would all be in vain, they would all benefit Longevity Heaven instead!

This decision was too tough and Yuan Qiong Du's mind was heavily injured, his thinking speed fell greatly.

When Flower Lady got to the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower and saw fate Gu, Yuan Qiong Du had yet to make up his mind.

"Success!" Flower Lady's eyes shined brightly, she stretched out her hand and wanted to grab fate Gu.

If she succeeds, she would be the biggest contributor of Longevity Heaven in this trip!

But at this moment, on the walls of Heaven Overseeing Tower, a bamboo forest painting suddenly appeared.

"What is that?" Flower Lady had a look of shock, she was very stunned.

Three hundred thousand years ago, during the Medieval Antiquity Era.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable walked down Star Zone Mountain as he smiled bitterly in his heart: "This is the chess game set by Limitless Demon Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it contains the grand power of these two venerables as well as replenishment from Heavenly Court at all times. If I interfere forcefully, I would have to resist the joint power of two venerables."

"Of course, these are just two venerables' methods, they are not alive and cannot think like humans. After finding out information on them, I will be able to target them, but even if I succeed, that would only harm Heavenly Court."

"Since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable agreed to Limitless Demon Venerable's suggestion back then and created this chessboard together, she must have her considerations, this will definitely benefit Heavenly Court. I do not need to be a sinner."

Even so, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was not completely assured.

He thought about it as he walked, when he raised his head, he realized he had arrived at the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower.

He suddenly lost all his frustrations, he smiled at the blank walls: "That's right, I can leave my painting here!"

Unknown to everyone, he created a painting here.

After he finished it, this painting vanished without a trace, it was so deeply concealed that even Heavenly Court did not know of it. Other than Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, everyone was kept in the dark.

Three hundred thousand years later, this bamboo forest painting that nobody knew of appeared before Flower Lady.

Flower Lady's hand was merely an inch away from fate Gu, but this distance could not be breached!

Flower Lady's body floated in the air, she could not move.

Her gaze was completely in a daze, after looking at the bamboo forest painting for a moment, she fell into a multi-layered illusion.

The bamboo forest was huge, but she was just a single person, she could not leave after getting lost.

Flower Lady was very anxious but there was nothing she could do!

Winds blew as bamboo leaves shook, jade green light and shadows enveloped Flower Lady.

Flower Lady who was inside the bamboo forest felt the world spinning as she fainted on the spot.

But the bamboo forest painting did not vanish or freeze, the jade bamboos on the walls started to sway as if the wind was blowing.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Instantly, all of the immortals in battle heard the sound of the wind.

On the wall, beautiful leaves that resembled jade fell off the branches, it was a beautiful sight.

This wind that did not exist not only penetrated the refinement path immortal formation and reached the immortals' ears, it even entered Duke Long's heart.

Instantly, Duke Long fell into an illusion too.

He was lying on the ground, surrounded by thick jade bamboos.

The wind was blowing, jade bamboo leaves were falling elegantly.

Duke Long received almost the same treatment as Flower Lady, but he did not feel anything discomfort, his mind was getting clearer.

At this instance, he could feel the pure power and profundity of wood path!

He could feel the concealment of the bamboo forest, he could feel the pressure of the trees, he could feel the vitality and strength of the grass that grew out of the soil.

Next, his limbs felt like the grass and trees, gaining new strength as they grew.

With this newfound strength, Duke Long supported himself and stood up slowly, standing in the bamboo forest.

In a daze, he seemed to have seen Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable.

He had the appearance of a young man, he was gentlemanly and polite, wearing green clothes and a white headband, his long hair was fluttering with the wind.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable smiled mildly as he walked past Duke Long slowly.

His words could be heard from the gentle winds: "The left is love, the right is affection, walking on both sides of life, scattering seeds and blooming flowers, making this journey full of flower fragrance, allowing the person who walks through branches and leaves to feel no pain even as they step on thorns, they can shed tears but feel no sadness."

Saying so, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable walked into the bamboo forest.

"You are Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable?" Duke Long turned around, only to see that Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was vanishing among the bamboo trees.

Only one sentence was left by him: "Remember, this move is called — Through Branches and Leaves."

At the next moment, Duke Long woke up.

He was shocked to find that he was already standing, the silver chains that were binding him turned into bamboo leaves that scattered on the ground.

These leaves looked like they were made from jade.

TL Note: Genesis' words are a quote from the author Bing Xin.

Chapter 1721: Heavenly Dragon's Last Stand

At once, Duke Long understood that this was a Genesis Lotus true inheritance!

He could clearly feel his wood path attainment level rising to an extremely high level, at the same time, memories related to this wood path killer move through branches and leaves were all etched into his mind.

That bamboo forest, rather than calling it an illusion, was more like a state of mind.

The power of through branches and leaves killer move was to free the Gu Immortal of all harmful restraints.

"I am truly pathetic." Duke Long laughed at himself.

He felt the power of a venerable once again.

The truth was, he had some understanding towards the chess game of both venerables in Imperfection Regret Pavilion. This game had unparalleled might, it was one with Heavenly Court and could continuously draw strength from it. This was the secret agreement between Star Constellation's will and Limitless Demon Venerable back in the days.

Because it had the power of two venerables, it could not be dealt with by a single venerable.

But the silver chains on Duke Long was just made from one of the pieces in this chess game. The through branches and leaves killer move that Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable left behind was able to free Duke Long from its effect.

"Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable really put a lot of effort into it, it is a waste for this wood path true inheritance to be given to me."

Duke Long sighed as he kept away his emotions.

His dragon pupils looked around as he stared at the Calamity Luck Altar not too far away.

Calamity Luck Altar was so huge it covered half of Duke Long's vision.

While Duke Long was restrained, he had been incapacitated near Calamity Luck Altar, now that he regained freedom and stood up, he was not far from it.

Breathing in deeply.

The sounds of the surrounding battle, explosions or shouting, became very soft as he blocked them out.

While he was restrained, Duke Long's anger, guilt, and hatred filled his heart, now that he regained freedom, these surging emotions erupted like a dormant volcano that had reawakened.

Unknowingly, all the present Gu Immortals all had a feeling, that was the calm before a storm.

Breathe out…

Breathe in…

Duke Long cultivated qi path with transformation path on the side, each time he breathed, he sucked in a huge amount of oxygen, it was a great commotion. In fact, this commotion was slightly affecting the surrounding qi wall's stability.

Behind Duke Long, his dragon tail waved about, his dragon claws and horns were shining in a purple-gold light, he was extremely grand and royal. Ripples started to form in the surrounding air, the particles seemed to be flickering with a similar purple-gold light.

A terrifying aura was emerging in his body, he was like a catastrophic beast that created heaven and earth, after eons of slumbering, he had finally awakened.

Countless gazes landed on Duke Long at this moment!

"Damn it." Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth.

Flower Lady was unconscious while Duke Long broke free, Longevity Heaven had faced the greatest setback since they started this attack.

Inside the refinement path formation, Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster sensed something amiss, they fought with all their strength. But Che Wei and Cong Yan held on desperately, they did not give the enemy a chance to breakthrough.

At a deeper area of the refinement path formation, Yuan Qiong Du was spitting out blood, he tried hard to sustain the refinement path formation's operations, he was already resolved to die.

Bing Sai Chuan tried hard to think of a plan.

The situation was turning bad, sweat formed on his forehead.

He had already expended all his trump cards, he could not seek help from Limitless Demon Venerable again. The truth was, Limitless Demon Venerable did not even turn around earlier, his attitude was very clear.

Duke Long's aura surged to its limit, it was grand and overwhelming!

Even though he had not moved, he had already gained the attention of everyone.

"He is Lord Duke Long?" Some Heavenly Court Gu Immortals looked over with admiration. Duke Long's seniority was still quite high.

But someone was even older than Duke Long, an old Gu Immortal did not recognize him: "He is one of us?"

"Duke Long finally escaped." Fairy Zi Wei was very excited, she observed the entire situation, she knew clearly that among the Heavenly Court immortals now, Duke Long was the strongest person.

He broke the chains and recovered his freedom, he had stood up at a timely moment!

Or more accurately, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's arrangements were simply too timely.

Thinking of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, Fairy Zi Wei felt a deep sense of admiration.

"Unbelievable methods! After Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's era, Heaven Overseeing Tower had been modified countless times, many of the Gu worms were replaced. Especially during the recent decade of fighting, it had been damaged constantly and repaired afterwards. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's method was actually intact after all that, it was hidden so deeply that nobody found it."

"His immortal killer move could hide within Heaven Overseeing Tower which is the number one investigative Immortal Gu House in this world, remaining undiscovered. And most amazingly, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's immortal killer move had never disrupted with the workings of Heaven Overseeing Tower."

Thinking of this, Fairy Zi Wei had a flash of inspiration: "Don't tell me that rumor is true?" Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable really created painting path? The greatest advantage and trait of the rumored painting path is that it can perfectly accommodate the operations of other Immortal Gu and killer moves… this has the same level of profundity as sovereign immortal body's non-conflicting dao marks!"

Fairy Zi Wei could only guess.

The ten venerables were the apex of Gu cultivation, they were the brightest stars with unparalleled luster. Even though Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable did not cultivate wisdom path, he could comprehend the profundities of heaven and earth, he was able to make arrangements that affected the future era.

And most importantly, his arrangement worked at the most crucial moment, his control of the timing was simply impeccable.

Bing Sai Chuan was very nervous, he ordered: "Block Duke Long!"

Even without his reminder, all of the Northern Plains Gu Immortals could tell that Duke Long was a huge threat.

After Duke Long's aura reached its limit, it started to condense and shrink, it was like someone who was pulling back his fist, once he attacked, it would be a terrifying sight.

This action created huge mental pressure among the Northern Plains' immortals.

"Kill." A Northern Plains male immortal shouted as he charged at Duke Long.

The second Northern Plains Gu Immortal was silent but followed behind the male immortal, charging and defending him.

"No, let me face him!" The third Northern Plains expert suddenly moved out with great speed, he arrived before Duke Long instantly.

Duke Long had a peaceful expression, he stood silently on the ground without moving, like a statue.

Roar—!

Suddenly, a dragon roar was heard, an elegant purple-gold dragon qi appeared in the sky for an instant.

The Gu Immortal wanted to see it but all they saw were the remnant traces of the purple-gold dragon qi.

The Northern Plains expert who arrived before Duke Long became motionless.

He lowered his head, looking at the hole in his chest with an expression of disbelief.

Through this hole, he could see the world behind him.

Guh.

At the next moment, blood gushed out of his mouth as countless mini dragon-shaped qi emerged on his body.

Bam.

With a thud, he self-detonated, turning into a pile of flesh and blood, dying on the spot.

He was a famous expert of Northern Plains, but he was unable to take one hit from Duke Long!

"How can this be?" Seeing this, the two Northern Plains Gu Immortals who wanted to kill Duke Long became lost for words as their expressions changed.

"What are you looking at?" Duke Long's calm voice resounded behind them.

"Oh no!" The two Northern Plains experts activated their strongest defenses without thinking.

This instinct was ingrained into their very existence, it saved their lives.

At the next moment, Duke Long's two ferocious dragon claws landed.

The two Northern Plains experts' defenses crumbled instantly, they were like two shooting stars, crashing and creating a huge pit on the ground.

With a loud boom, rocks flew as dust clouds rose.

The two Northern Plains experts fainted in the pit.

Duke Long's attack was truly shocking! Instantly, he killed one and made two unconscious, Longevity Heaven lost the battle strength of three rank eights just like that!

"Terrifying!"

At once, the battle strength that Duke Long unleashed stunned Heavenly Court's members.

The old man who did not recognize Duke Long felt very surprised: "After my time, there was actually such a talented junior?"

"He is the master of Red Lotus Demon Venerable, he is also a Dao Guardian." The Heavenly Court Gu Immortal beside him explained.

The old man realized: "Oh, no wonder."

The Dao Guardians of venerables were usually the strongest person besides the venerable if they matured fully.

Of course there were exceptions.

Like Reckless Savage Demon Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

But no matter what, these Dao Guardians were monumental in the growth process of the venerable.

"He's coming!" Bing Sai Chuan breathed in deeply, concentrating his mind.

After Duke Long defeated the three, he went straight for Calamity Luck Altar, his advancement carried huge pressure as everyone looked at him with great fear.

At this moment, Bing Sai Chuan felt that even the powerful Calamity Luck Altar was showing a sign of fragility.

"Protect me!" Bing Sai Chuan shouted.

Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals quickly went back to reinforce him.

Duke Long's action was the same as attacking a beehive, a large number of Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals gathered and encircled him from the front and back, forming a huge web.

Countless immortal killer moves landed on Duke Long, they were like fireworks that sparkled, fatal danger was hidden within these beautiful sparks.

The purple-gold dragon-shaped qi flashed again!

Duke Long appeared far away, many killer moves missed their target.

The remaining killer moves were directed by the user as they changed directions.

Duke Long's body flickered again, he showed disdain towards the killer moves that were targeting him.

"Break!" He shouted as he used a qi path killer move.

A surging qi wave erupted in all directions, all killer moves were pushed away, the surroundings were completely cleared out.

The Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals could only pounce towards Duke Long.

"You have already attacked, now it is time to face my killer move as well!" Duke Long snickered.

Longevity Heaven lost two more Gu Immortals.

Duke Long continued to approach Calamity Luck Altar.

Under Bing Sai Chuan's manipulation, Calamity Luck Altar had no choice but to retreat rapidly.

Duke Long continued to chase it, regardless of which Northern Plains expert that was in his way, he went through their line of defense without difficulty.

Of course, he would dodge the powerful killer moves as well.

Shock was exposed in Bing Sai Chuan's eyes: "Impossible! How can Duke Long become so powerful in such a short time? Is this part of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's method?"

He was wrong about this.

Duke Long was strong because of himself.

Immortal killer move — Heavenly Dragon's Last Stand!

The lower his lifespan, the greater the amplification that heavenly dragon's last stand gave him.

This amplification was in all aspects, it made Duke Long powerful beyond words, his battle strength was rising every second.

His vitality was shrinking but his aura continued to grow. This was his final battle, at the last moments of his life, Duke Long erupted with unprecedented brilliance!

Chapter 1722: Seven Extreme Desolation

Heavenly dragon's last stand made Duke Long increasingly stronger, with each breath of time, he became stronger than before.

Looking at the phantom River of Time in the sky, Duke Long showed a complex emotion in his eyes, he sighed lightly: "Oh Red Lotus, I have already witnessed your call of the ancient and support of the future. Now, let me show you my heavenly dragon's last stand!"

Duke Long's words infuriated all of the Northern Plains experts.

He obviously looked down on all of the Northern Plains immortals present, there was only Red Lotus Demon Venerable in his eyes.

The Northern Plains experts were all famous people in history, they had their own arrogance and pride. But they had no way of rebuking Duke Long's words.

Because their existence was the result of Red Lotus Demon Venerable's immortal killer move!

"Old man, you speak too much!"

"Don't look down on us."

"We will show you our power!"

Several Northern Plains rank eights charged at Duke Long.

Duke Long snickered as he roared, the purple-gold dragon-shaped qi flickered continuously.

Boom boom boom!

An intense explosion resounded, Duke Long rampaged among the Gu Immortals who encircled him, he was simply unstoppable.

In contrast, the Northern Plains experts were losing numbers rapidly from his ferocious attacks.

Fast!

Duke Long was just too fast, the Northern Plains Gu Immortals could not stop him.

Any killer move needed time to prepare and activate.

Because Duke Long was concentrating on Calamity Luck Altar, he did not bother wasting time with the Northern Plains Gu Immortals that obstructed him.

"Block him!"

"Don't think of leaving Duke Long, fight me for three hundred rounds!"

"We must stop him."

Purple-gold dragon qi flickered again.

The battlefield became silent, Bing Sai Chuan raised his head and looked.

Duke Long was finally standing before Calamity Luck Altar, his emotionless pupils looked at this luck path rank eight Immortal Gu House.

"Oh no." Sweat poured down Bing Sai Chuan's forehead.

At the next moment, Duke Long roared as his qi path killer move was activated again.

Myriad qi rampaged, the world changed colors.

Immortal killer move — Qi Engulfing Mountains and Rivers!

At once, the rank eight Gu Immortals shook intensely as they felt an unparalleled pressure slamming down at them from all around.

Many killer moves collapsed, the Northern Plains experts who were pursuing Duke Long fell into the water like dumplings falling into a pot.

The world became still, nothing was left standing!

Crack, crack…

Calamity Luck Altar could barely operate, its thin light halo was resisting qi engulfing mountains and rivers killer move.

This luck path rank eight Immortal Gu House could not fly, it was suppressed by Duke Long and forced to stay on the ground!

At once, Duke Long became the main character of this battlefield, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals looked at him with shock and amazement.

He had suppressed the entire situation singlehandedly.

Even though Northern Plains' experts were strong and proud, their raised heads were forcefully lowered by Duke Long.

"Damn it, this qi engulfing mountains and rivers killer move had once been used in Eastern Sea by Duke Long. But its current power is more than ten times of before!" Bing Sai Chuan could not conceal the shock on his face.

Duke Long's strength was too overwhelming, it was far out of his expectations.

"This damned old man is quite strong! It seems that you need Grandpa Mao's help now!" Far away, Mao Li Qiu and his clone had been suppressing the two legendary immemorial beasts from Heavenly Court, after seeing Duke Long's power, Mao Li Qiu gritted its teeth and wanted to rush over to help.

"You want to leave? Dream on!" The immemorial green jade crane shrieked, it activated an immortal killer move and attacked Mao Li Qiu's clone.

"Stand there!" Shabi Ninety-five grabbed Mao Li Qiu's right hind leg as it bit.

"These two idiots…" Mao Li Qiu was furious, it was unable to get away from these two.

Heavenly Court's two legendary immemorial desolate beasts might not be able to turn the situation around, but they were great at keeping the status quo.

Duke Long's power was simply like steroids injected into his allies, it made these two legendary immemorial desolate beasts extremely energetic!

"Go away!" Calamity Luck Altar suddenly shined in a fierce light, it started to rise slowly.

Next, the Northern Plains experts who were on the ground and used their killer moves on Duke Long.

Even though Duke Long was strong, he could only suppress them for some time, he was not just going up against the rank eight Immortal Gu House that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created, there were also the countless experts from the Northern Plains Huang Jin tribes' history!

"Go assist Duke Long!"

"We will make Longevity Heaven pay with bloodshed!"

"How can Heavenly Court's authority be undermined."

Heavenly Court's immortals reacted, they moved like rushing tide as they went to reinforce Duke Long.

A portion of the Northern Plains experts had to go and block Heavenly Court's attacks on the outside. Inside, the remaining ones attacked Duke Long with all their might.

Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan's heart sank to rock bottom.

Duke Long was unstoppable even in the encirclement, he had the complete advantage, and outside, there were fewer Northern Plains Gu Immortals than Heavenly Court's side, they were also losing there.

Bing Sai Chuan understood: Unless a venerable makes a move, Longevity Heaven's invasion had failed!

Their goal was to take fate Gu but now, they were barely able to stay alive, not to mention snatch anything.

The truth was, Longevity Heaven was just one step away from success. The problem was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable and his arrangement, it ruined Longevity Heaven's plan.

"Even though my Longevity Heaven failed, your Heavenly Court may not succeed either!" A cold light flashed in Bing Sai Chuan's eyes, he gave his orders — destroy the refinement path formation!

Since they could not obtain fate Gu or destroy fate Gu entirely, he would make sure that they fail in restoring it!

This way, Heavenly Court would need to continue holding the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention to repair fate Gu in the future.

And that would give the other four regions some respite.

But in that situation, in the future Central Continent Refinement Path Conventions, Heavenly Court would guard themselves deeply, Longevity Heaven would no longer have this chance to invade.

But there was no choice, the situation was forcing Bing Sai Chuan to make such a decision.

"Okay!" Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster received their orders, they immediately attacked the refinement path formation.

Guh.

Cong Yan spit out a mouthful of blood, his face turned pale.

But he had a faint smile as he said: "Hmph, why do you think Lady Zi Wei made me guard the formation internally? It was to prevent you guys from causing destruction!"

Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster frowned deeply.

They realized that their attacks on the refinement path formation was actually transferred to Cong Yan. This was a rule path method unique to Cong Yan, he could transfer damage onto himself.

"You want to destroy the formation, how can we allow that?"

"With us around, don't even think about it!"

Outside the refinement path immortal formation, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals formed lines of defense as they blocked the assault of the Northern Plains experts.

Bing Sai Chuan changed his goal and attempted to destroy the refinement path formation, this was his enemy's weakness as well.

For Heavenly Court, they had no choice but to defend the formation.

This way, the battle between the two sides went into a deadlock.

Most of Heavenly Court's members were protecting the refinement path formation, Duke Long alone was attacking Calamity Luck Altar.

For Northern Plains, they were mainly defending Calamity Luck Altar while attacking the refinement path formation with a barrage of attacks.

Even though Duke Long was obstructed by all the Northern Plains experts, he still had the energy to attack Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar endured attacks from Duke Long time and again but it still remained standing, this was the immense defense of a rank eight Immortal Gu House.

The truth was, Calamity Luck Altar's methods were not just limited to these, against Duke Long, it could still retaliate.

But now, Calamity Luck Altar's main purpose was to sustain call of the ancient killer move.

If it used other methods, this call of the ancient would be interrupted.

The root of the issue was that call of the ancient was a time path killer move, it was incompatible with Calamity Luck Altar's methods. If there were any abilities similar to Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's earlier methods resembling painting path, the situation would not be this awkward.

Bing Sai Chuan was clear in his heart, once he stopped using call of the ancient killer move, the situation would worsen instantly. Only through this move could they resist the awakening Heavenly Court members.

As time passed, the situation got more intense, more and more Gu Immortals died.

Duke Long's attacks from time to time made Bing Sai Chuan's heart shook. He did not know how long Calamity Luck Altar could last, maybe at the next moment, call of the ancient killer move would stop.

If that happens, Longevity Heaven would lose this battle without doubt.

Even though both sides were attacking and defending, as Duke Long continued to unleash powerful moves, the situation was already changing. Heavenly Court had a slight advantage, Longevity Heaven was slowly losing their edge.

Boom!

A lightning path killer move landed on Duke Long's back.

But Duke Long's body did not even move, as the dust clouds settled, his back was exposed.

It was covered in purple-gold dragon scales.

As the effect of heavenly dragon's last stand persisted, Duke Long's body became stronger and larger, his size was already twice of before.

His dragon claws became sharper, his dragon tail became longer and more flexible, his dragon horns were originally very short but now they grew rapidly, they were the size of a deer's antlers, they looked like a crown on his head, displaying his royal and authoritative figure.

Every moment and every second, Duke Long was getting stronger!

Bing Sai Chuan who was inside Calamity Luck Altar as well as the Northern Plains Gu Immortals could feel this very deeply.

"This is a monster!" A Northern Plains expert shouted in hatred.

"Monster? Hahaha, we Seven Big Dipper Immortals love dealing with monsters!" At this moment, from the phantom River of Time, seven Gu Immortals walked out.

"Ah! It's them." Bing Sai Chuan saw this, becoming surprised and happy.

These Seven Big Dipper Immortals were all from Huang Jin tribes, there were three rank eights and four rank sevens, they were all from the same period of time in history.

During their era, legendary immemorial desolate beasts wreaked havoc, they caused the righteous path to suffer great losses. Thus, the Huang Jin tribes banded together and chose seven people to learn the ancient battle formation, they spent countless years to soothe the chaos and capture the beast, returning peace and serenity to Northern Plains.

Ancient battle formation — Seven Extreme Desolation!

At once, the seven Gu Immortals turned into a three headed four armed black-gold giant with a huge metallic ring on its back.

Immortal killer move — Winged Blade!

The black-gold giant's right arm moved like a blade, creating an afterimage as it slashed towards Duke Long.

"Winged blade?!" Duke Long's pupils shrunk, he could feel a fatal danger.

Chapter 1723: Fatal Strike

Winged blade had very high reputation, it was publicly recognized as the number one offensive method of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, it could even cut apart the winds of assimilation temporarily, its fearsome might was known to all.

"I managed to dodge?" The purple-gold dragon-shaped qi flickered as Duke Long appeared elsewhere, shock still showing on his face.

Crack!

At the next moment, he watched as the horn on his forehead fell slowly towards the ground in front of him.

At the crucial moment, Duke Long managed to dodge the winged blade but his right dragon horn was sliced apart.

Duke Long was deeply shocked.

At this moment, the black-gold giant hooked its finger at Duke Long.

Immortal killer move — Immortal Binding Rope!

This was the number one capturing method in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

A green-gold rope appeared on Duke Long's body, it wrapped around his waist thrice as he was pulled towards the black-gold giant.

Immortal killer move — Winged Blade!

The black-gold giant raised its right arm, aiming at Duke Long as it used the powerful killer move again.

Duke Long gritted his teeth, he shouted as his muscular body shook, he broke free of the immortal binding rope and retreated, avoiding the winged blade.

The black-gold giant wanted to capture Duke Long again but he dodged while spitting out two sharp dragon fangs.

The dragon fangs flew out of his mouth and expanded in size, they were like two curved blades that danced in the air, defending his body.

It was immortal killer move — Spiraling Dragon Fang.

Spiraling dragon fang was an offensive killer move but Duke Long used it for defense instead.

Even though the black-gold giant Seven Extreme Desolation had a powerful immortal binding rope killer move, it would be cut by the dragon fangs if it tried to bind Duke Long.

Bing Sai Chuan watched this as he felt suspicious and regretful: "The original spiraling dragon fang is only an arm's size, but it is like two gigantic pillars now! What method did Duke Long use to make his immortal killer moves grow so powerful? It is a pity that Seven Extreme Desolation is much weaker now as fate Gu recovers due to the decreased power of call of the ancient killer move, otherwise, if they had their original power, Duke Long would be heavily injured from the attack earlier!"

Seven Extreme Desolation was an ancient battle formation made of three rank eights and four rank seven Gu Immortals.

Each of them were elites of the Huang Jin tribes in their time, they were famous in Northern Plains. And most importantly, the killer moves that they used were the trump cards of the respective tribes. For example, Chanyu tribe's winged blade and Ye Lui tribe's immortal binding rope.

With Seven Extreme Desolation restricting Duke Long's attacks, the situation went into a deadlock again.

Calamity Luck Altar was temporarily safe, but Longevity Heaven's side could not destroy the refinement path formation no matter what they did.

Heavenly Court had three layers of Gu Immortals both inside and outside, they formed a tight defense, the Northern Plains experts could not even get close to the formation, not to mention getting inside. In fact, Gu Immortals were already starting to set up new defensive formations outside the refinement path immortal formation.

"This looks like a deadlock but the initiative has been lost, at this rate, Heavenly Court will simply continue the battle of attrition." Bing Sai Chuan had a cold expression but determination still shined in his eyes.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortals loved to fight, they had countless battles in their life, far more than other regions' people.

Bing Sai Chuan was a time path rank eight great expert, he was the same. He had experienced countless difficulties in life, even though the situation was increasingly dangerous now, his fighting spirit did not waver.

He was trying to find a way out.

"The plan to invade Heavenly Court had been closely planned by my Longevity Heaven, we have our methods to retaliate."

"For now, we need to communicate with Fang Yuan and the rest, to target the outside world instead."

Bing Sai Chuan immediately contacted Fang Yuan and the rest, giving his orders.

"Luck path method again, they are communicating with the outside world." The moment Bing Sai Chuan acted, a few of Heavenly Court's members sensed it.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled bitterly, the supreme profundity of luck path was held by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Heavenly Court could not stop Bing Sai Chuan.

Emperor City.

Fang Yuan had activated emperor yama killer move as he flew rapidly in the sky.

Winds blew around him, in his vision, Li Huang and Qing Ye were like two torches that charged towards him in the darkness.

Fang Yuan stretched out his finger, countless yama children flew out to obstruct Li Huang and Qing Ye.

Next, he attacked the closest Immortal Gu House.

The Gu Immortals inside that Immortal Gu House were shocked, they quickly retreated.

"Fang Zheng, quickly use that move!" A Gu Immortal shouted.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was also inside this Gu House, he immediately acted as the Immortal Gu House shot out a blood light that moved it with several times the speed, causing Fang Yuan to miss his target.

Using this chance, Li Huang and Qing Ye arrived and fought against Fang Yuan again.

The Western Desert Gu Immortals could not take it as they mocked: "This is clearly a blood path method, the great righteous path Heavenly Court is actually using blood path killer moves in public right now!"

"Bullshit, my Central Continent has unfathomable methods, how can you fools understand what we are doing?"

"Western Desert scoundrel, you are jealous of my Central Continent's wealth, this is slander towards the righteous leader of humanity, this is unacceptable!"

How could Central Continent's Gu Immortals acknowledge it, even though most of them knew that this was Fang Zheng's blood path methods after all.

"Damn it." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, Li Huang and Qing Ye were too annoying, he felt like he was stuck in a swamp.

In this current situation, his best method was great thief ghost hand, using this move, he could destroy many of the Immortal Gu Houses of Heavenly Court.

But Li Huang and Qing Ye were disturbing him, he did not have a chance to succeed.

But Western Desert was also very wary of him, they did not want to cooperate.

Fang clan had a secret cooperation with Fang Yuan but how could they expose that in public right now!

Fang clan had obtained Divine Bean Palace years ago and that caused Western Desert's righteous path to gang up on them, they were keeping a low profile now. Using this Refinement Path Convention as a chance, they made an agreement with Western Desert's righteous path forces. If they worked with Fang Yuan now, they would be giving the righteous path forces more excuses to suppress them afterwards.

"This is not looking good, the competition is nearing its end!" Fang Yuan had participated in the Refinement Path Convention before, he was clear of the situation now.

"Most importantly, why are those fools from Longevity Heaven not doing anything? Hmm?" At this moment, Bing Sai Chuan contacted Fang Yuan.

Towards Fang Yuan, he would naturally not use an authoritative tone, but Bing Sai Chuan knew how to convince Fang Yuan, he told him everything regarding Longevity Heaven's invasion of Heavenly Court!

These were all truths, they had no loopholes.

Bing Sai Chuan did not hide or make up anything because he knew about Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment.

"These bunch of snakes!" Fang Yuan learned about what happened in Heavenly Court as brilliance flashed in his eyes, he gritted his teeth in anger.

He made use of Longevity Heaven and treated Bing Sai Chuan and the rest as pawns, was it not the same in reverse?

Longevity Heaven had their own goals, right now, they were being truthful because they wanted Fang Yuan to cause chaos and prevent Heavenly Court from repairing fate Gu fully.

Inside Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven was only able to stabilize the situation and stall Heavenly Court's experts, they had no chance of winning.

But if Fang Yuan destroyed Emperor City and ruined the competition, Heavenly Court's human path methods would be stopped, they would not be able to take success dao marks from Infallible blessed land.

Without success dao marks, how could Yuan Qiong Du dare to repair fate Gu?

This was the only chance of victory!

Breathing in deeply, a cold light flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes.

Even though he knew that Longevity Heaven was making use of him, this open scheme was in line with his own benefits, he had to do it!

Activating his immortal killer move, Fang Yuan moved like a phantom as he dashed around with shocking speed.

Everywhere he went, Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses avoided him, because of Fang Yuan, the defensive line of Heavenly Court was in complete chaos.

It was a pity that at this time, Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses were all restricted by Heavenly Court, they also had no motivation to go all in, they were unable to make a breakthrough.

Li Huang and Qing Ye arrived again and interrupted Fang Yuan.

Usually at this time, while Fang Yuan was busy with Li Huang and Qing Ye, Heavenly Court's defensive line would be reformed.

But it was different now!

Fang Yuan roared, turning into the immemorial year monkey.

Immortal killer move — Spring Scissors!

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Be it spring scissors or summer fan, Fang Yuan aimed at the Emperor City below.

This made Li Huang and Qing Ye's expressions change.

"Be careful, demon Fang Yuan is going all in!"

"Stop him!"

Li Huang and Qing Ye's killer moves landed on Fang Yuan, winter coat killer move resisted them with difficulty, rank eight immortal essence was expended rapidly.

All the Immortal Gu Houses flustered, they tried to defend Emperor City by blocking the attacks.

Using this chance, Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses attacked.

Fang Yuan ignored everything, he focused his killer moves on Emperor City.

Winter coat killer move was finally unable to hold on, it broke with a loud sound, Fang Yuan's flesh was torn and his bones broke from countless attacks. Fang Yuan forcefully activated winter coat killer move disregarding the damage to the core Immortal Gu or his injuries.

But the core Immortal Gu of winter coat killer move was already damaged, now that it was used, the defensive power was much weaker, it continued to get broken by attacks. Eventually, Immortal Gu Winter succumbed to its injuries and got completely destroyed.

Fang Yuan was no longer able to use winter coat, he lost his main defensive method, thankfully, the immemorial year monkey had a strong body to begin with, Fang Yuan also used many time path methods that were better than nothing.

Fang Yuan's relentless attacks had some great effect.

Emperor City was shaking, the Gu Masters who were in the competition got disrupted as their refinement failed.

"What happened?"

"The entire city is shaking!"

The Gu Masters were shocked and uncertain.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals who were inside Emperor City quickly made their move.

"Protect these Gu Masters!"

"Don't let them die."

"These people are blessed by Central Continent's human path luck, they are people with great fortune. If many of them die, our luck will not be able to resist demon Fang Yuan."

It turned out that Heavenly Court's arrangements also considered the element of luck.

Even though Heavenly Court did not have too much confidence in luck path, they could use this rough method to eliminate Fang Yuan's advantage in luck path.

"Ah, a chance! Fang clan's immortals, the best opportunity is before us." Inside Immortal Gu House Chicken Dog Coop, Fang clan's rank seven Gu Immortal shouted as his eyes shined.

"Kill!"

Chicken Dog Coop was manipulated by Fang clan's Gu Immortals, they crashed towards Emperor City while moving extremely close to the ground.

Heavenly Court's attention was completely drawn to Fang Yuan.

If Chicken Dog Coop used an immortal killer move, it would be detected, they would lose the chance as Heavenly Court would return to defend the city.

But now, Chicken Dog Coop gave up on all methods, they charged directly without reservation, they had used their time optimally!

"Oh no!" Li Huang, Qing Ye, and the rest were pale with shock.

Undoubtedly, Chicken Dog Coop chose the best timing to attack, at this moment, Heavenly Court could only watch as it crashed into Emperor City.

Even though they had several immortal killer moves, there was too little time, they did not have enough power to stop Chicken Dog Coop.

Close, they were close.

The Gu Masters in Emperor City were still unaware while Li Huang and the other Gu Immortals had looks of despair.

The fatal attack was going to land!

Chapter 1724: Heroes Among People

Heavenly Court battlefield.

The front lines were extremely chaotic, the Heavenly Court immortals led by Duke Long fought against Northern Plains' members in close range.

But because of the qi wall, it was very peaceful at the back. Fairy Zi Wei was managing the situation, paying attention to all the battles at once.

"Hmm?" When Chicken Dog Coop was about to hit Emperor City, Fairy Zi Wei's heart tightened.

"Senior Zheng Yuan, quickly save Emperor City!" She made her decision in an instant, she shouted with an unavoidably nervous expression.

Old Man Zheng Yuan nodded lightly: "Don't worry, we have enough human will now, my mission is about to be completed… open!"

At once, Old Man Zheng Yuan's body shook intensely as his immortal essence surged, blood flowed out of his seven orifices.

He cultivated human path but he was only rank seven, it was hard for him to be the key that activated the human path methods, each attempt was excruciating beyond his limit.

But Old Man Zheng Yuan had never shown any bitterness on his face.

Right now, he had a blissful expression as he completed his task.

After the killer move people's united hearts, a new human path method left by the Immortal Venerable was activated.

Emperor City battlefield.

"Crush them all!" Fang clan's Gu Immortal laughed loudly as his expressions turned ruthless.

In his field of vision, Emperor City was getting closer, as long as they destroyed it, it would be a grand achievement! Not only would the Gu Immortal himself be famous throughout the five regions, the entire Fang clan would benefit, their reputation would rise, they would be the role model of Western Desert's righteous path force.

"Good!" Fang Yuan saw this and cheered internally.

He had a gut feeling that if this attack succeeds, he would benefit greatly from it.

Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was high, these kinds of feelings were very reliable. But his luck path attainment level was inferior, he could not sense if luck path contributed to this feeling.

However, a change occurred right at this moment.

A faint white light flashed on Emperor City for a moment.

This white light appeared and disappeared just as quickly.

For some reason, Chicken Dog Coop's ferocious aura vanished, it was still charging but it could not intimidate anyone anymore.

The earlier Chicken Dog Coop was like an advancing warship, but now, it was a damaged boat without anybody steering it, it was moving with the waves.

Next, under everyone's shocked gaze, Chicken Dog Coop started to break apart and disintegrate, countless shards scattered with the wind.

It continued to break apart like an old house, amidst the ferocious winds, it was torn apart piece by piece.

A large number of Gu worms scattered, even more Gu worm corpses fell onto the ground.

One moment ago, the Fang clan Gu Immortal with great morale and determination became completely silent.

Even though the remaining Fang clan Gu Immortals were still shouting now.

A bad feeling emerged in the hearts of the Fang clan Gu Immortals.

Soon, the answer arrived.

From the broken Chicken Dog Coop, corpses fell out one by one, they were the Fang clan Gu Immortals inside who were still lively a moment ago!

"How could this happen?!"

Fang clan's Gu Immortals shouted in shock, they called these Gu Immortals by their names but there was no response.

"What killer move is this? With just one hit, the Immortal Gu House broke apart and not a single Gu Immortal inside survived?!" Even Fang Yuan's expression changed in horror.

Even in the five hundred years of his previous life, such a thing had never happened.

This was the foundation of Central Continent's Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan and the Western Desert Gu Immortals had finally forced them to use it. After all, in the previous life, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable succeeded in defying heaven, he managed to infiltrate Heavenly Court and prevented such a battle from occurring.

Of course, the issue could also be Fang Yuan's own memories. He was once manipulated by heaven's will as a chess piece, he had used Spring Autumn Cicada many times, the memories he had were not entirely reliable.

"This is immortal killer move — Broken Homes and Dead Family!" Li Huang's eyes shined with light, he was extremely excited.

He looked at the sky as he thought to himself: "It seems that the human will has already been accumulated sufficiently."

Sensing this, Li Huang gained an immense confidence in this battle.

He shouted as his voice resounded in the battlefield: "Everyone, what are you waiting for? Heavenly Court has already acted, it is time for us to counterattack!"

"That's right, let these invaders taste the power of our Central Continent!" Qing Ye added.

At the next moment, all over the territory of Central Continent, countless white lights started to emerge.

These white lights were like specks or balls, they resembled countless lanterns, each were as large as dandelions, they floated casually with the wind, rising up and covering the sky.

"What killer move is this?" Western Desert's Gu Immortals were wary and uncertain.

Fang Yuan turned into emperor yama form, he used soul path killer moves to defend himself. Now that winter coat was destroyed, Fang Yuan could only rely on his soul path defensive killer moves.

He stood among the sea of white lights, this scene also made him rather uncertain.

He tried to probe them carefully.

But these white light spots did not have offensive power, they were like illusions, none of Fang Yuan's methods worked.

Even though this immortal killer move was grand and affected the whole of Central Continent, it did not have any offensive power.

Next, these lights moved like fish or birds returning to their homes, landing in all of the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals became covered in more and more white light specks, they were not too flaring, instead the light was warm and mild.

This did not just happen in Emperor City battlefield, it was occurring in Heavenly Court, Infallible blessed land, and all other parts of the continent.

This was human path killer move — Hope of the People!

People's united hearts and 'broken homes and dead family' were Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's human path methods.

But hope of the people and the following move were Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's gains from exploring human path.

Inside Heavenly Court, Old Man Zheng Yuan shouted again.

Human path killer move — Heroes Among People!

The white lights surrounding the Central Continent Gu Immortals started to shrink, while the Gu Immortals' auras started to grow.

"Their auras changed, what is going on?" Seeing this, Gu Immortals of the other four regions were very perplexed.

"So strong, such strong power!" Central Continent's Gu Immortals had an incredible feeling, their bodies were surging with new strength. This strength was so grand and vast, it felt like an endless tide, sweeping through their bodies and minds constantly.

All their fatigue was gone.

Their minds were clear, their fighting spirit also rose sharply.

This situation was most evident in Li Huang, Fairy Zi Wei, Chen Yi and the rest.

"Retreat!"

"Quickly retreat, stop attacking."

"Let's observe the situation first."

The Western Desert Immortal Gu Houses retreated, this scene had truly shocked them.

Fang Yuan squinted his eyes but attacked at this moment, he wanted to probe them using an offensive method.

Yama children flew out towards Li Huang and Qing Ye.

Li Huang breathed in deeply, snickering as the verdant sun flame cloak expanded rapidly on his back by several times its original size, blazing with strong flames.

Before the yama children got close, they were incinerated into nothingness.

"Demon, take this!" Li Huang attacked as Fang Yuan defended himself.

After several rounds, Fang Yuan was greatly astounded: "This human path killer move amplified Li Huang's battle strength by at least three times as before!"

This was not the amplification of dao marks.

Dao mark amplification affected the power of immortal killer moves.

But heroes among people targeted the Gu Immortal themselves!

At rank eight, double amplification was already terrifying. For example, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's perfect pair killer move could create a clone that had the same battle strength as the user, it could be considered a double amplification.

But this heroes among people was at least triple in amplification. And most shockingly, it did not just affect Li Huang, it affected countless Central Continent Gu Immortals!

Hope of the people together with heroes among people, this was the power of two rank nine killer moves used together!

It was like Red Lotus Demon Venerable's 'call of the ancient' and 'support of the future', Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's set of killer moves, 'hope of the people' and 'heroes among people', also had terrifying power that shocked the world.

An even worse situation had arrived.

Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses started to shine in white light as well.

The effect of heroes among people was also working on Immortal Gu Houses.

This was because Immortal Gu Houses were immortal killer moves in essence, used by Gu Immortals. Since heroes among people could amplify other immortal killer moves, Immortal Gu Houses were naturally part of this range.

Central Continent received a great boost, they were at least three times as strong as before, this was a proud moment!

When Gu Immortals fight, numbers were not always an advantage.

Because Gu Immortals often lacked cooperation, the dao marks of different paths conflicted, one plus one was often smaller than two.

If Gu Immortals wanted to fight together, they would usually control the same Immortal Gu House or be the formation cores of immortal formations. But in this aspect, Gu Immortals were mostly just providing immortal essence or repairing Immortal Gu Houses and formations, that was all they had to do.

Compared to this, ancient battle formations had a clear advantage. Even though it was outdated already, it could unleash the potential of the individual Gu Immortals, there was a lot to learn from it.

Be they immortal Gu formations or Immortal Gu Houses, they had fixed killer moves that were prepared beforehand, so their methods did not vary.

But ancient battle formations were different, they could use the methods that Gu Immortals had, even amplifying them when used.

An ancient battle formation was truly able to unite the strength of many Gu Immortals together in an intrinsic method.

This was also why Seven Extreme Desolation could resist Duke Long and leave him without options. It was because the seven Gu Immortals using it had combined their strength, one plus one was more than two.

From this aspect, heroes among people was even more profound than perfect pair.

Because perfect pair could only create one clone with the same battle strength as the user. But heroes among people directly amplified the main body by at least three times as before. The strength of the main body was more valuable than gaining a clone of similar power!

Pressure intensified, Western Desert's Gu Immortals were forced to retreat by Central Continent's forces.

"Fang Yuan, where do you think you're going?!"

"Die here!"

Li Huang and Qing Ye attacked Fang Yuan, he had to resist while retreating.

The amplification of heroes among people was in all aspects, the two rank eights became much faster now, they could advance and retreat at will, they had the initiative now.

Chapter 1725: Four Dragon Generals

Emperor City battlefield.

After an intense battle while moving around, Fang Yuan started to discover some facts.

Such a powerful killer move like heroes among people was simply heaven defying, but it was not costless.

The white light on Li Huang and Qing Ye had been weakening continuously, it was rapidly expended.

But at the same time, the white light was being replenished.

The white light in the sky was at a vast amount, it seemed limitless as it continued to pour into Li Huang and Qing Ye.

Fang Yuan tried to counter it many times but there was no effect.

"The weakness of this human path killer move is very obvious." Fang Yuan had countless ideas, his mind was like a storm that rapidly produced new thoughts.

"We just need to destroy the white lights in the sky, that's all."

"Without these lights, Li Huang and Qing Ye would not be replenished, as the battle drags on, the amplification will vanish."

"But I do not have a method that targets these lights!"

Fang Yuan tried many times but regrettably, he could not even target these white lights at all.

This required an understanding of human path.

Human path had always existed. In fact, because of <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, it was likely the first existing path of human cultivation history. But Gu Immortals who could truly master human path were few, even throughout history, only those geniuses with unparalleled talent could interpret bits and pieces of it.

These comprehensions were often scattered and meager. In most cases, they were merely a set of killer moves. Like Red Lotus Demon Venerable's call of the ancient and support of the future, or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's heroes among people and hope of the people.

Fang Yuan did not have such methods, even the Western Desert Gu Immortals present had no such methods.

Throughout this entire Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, Fang Yuan was losing because of the human path aspect.

If it were other paths, with Fang Yuan's deep foundation, he could deal with it. But human path was simply foreign to him.

Not just him, most Gu Immortals in this world were unfamiliar with it.

Thus, once human path methods were used, the effects were tremendous.

For example, Longevity Heaven's call of the ancient, or Heavenly Court's heroes among people.

"It seems that I need to read <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> more often and comprehend the profundities of human path from it. Without human path methods, it is really difficult to deal with Heavenly Court."

"During the five regions chaotic war, all the super forces will at least have some human path methods too."

"My foundation in this aspect is truly lacking."

Fang Yuan realized this.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was very high already, there were many reasons for this, he had always been trying to raise his battle strength through all means possible. In terms of pure battle strength, he was already standing at the top ranks of this Gu Immortal world.

In terms of resources, Fang Yuan acquired them from many means, and because of sovereign immortal aperture's usefulness, he was self-sufficient. He was able to feed his many Immortal Gu and also earn some revenue. But currently, he did not have the finances to refine a rank eight Immortal Gu, he needed time and accumulation.

But Fang Yuan's shortcomings still existed, and there were many of them.

He had quasi-supreme attainment level in refinement path and time path, his theft path was great grandmaster, blood path, strength path, transformation path, wisdom path, star path were also quite good. But in terms of poison path, dream path, space path, sword path, and others, he lacked the foundation in them, these were all weaknesses.

The same went for human path.

Li Huang and Qing Ye were amplified by heroes among people, becoming able to suppress Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not want to give up, he could only go on the defensive.

Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses started to attack, encircling Western Desert's immortals as well as the Immortal Gu House that Bai Ning Bing and the rest were in.

Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses gained a surge in battle strength, they were not afraid of these enemies' Immortal Gu Houses escaping.

Hidden Dragon Cave battlefield.

"Soon." Song Qi Yuan had a heated gaze, he stared at the rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace as he continued to refine it.

Along with him, there were the other rank eight Gu Immortals of Eastern Sea — Qing Yue An, Hua Cai Yun, Shen Cong Sheng, Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, Shi Miao, and Yang Zi He.

These Gu Immortals cooperated and refined Dragon Palace, trying to make it their own.

Even though Dragon Palace was refined by Duke Long, it was unmanned at the moment, because a portion of its power was used to suppress Di Zang Sheng, it could barely resist the refinement of Eastern Sea's rank eights.

Time passed, Dragon Palace was gradually refined by the Eastern Sea immortals.

Just when they were about to succeed, Eastern Sea's immortals became increasingly alert.

"Be careful, we do not want to fail at the last second!"

"That's right, I have a bad feeling for some reason."

"Indeed, even though we attacked this place, Heavenly Court had not sent a single reinforcement."

"Don't worry, that Heavenly Court is probably busy fending for themselves, they cannot spare any effort here. I'm sure they've already given up on this place."

"Old Slave Bei Feng, go and guard the cave entrance, kill anyone who approaches suspiciously. If Heavenly Court sends reinforcements, you cannot retreat even if you die!" Shen Cong Sheng shouted, he had already enslaved Old Man Bei Feng successfully.

Old Man Bei Feng had lost his freedom, he had to obey Shen Cong Sheng.

He sighed bitterly as he obeyed the orders, leaving with his grandson Feng Chan Zi.

Feng Chan Zi was Old Man Bei Feng's grandson, he only had rank six cultivation level and was insignificant to the Eastern Sea immortals. After Shen Cong Sheng enslaved Old Man Bei Feng, he also enslaved Feng Chan Zi.

"It seems that this time, Brother Shen's gains are the largest." Zhang Yin laughed.

According to the alliance agreement, Dragon Palace was shared among the immortals, but Shen Cong Sheng managed to enslave Old Man Bei Feng and his grandson. Forget about Feng Chan Zi, the key was Old Man Bei Feng, he was a genuine rank eight. The only problem was that his injuries made his battle strength fall drastically.

Shen Cong Sheng was silent, he knew that with his huge gains, even though the others looked calm on the outside, they had other thoughts internally.

Because Shen clan had just gained a new rank eight existence. After Old Man Bei Feng recovers, it would break the balance of the current Eastern Sea!

Thinking of this, Shen Cong Sheng smiled: "What can this Old Man Bei Feng do? He is old and extremely injured, he needs to spend a lot of time and energy in recuperating. It is nothing compared to Dragon Palace!"

He tried to devalue Old Man Bei Feng while diverting the attention of the immortals to Dragon Palace.

"This Dragon Palace is able to suppress and even enslave Di Zang Sheng. With it, when the five regions combine, we will have the power to resist the four other regions." He was trying to alert the other immortals' sense of danger, to remind them that he, Shen Cong Sheng, was their ally, their true enemies were the other four regions including Central Continent.

"Let's observe properly, according to our deductions, Dragon Palace should have a dream path Immortal Gu in it, I hope Duke Long did not take it away!" Shen Cong Sheng added.

The immortals were silent.

Shen Cong Sheng made a lot of sense, his eloquence made his companions feel less envious now.

"Dragon Palace is basically ours now, what are we going to do now?" Granny Rong asked.

"Once we subdue Dragon Palace, we will act together and help it enslave Di Zang Sheng. After that…" Song Qi Yuan pondered.

"Heavenly Court's reinforcements did not show up, it shows that their fight is very intense. Maybe we can help the others a little, even if it is Fang Yuan!"

"That's right, Central Continent is the strongest among the five regions now, we need to weaken it."

"Hehe, who said that Heavenly Court has no reinforcements?"

A change occurred right at this moment!

Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, Shi Miao, and Yang Zi He suddenly attacked, targeting Song Qi Yuan, Qing Yue An, Hua Cai Yun, and Shen Cong Sheng.

How could Song Qi Yuan and the rest expect that their allies would suddenly attack them! They were all hit as they spat out blood and escaped.

Rank eight Gu Immortals had immense foundation, their defenses were extremely thick, even though Zhang Yin and the rest attacked by surprise, they did not kill anyone.

But that was enough.

Song Qi Yuan and the rest were moderately injured as they retreated away.

Zhang Yin and the rest stood at the inner circle, defending Dragon Palace.

Song Qi Yuan and the rest were furious and shocked.

Qing Yue An shouted: "Zhang Yin, are the four of you insane? You want to take Dragon Palace for yourselves?!"

Zhang Yin chuckled: "All four of us are working together, we're not trying to monopolize it."

Shen Cong Sheng had a grim expression: "Don't forget that we set an alliance agreement. You are breaking the agreement now, get ready for the backlash."

Yang Zi He had a plain tone but firm determination: "Even if we die, we will protect Dragon Palace, you will not obtain it."

Hua Cai Yun frowned instantly, saying lightly: "Something is wrong."

Even though Zhang Yin and the rest were lone or demonic rank eight immortals, they were still Eastern Sea people, even though they had some conflicts with Song Qi Yuan and the other super forces' leaders, it was too strange that they would risk their lives and even be willing to die to protect Dragon Palace.

"Why are you doing this?" Song Qi Yuan shouted.

Zhang Yin and the rest started to smile creepily at the same time.

Next, their bodies became taller, their hands and legs became claws, scales appeared on their skin, horns appeared on their forehead as their pupils became vertical-slit pupils.

Their appearances had changed drastically.

Song Qi Yuan and the rest were deeply astounded.

Because these changes were similar to Duke Long's transformation.

Qing Yue An could not contain his anger: "You all gave up your superior statuses as humans to become these inferior variant human dragonmen?!"

"What do you know?"

"Dragonman is the noble race, the future ruler of this heaven and earth!"

"Humans are bound to be exterminated in this world."

Zhang Yin and the rest spoke one by one, at this point, they shouted together: "We are the guardians of Dragon Palace — the Four Dragon Generals!"

Song Qi Yuan and the rest were shocked until they were speechless.

"I get it now!" Hua Cai Yun had a flash of inspiration, cold light shined in her eyes: "The four of them were enslaved by Dragon Palace long ago, they fought against Duke Long earlier in Dragon Palace because that was their responsibility. After Duke Long took away Dragon Palace and refined it, he became their master, but this Duke Long is too crafty,he did not send them away, instead, they stayed by our side. Heavenly Court's reinforcements had arrived long ago, they came with us."

Chapter 1726: Destiny Song

Hua Cai Yun couldn't help but smile bitterly.

It turned out that although they seemed successful, this was just a huge trap meticulously set by Heavenly Court!

"Precisely so." Zhang Yin and the rest smiled calmly.

Qing Yue An and the rest finally reacted.

"In order to assure us, you actually let me enslave Old Man Bei Feng, your schemes are truly deep." Shen Cong Sheng said in a cold tone.

"This was not our intention, it was also not part of Lord Duke Long's plan." Zhang Yin shook his head, as the leader of the group, he said: "Do you know that everything that happened here was already part of Fairy Zi Wei's deductions. She was the one who assigned us this task."

Song Qi Yuan's gaze landed on Dragon Palace again: "So this means that the rank eight Immortal Gu House is actually an enslavement path Immortal Gu House… it can actually enslave rank eight Gu Immortals, and even as many as four! Even after that, it can still continue to suppress and enslave Di Zang Sheng… throughout history, this has to be the number one enslavement path Immortal Gu House!"

Zhang Yin and the rest had a change of expression.

Qing Yue An, Hua Cai Yun, and Shen Cong Sheng looked at Song Qi Yuan for a second, realizing that he had not given up.

Even though there was this accident, Song Qi Yuan and the rest were rank eight Gu Immortals, how could they give up so easily?

Even though they were sneak attacked and got injured, their battle strength was still quite well preserved, if they continued to fight, there was still hope.

It was not easy to sneak attack rank eight Gu Immortals.

Most immortal killer moves would release their aura when activated.

Thus, Zhang Yin and the rest did not use any terrifying killer moves, they had a hard time concealing the aura of their killer moves to begin with.

Methods that could conceal the aura of killer moves were very rare.

Currently, only Southern Border's Wu Yong had such methods. Others, including Heavenly Court's members, did not have any.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions resounded again.

Song Qi Yuan and the rest did not give up, they fought against Zhang Yin and the rest once more.

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

Bai Cang Shui retreated alongside Chen Yi.

Wu Yong and the rest attacked, trying to force her away from the formation behind her, so as to kill these two rank eights from Heavenly Court outside the formation.

Bai Cang Shui moved around in different directions, dodging fatal attacks time and again.

Southern Border's immortals gave her huge pressure, especially Wu Yong, all of his killer moves' auras were concealed before they were unleashed, Bai Cang Shui was very wary of him. Even if Wu Yong did not attack, she had to keep her attention on him at all times.

"Let me down, you should escape!" Chen Yi said.

He was hit by the unorthodox farewell friend wind, he could not move and could only wait for his death.

Right now, his clothes, eyebrows, and hair were vanishing, his limbs were also disappearing, the terrible might of farewell friend wind was about to completely erode his limbs, followed by his body.

Thankfully, farewell friend wind did not spread among people, it only targeted Chen Yi, that gave Bai Cang Shui the courage to protect him.

"You think I want to save you?" Bai Cang Shui transmitted secretly.

Chen Yi was stunned.

He suddenly realized.

As he expected, Bai Cang Shui continued: "I am purposely doing this and pretending that I do not want to give up on you, to put myself in danger and attract the attention of the Southern Border immortals, so that we can stall for time and let the others set up more immortal formations. You are definitely dying, but you can still be useful. I might die too, but we must stall for time. For Heavenly Court, for Central Continent, for the people in this world, so what if we sacrifice ourselves?"

Chen Yi was silent, he suddenly wanted to smile, at this moment, death seemed so insignificant.

Even though he was someone obsessed with authority, he was also someone who upheld humanity's righteousness. He was like Bai Cang Shui, he did not fear sacrifice, if not for this, Fairy Zi Wei would not have made him a member of Heavenly Court.

But Chen Yi could not smile, his face showed even more pain and bitterness, he needed to act, to cooperate with Bai Cang Shui and deceive the Southern Border immortals.

"Let me be useful at the final moment of my life." Chen Yi spoke openly, he was resolved to die.

But at this moment, he heard a song playing by his ears.

In such an intense fight, who would have the mood to sing?

Chen Yi was stunned before his attention was fully drawn to the song.

Bai Cang Shui, Wu Yong, and the rest were in the same situation as him.

The singing voice was illusory and deep, it was filled with conflict and was very unique.

Initially, the song was like a small stream of water in the mountains, flowing slowly. Gradually, the stream turned into flowing lava that expanded the river's width, in the range of mountains, it sounded like a dragon's roaring echo.

At the same time, the river of lava on the mountain turned into a raging tide, swish swish swish, ebb and flow, it continued without stopping.

The lava and waves collided, reacting and creating steam that covered the entire sky.

The steam condensed into clouds that wanted to fly towards the high heavens.

Suddenly, lightning struck and thunder roared, the lightning bolts landed on the clouds as the immortals felt like they had fallen from the sky, they felt a sense of hollowness in their hearts.

Phantom or real, high or low, being proud and confident at times, feeling lost and desperate during disasters. Bending one's back at times, spreading one's words at times…

In the battlefield, all conflict had ceased, everyone was engrossed in the song, they forgot everything else.

But suddenly, the song stopped, everyone woke up immediately.

Chi Qu You had a solemn expression: "What song is this? It is terrifying, it actually made all of us so engrossed in it without resistance!"

Qiao Zhi Cai had a pale face as he said with lingering fear: "Thankfully it stopped, otherwise, none of us would have gotten free, we would have been hit badly."

"What song is this?" Yi Hao Fang asked.

A rank eight Gu Immortal walked out of the formation, he wore a red and white robe, he had extreme elegance as he smiled: "This is my newly created destiny song."

It was Feng Jiu Ge!

"Hmph, destiny? You talk big." Ba Shi Ba snored coldly.

"Unbelievable! This destiny song actually saved my life." Chen Yi cheered, he only had his body and head left, but farewell friend wind had stopped. Even though his injuries were severe, Chen Yi's life was not over.

The Southern Border immortals were dazed.

Wu Yong's farewell friend wind was rank eight. Feng Jiu Ge's destiny song used Fate Armor as the core, it was also rank eight!

"You again!" Wu Yong stared at Feng Jiu Ge with deep anger.

Last time, he wanted to kill Fang Yuan but Feng Jiu Ge saved him.

This time, he wanted to kill Chen Yi but Feng Jiu Ge stopped him yet again.

Twice, Feng Jiu Ge had ruined Wu Yong's plans twice!

And these were two crucial timings.

Even with Wu Yong's supreme disposition and ability to endure any circumstance, he could not help but become very angry.

"Feng Jiu Ge, you are truly an unrivaled genius." Wu Yong squinted his eyes, his voice was cold as a blizzard, it could send a chill down someone's spine: "Come, show me everything you've got, I'll take you on myself."

Saying so, an intense wind blew.

This was Wu Yong's unlimited wind, it had been ravaging the battlefield, like a huge pillar supporting heaven and earth.

This move expended ten thousand of Wu Yong's wind path dao marks!

Unlimited wind was unceasing and grand, it approached Feng Jiu Ge and the rest with divine might.

Feng Jiu Ge smiled bitterly: "Lord Wu Yong is truly powerful, I have no choice but to avoid you."

Bai Cang Shui grabbed Chen Yi: "It is time, let's go!"

Behind the three, the formation expanded, they were successful in retreating back into the formation.

Once they were inside the formation, Feng Jiu Ge spit out a mouthful of blood, his face was pale as paper, he was standing shakily.

"What happened?" Bai Cang Shui quickly supported him.

Feng Jiu Ge smiled with an ugly expression, his breathing was very weak: "My destiny song was only created in a rush, I have not even finished half my song. Because I had no choice but to use it this time, I suffered heavy injuries as a result."

"Brother Feng risked your life to save me, I will never forget this debt of gratitude!" Chen Yi sighed.

"Right now, Central Continent is in chaos, Southern Border's immortals are here with vengeance, I save you for the sake of Central Continent." Feng Jiu Ge shook his head.

Chen Yi looked at Feng Jiu Ge and Bai Cang Shui, thinking of their relentless actions, he laughed with heroism: "No matter how dangerous it is, with people like us that do not fear sacrifice or death, Central Continent will definitely win, Heavenly Court will emerge victorious!"

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei who had been observing Infallible blessed land let out a breath of air as she smiled.

"Truly incredible, Feng Jiu Ge and destiny song!"

Fairy Zi Wei knew about Heavenly Court's plan for destiny Gu. Longevity Heaven was also ambitious towards it. Earlier, Heavenly Court wanted to obtain fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, while now, Longevity Heaven was after fate Gu, they were all trying to obtain destiny Gu.

However, the one who took a big step in this direction was not the two supreme forces, but a lone Gu Immortal.

"Feng Jiu Ge!" Fairy Zi Wei muttered.

Even though she had always thought highly of his talent and ability, she realized now that she had vastly underestimated him.

Chen Yi's sacrifice was certain in Fairy Zi Wei's perspective. Because farewell friend wind could not be undone, unless they had defended against it beforehand.

To think that this rule was overwritten by Feng Jiu Ge today.

In history, there had never been any case of farewell friend wind being broken. Undeniably, after assimilation wind song, Feng Jiu Ge has written history once again!

Emperor City battlefield.

A wave of cheers resounded in Emperor City.

The final competition of Central Continent's Refinement Path Convention had ended.

This meant that this was no longer Heavenly Court's weakness.

The Western Desert Gu Immortals who sensed this quickly retreated, they wanted to escape.

They did not manage to destroy Emperor City or the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

"Everything has ended."

"Sigh, Heavenly Court succeeded in the end."

Western Desert's Gu Immortals were dejected, it was not easy to retreat now, Central Continent was supported with heroes among people, they could not escape so easily.

Fang Yuan had a heavy heart.

He had tried his best but there was no helping it.

Heavenly Court's methods were truly out of his expectations, he could not handle them.

In the end, Heavenly Court's foundation was too deep, Fang Yuan was not their match.

Even though he had obtained many venerable inheritances, through plunder his strength also grew rapidly at an unprecedented speed, Heavenly Court and Central Continent had gone through three million years of accumulation, it was nurtured by the efforts of countless generations of elites!

Chapter 1727: Killing Fang Yuan to Save the World

Fang Yuan's achievements were due to his own hard work and also the help of many predecessors.

Heavenly Court and Central Continent were the same, it was not strange that they could defend against Fang Yuan and Western Desert's immortals. This was their strength and foundation, countless generations of people in Central Continent and Heavenly Court had achieved this.

Their hard work was undeniable be it past or present.

"There is no choice, I need to retreat." Fang Yuan thought.

Li Huang and Qing Ye were trying hard to stall Fang Yuan, but with his methods, he was confident of breaking out.

Fang Yuan no longer had any intention of destroying Emperor City.

At this point, it was useless, furthermore, Central Continent's Gu Immortals were protecting it, it was too hard to destroy it now.

But at this moment, there was a loud sound.

The earth cracked open as a huge Earth Trench emerged from the north to south, devouring all forests or mountains in its path at an extreme speed!

And of all coincidences, Emperor City was right ahead of this expanding Earth Trench.

"Oh no!"

"Protect Emperor City!"

This was out of everyone's expectations.

Central Continent's immortals were busy as they quickly tried to protect Emperor City.

But the might of heaven was unpredictable, Earth Trenches were not normally formed, they were created because the earth veins of the five regions were combining. This was such a grand power of heaven and earth, how could a bunch of Gu Immortals resist it?

Thus, Central Continent's Gu Immortals could only watch as the Earth Trench devoured Emperor City!

Emperor City was unable to fly, it was huge and as the ground cracked, it fell into the Earth Trench, disintegrating continuously.

In this huge city, there were nearly a million people. There were countless Gu Masters, they were all elites gathered from all over the world. Especially when this gathering was meant to resist Fang Yuan's luck, there were many people with strong luck gathered here.

Ye Fan and Hong Yi were part of this group, there were many others similar to them.

"Quickly save them!" Li Huang shouted.

"Hahaha, wishful thinking!" Fang Yuan attacked.

He was in emperor yama form now, it was easy to use soul path killer moves.

Fang Yuan dived into the crowd of a million, he saw Hong Yi and Ye Fan, these two were luck connected to him, it was no wonder that his luck was suppressed all along.

Immortal killer move — Luo Po Seal!

Immortal killer move — Spring Scissors!

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Fang Yuan first used Luo Po seal before turning into the immemorial year monkey and using two time path killer moves.

"No!" Li Huang could not block Fang Yuan's vicious attack in such a rush, he shouted angrily but could only watch as countless lifeforms died in Fang Yuan's hands.

Among them were the elites who took part in the finals of the refinement path competition.

Hong Yi and Ye Fan were not spared.

"Fang Yuan, as a grand rank eight Gu Immortal, you actually slaughtered mortals. You are so vicious and evil, you should die, you deserve death!" Qing Ye's eyes were bloodshot and red, he was incomparably angry as he charged at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's attack caused huge losses to Central Continent!

Qing Ye knew that this Emperor City was an important location of Central Continent, it had human path arrangements that attracted and nurtured generations of elites. With the accumulation over time, there was an abundance of human qi here, it was the greatest breeding ground of Gu Immortals.

Central Continent followed the sect system after all, it was not like the other regions. Emperor City produced many talented people, they were all geniuses with abundant luck. If these people obtained sufficient resources and grew properly, there was a high chance of becoming Gu Immortals!

In the future, during the five regions chaotic war, many Gu Immortals would die, these people were Gu Immortal seeds for Central Continent, so they could produce more immortals in the future.

Fang Yuan's attack almost wiped out people in the city, he killed a good portion of Central Continent's seeds, their potential during the war was greatly lowered.

The losses were too severe, how could Li Huang and Qing Ye not feel enraged, they wanted to tear Fang Yuan to shreds!

After Hong Yi, Ye Fan, and a bunch of talents died, Fang Yuan felt a sensation of relief.

He knew that his luck path was starting to show its advantage.

Taking a final look at the lingering pieces of the descending Emperor City and the corpses that he created, Fang Yuan retreated rapidly.

Li Huang, Qing Ye, and the Immortal Gu Houses started to chase after him relentlessly.

"Demon! Demon!"

"He almost killed everyone in the city, my… my family was inside!"

"Kill him, rid the world of this great harm!"

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were full of rage and killing intent.

Fang Yuan laughed maniacally: "Can you stop me?"

They could not.

While Fang Yuan could not do anything to these Central Continent people, their Immortal Gu Houses and the rank eight Gu Immortals could not blockade Fang Yuan even though they could encircle Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses.

Unless they used an immortal Gu formation or an immortal battlefield killer move.

But in this short time, how could they set it up?

Even if they could set up an immortal Gu formation or battlefield, unless they could kill Fang Yuan rapidly, with his wisdom path attainment and powerful methods, he could escape.

Zhou Xiong Xin's death was the best evidence.

Not only could they not trap him, Fang Yuan could even retaliate.

Boom!

With a strong attack, Fang Yuan almost dismantled an Immortal Gu House.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was inside this house, he was breaking out in cold sweat from fear. This Immortal Gu House quickly moved back to heal, while the other Immortal Gu Houses moved to fill up the gap.

Fang Yuan looked at this house regrettably, even though he did not know that Fang Zheng was inside, his intuition told him that if he destroyed it, he would benefit greatly.

Fang Zheng's existence was a type of restraint and burden on him.

"Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan!" At this time, Bing Sai Chuan contacted him again.

"Bing Sai Chuan, you still have the face to contact me? Today's loss was because of you!" Fang Yuan showed an angry expression.

The truth was, even though Central Continent's Heavenly Court had deep foundation, it was still at a disadvantage against all four other regions.

However, Central Continent's people's united hearts made them a collective force, while the other four regions had their own agendas, even though they were strong, they could not work together.

And in fact, all four regions preserved their strength. For example, even though Eastern Sea attacked with many rank eights, they did not mobilize many rank seven Gu Immortals or Immortal Gu Houses. Western Desert sent rank six and seven Gu Immortals as well as Immortal Gu Houses but did not send rank eight Gu Immortals. Many experts like Xi clan's first supreme elder did not join the battle, they were staying in Western Desert.

Bing Sai Chuan sighed bitterly: "I cannot hold on much longer, we suffered huge losses but there is still a chance! That is Infallible blessed land!"

Originally, Heavenly Court used human path methods to host the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, its goal was to use the countless refinement failures to create the success dao marks in Infallible blessed land.

Right now, fate Gu had not fully recovered, it still lacked the final batch of success dao marks.

Even though the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was completed, the final batch of success dao marks was still being produced, it was going to take some time before it was transported to Heavenly Court.

This was because Infallible blessed land was surrounded in immortal formations now.

Even though these immortal formations stopped the attacks of Southern Border's immortals, it also created problems for the transportation of success dao marks.

After hearing Bing Sai Chuan's explanation, Fang Yuan's mood brightened up: "It seems that Infallible blessed land is our last hope!"

Fang Yuan did not hesitate, he turned around and went towards Infallible blessed land instead.

Behind him, Li Huang and the rest including the Immortal Gu Houses chased with determination.

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

Unlimited wind was like a tall pillar sweeping everything in its path, it tried to destroy Heavenly Court's immortal formation with an unstoppable advancement.

The immortal formation shot out with golden light, resisting it fully.

Wu Yong and the rest had solemn expressions.

Rank eight Gu Immortal Chi Qu You said in a low tone: "Unbelievable, their immortal Gu formations were also amplified! What kind of human path methods actually created these countless white lights?"

Immortal formations were immortal killer moves in essence, they were manipulated by Gu Immortals.

Since Gu Immortals were boosted by heroes among people, immortal formations were naturally powered up too.

Wu Yong expended his own foundation to create the powerful killer move, unlimited wind, even though he still had the advantage now, his gains were smaller than before.

"It seems that we need to cooperate with the outside if we want to destroy the formation. We'll leave the outside to unlimited wind, we need to find the weak point from the inside." Yi Hao Fang said with deep concentration.

Ba Shi Ba pondered: "Times are different now, earlier we attacked by surprise and caught them off-guard. But a long time has passed already, we need to be wary of Heavenly Court's reinforcements. Thus, we need some people to stay outside the formation."

Everyone agreed with Ba Shi Ba's words.

Even though unlimited wind was powerful, it was just a killer move.

Killer moves were fixed, but people could think.

Wu Yong had a heavy heart.

Because they could not destroy the formation rapidly, their sneak attack failed, they had to use brute force now.

Even though Heavenly Court lost many formations in the meantime, they might have lost Immortal Gu but their foundation was untouched.

Chen Yi was meant to die, but Feng Jiu Ge actually managed to save him.

Wu Yong knew that the longer this went on, the more disadvantageous it was for them. They needed to split up now, a group would enter while the rest stayed outside. Of course, that would mean that they could not work together, their efficiency in destroying the formation would be much lower. If Heavenly Court's reinforcements arrive, they would also face greater pressure.

Wu Yong sighed to himself, even though there were great problems in splitting up, they had to do it.

"If only we had more people with us, even though I became the Southern Alliance Leader, I cannot mobilize too many people. With the three rank eights that we have, this is already the best outcome."

Wu Yong breathed in deeply, he started to make arrangements.

Chi Qu You had the highest formation path attainment, he naturally had to go inside. Wu Yong had the number one battle strength, he also had to go into the formation, to protect Chi Qu You and also to fight against strong enemies inside.

Meanwhile, Yi Hao Fang and Ba Shi Ba cultivated transformation path and rule path respectively, they could stay outside. After all, Heavenly Court's reinforcements might be powerful, letting two rank eights stay outside was safer.

Right when Southern Border's Gu Immortals discussed their next action, there was a commotion.

Wu Yong's expression changed, he looked towards the north, saying softly: "Someone's coming."

There were quite a lot of people!

They were led by three rank eights.

An old man carrying a walking cane, he had a kind aura and was the former first supreme elder of Northern Plains' Yao tribe, and the current South Desolation Immortal of Longevity Heaven — Yao Huang.

The second person wore a white robe, he had thick hair, a long and tall body, he was the first supreme elder of Northern Plains' Bai Zu tribe — Heavenly Lord Bai Zu.

The third wore a tall crown and golden cape, he had incredible disposition, it was Gong tribe's external supreme elder — Prince Feng Xian.

Those after them were all elites among immortals.

There were Domination Immortal Chu Du, Toad Fiend Immortal Nu Er Qian, Spear Deity Yuan Rang Zun, Wealth Devouring Boy Nian Er Fu, and others.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortals gathered towards the Southern Border immortals.

"Friends from Northern Plains, what do you want?" Wu Yong asked loudly.

Yao Huang chuckled as he said: "The enemy is before us, we would like to work together with you and attack Heavenly Court!"

Wu Yong laughed loudly, Heavenly Court's reinforcements did not come, instead, he gained some new allies.

Chapter 1728: Agreeing to Ally with Fang Yuan

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

"What formation is this?" Wu Yong asked.

Beside him were the two rank eights, Yi Hao Fang and Chi Qu You, followed by Southern Border's band of rank seven elites.

Not far away stood the leader Yao Huang, followed by the Northern Plains immortals such as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Chu Du.

After some discussion, both sides made a temporary agreement, they decided to cooperate and attack Heavenly Court.

But this was the first time they were working together, the alliance agreement was quite relaxed, they were still wary of each other. Despite this, Wu Yong was already quite satisfied.

"Southern Border and Northern Plains are cooperating, this is an unprecedented event in history!"

"With the help of Northern Plains, we will not lack numbers. Even if Heavenly Court sends reinforcements, Ba Shi Ba and Prince Feng Xian who are outside will be able to last for a while, we will have enough reaction time."

Wu Yong thought to himself.

Beside him, Chi Qu You spoke: "This should be a new formation, I have never seen any records of this."

Wu Yong nodded as he purposely spoke loudly: "In that case, we can only explore and probe this formation."

Over at Northern Plains, Yao Huang heard this as he smiled while grasping his walking cane: "Southern Border allies, wait a while and recover first. My side has just arrived, we are in good condition, we will do the probing."

Wu Yong showed delight on his face, he cupped his fist: "The bravery of Northern Plains is known to all, we will wait here and recover, if anything happens, we will definitely lend a hand."

Yao Huang nodded as he instructed someone to explore the formation.

This batch of Northern Plains Gu Immortals were purposely chosen by Bing Sai Chuan. After receiving orders, Yao Huang gathered these people in the name of Longevity Heaven and brought them here.

Before this, Bing Sai Chuan had already brought Calamity Luck Altar and his comrades to attack Heavenly Court.

It was not that Bing Sai Chuan had purposely diverted his forces, but he had his reservations.

Attacking Heavenly Court was an important matter, it needed to be kept secret. He was afraid that if they expanded the numbers and called too many people, the invasion would fail, they would get exposed and end up losing the battle in the end.

Thus, Bing Sai Chuan only chose the few people he trusted the most.

And undoubtedly, his decision was correct.

Because Prince Feng Xian was the spy of Spirit Affinity House, he was one of the most successful spies in terms of status.

The Northern Plains group was naturally led by Yao Huang.

After losing in Heavenly Court, Bing Sai Chuan sent out orders to Yao Huang first, before contacting Fang Yuan.

Yao Huang knew how important this mission was, because the hope of getting fate Gu from Heavenly Court was getting slimmer now, Infallible blessed land had become the most important battlefield. As long as they destroyed it, Heavenly Court's plan of repairing fate Gu would be foiled.

This way, Heavenly Court would need to try and restore fate Gu once more. The longer this dragged on, the more hope there was for the four regions.

Thus, Yao Huang and Southern Border's immortals joined forces with great sincerity.

Wu Yong purposely spoke loudly, Yao Huang knew his intentions and quickly offered to help, it was his display of sincerity.

Heavenly Court was united in ideals, Central Continent had people's united hearts, while Southern Border and Northern Plains had joined hands for the first time ever, this was truly a new page of history, despite both of them not trusting each other fully yet.

In order to succeed in this attack on Heavenly Court's formation, both sides cooperated earnestly.

Northern Plains sent none other than Wealth Devouring Boy Nian Er Fu. This person had a child's appearance, he had peak rank seven battle strength and cultivated space path, he was able to protect himself.

This formation was not ordinary, it was like an underground cave. The cave was huge and the Gu Immortals were like ants, there were countless stalagmites and stalactites that hung down from the ceiling or protruded from the ground like growing grass. They had all sorts of color and emitted a light that was a dazzling sight.

Nian Er Fu carefully went into the formation under everyone's observation.

He was famous in Northern Plains, he cultivated space path and moved unhindered around battlefields, he was able to preserve his life in dangerous situations and even earn huge profits from it, gaining an immense wealth. This was also why he was called Wealth Devouring Boy.

But at this moment, Nian Er Fu was very alert, he did not dare to be careless.

This was Heavenly Court's formation, any accident and his life would end here.

Nian Er Fu entered the formation as it started to activate, the stalactite and stalagmite started to grow as the rainbow lights enveloped Nian Er Fu.

In everyone's perspective, this underground cave created by the formation was like a fierce beast opening its mouth, it was shutting its mouth now, countless stalactites and stalagmites joined together and wanted to chew this Nian Er Fu into bits of flesh.

Nian Er Fu was very alert, upon sensing this problem, he turned around and ran.

The rainbow light was very troublesome, it hindered his movement ability, it could even penetrate his defense.

"This rainbow light is the exquisite seven orifices formation, let's quickly attack the light and help Nian Er Fu to escape before it's too late." Chi Qu You saw something amiss as he quickly shouted.

Southern Border's and Northern Plains' immortals worked together as killer moves erupted.

Nian Er Fu received a lot of help as he narrowly avoided the gathering of the rainbow light, returning to the main group.

"So close, without all of you, I would have died in there." Nian Er Fu felt great after-fear.

"Your face…" Suddenly, Nu Er Qian pointed at Nian Er Fu's face, showing a look of terror.

"What is it?" Nian Er Fu touched his own face but felt a hard jade stone texture.

"You were still hit. It seems that this formation is not a simple exquisite seven orifices formation, there is also the jade spike formation." Black Extremity said.

Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven had Four Desolation Immortals and Eight Extremities.

Among which, Black Extremity was skilled in formation path, he had incredible talent and had once cheated Old Ancestor Xue Hu by disguising as Sun Ming Lu.

Black Extremity's words received Chi Qu You's acknowledgment: "This is likely a combination formation made from exquisite seven orifices formation and jade spike formation."

"Then how do we break it?" Wu Yong looked at the permeating rainbow light and countless stalactites and stalagmites as he said.

Chi Qu You smiled confidently: "With just the few of us, it is very hard to break this formation. But with the friends of Northern Plains here, this is merely a troublesome issue."

Right when Southern Border and Northern Plains joined forces, Fang Yuan was also fighting against Qing Ye and Li Huang.

"This human path killer move is truly troublesome!" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a cold flickering light.

Li Huang and Qing Ye were boosted by killer move heroes among people, they pursued Fang Yuan relentlessly. As for those Immortal Gu House, only two remained chasing Fang Yuan, while the rest were either dealing with Western Desert's immortals or saving the Central Continent Gu Masters in the Earth Trench.

After getting the information from Bing Sai Chuan, Fang Yuan flew with rapid speed, but the direction was the opposite, he went further and further away from Infallible blessed land.

"It is time." Fang Yuan suddenly waved his sleeves as countless yama children flew out.

Immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

Fang Yuan who was in emperor yama form quickly transformed into a yama child as he mixed in with the crowd.

"Fang Yuan, where do you think you're going!" Li Huang shouted, he was covered in a blazing cloak, burning with intense flames.

"You were hit by the investigative killer move, how can you escape through this method?" Qing Ye snickered in his white robe.

The two Immortal Gu Houses were quite lost, but these two Heavenly Court rank eights targeted Fang Yuan's main body instead.

Evidently, Central Continent's Heavenly Court had already started to make countermeasures against Fang Yuan's familiar face.

"So troublesome." Without a choice, Fang Yuan ascended to heaven, entering white heaven.

Rank nine immortal killer move — Heaven Form!

Using this move, Fang Yuan quickly found a bunch of black-white overturning clouds.

"Oh no, stop him."

"Destroy these overturning clouds!"

Li Huang and Qing Ye had rich battle experiences, they could tell that Fang Yuan was trying to use the clouds to escape.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Why don't you try and deduce my main body again?"

Immortal killer move — Myriad Ghost Sword Dragon!

This was a fusion move that comprised ancient sword dragon transformation, myriad self, yama child, emperor yama, and familiar face, it was also one of Fang Yuan's greatest achievements in his killer move modification a while back.

Once the killer move was used, a loud explosion occurred as countless black dragon-shaped soul beasts flew out, these soul beasts had silver-white claws, teeth, horns, and scales, they were emitting an eerie sword qi at all times.

Countless ghost dragons flew in the sky, some attacked the pursuers while the rest continued to fly aimlessly in a chaotic manner.

"Such an amazing method!" After a brief fight, Li Huang and Qing Ye's expressions changed.

This killer move was threatening to them, especially when the ghost dragons self-detonate, they had incredible might, there was the explosive force of the soul beast, and also the rampaging sword qi that gave it extraordinary power.

Li Huang wore his verdant sun flame cloak but it could not hold up, after tens of self-detonations, the cloak was flickering, the flames had weakened tremendously.

Qing Ye was in an even more pitiful state, he tried to defend himself as he thought to himself in great shock: "How can this move be so powerful?"

This was only natural.

Myriad ghost sword dragon had the same weakness and price as Wu Yong's unlimited wind. It expended the dao marks of the Gu Immortal permanently.

However, unlimited wind used ten thousand dao marks each time, while Fang Yuan's myriad ghost sword dragon used four thousand soul path dao marks per use.

Li Huang and Qing Ye were busy defending themselves while Fang Yuan used the opportunity to escape into the black-white overturning clouds.

After going from white heaven to black cloud, Fang Yuan immediately destroyed the cloud as he used Fixed Immortal Travel as the core to activate a killer move.

After a few breaths of time, he vanished on the spot, arriving in Infallible blessed land.

"To think that Infallible blessed land was here!" Fang Yuan sighed.

Since Bing Sai Chuan called him, he naturally gave him the location of Infallible blessed land.

This place was not like the stone lotus island or dragon whale grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan could enter using his killer move.

"Who?" Fang Yuan's appearance triggered the alertness of the Southern Border and Northern Plains army.

"Me!" Fang Yuan snorted coldly.

The Gu Immortal asking him was full of cold sweat, he felt a strong pressure. Even before Fang Yuan answered, he had already realized this, he regretted his action of asking in reflex almost immediately.

After all, Fang Yuan was the fiercest demon currently renowned in the five regions!

Fang Yuan quickly observed the battlefield, the giant tornado that supported heaven and earth, unlimited wind, was the thing that attracted his attention the most. Next, he looked at Prince Feng Xian for a second before turning to Ba Shi Ba and the other defending Gu Immortals.

"You are here." Chu Du was moderately injured, he flew towards Fang Yuan and greeted.

Prince Feng Xian and Ba Shi Ba looked at Fang Yuan with a complex expression.

Li Huang and the rest had chased Fang Yuan too relentlessly, he only managed to find a chance to teleport here after so long.

Right now, Wu Yong and Yao Huang had not only broken the jade spike exquisite formation, they had also gone past the next two formations, they were stuck at the fourth now.

Chu Du displayed incredible worth during the second formation, but he was injured as a result, because Fang Yuan was coming, he stayed outside to wait for him.

With Bing Sai Chuan's arrangements, Northern Plains' side knew that Fang Yuan was coming, that also meant that the Southern Border immortals knew as well.

Fang Yuan created huge chaos in Northern Plains and Southern Border, the righteous path forces of both regions had suffered losses due to him. Northern Plains' Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was destroyed by Fang Yuan, while many of Southern Border' righteous path super forces were extorted by him.

But now, they were all cooperating against a common enemy, Heavenly Court.

"No matter how strong the formation is, how can it obstruct my path!"

"Time is pressing, I won't explain further, open a path for me, I am going to detonate the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies!"

Fang Yuan nodded towards Chu Du as he attacked the formation, not wasting any time.

Chu Du and the rest were overjoyed, they waited for Fang Yuan and were willing to cooperate with him because of this.

Fang Yuan had dream path methods, as long as he detonated the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and spread the dream realm, this formation would break without fail!

Fang Yuan's arrival was soon found out by Yao Huang and the rest.

Yao Huang took a glance at Wu Yong and the rest, asking purposely: "Oh, Fang Yuan is here already?"

Wu Yong's expression froze slightly, before he turned to Yao Huang: "Let Fang Yuan undergo the alliance agreement first, then tell him that I am willing to forgo our feuds and cooperate temporarily!"

Chapter 1729: Nine-nine Consecutive Unceasing Formation

Because of Yao Huang's notice, Wu Yong was mentally prepared that Fang Yuan was coming.

He was an ambitious person, even though he had deep enmity with Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court was the common foe now. Dealing with Heavenly Court and preventing fate Gu from being fully repaired would give Wu Yong the greatest benefits, for this sake, he could put down his feuds and cooperate with Fang Yuan now.

"Friend Wu Yong is truly wise and clear headed." Yao Huang praised.

Immediately after, Chi Qu You and the rest also resounded: "Not just Alliance Leader Wu Yong, the super forces of Southern Border are also willing to resist Heavenly Court with Fang Yuan ignoring our past feuds."

Fang Yuan had killed many Southern Border Gu Immortal captives for his own gains, but they were also making the same decision now for the sake of the big picture.

They were being logical, but the bigger reason was that this situation was truly dangerous, and Heavenly Court was very powerful!

Bing Sai Chuan not only told Yao Huang and Fang Yuan about Heavenly Court's current situation, the information was also given to Wu Yong and the rest. This made the Southern Alliance immortals even clearer about their current situation.

Heavenly Court and Emperor City were hopeless already, the only chance of victory was here.

Only by using their time well and destroying the formation rapidly could they prevent the final batch of success dao marks from being sent to Heavenly Court, that would force them to hold the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention once again.

"Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, go destroy this formation." At this time, Fang Yuan sent several Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies towards the formation.

In the current era, dream path was still underdeveloped, there were only several seeds, it had not grown yet.

Against the corrosion of the dream realm, almost all immortal Gu formations, regardless of ranks, could not block it. Unless it was an immortal formation possessing dream path Gu worms, or had relevant dream path methods to block that corrosion.

But right when the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies got close to the formation, a change occurred.

Immortal killer move — Shatter Dream!

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

With the use of two killer moves, Fang Yuan's Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies shattered at the first moment, they started to spread towards the surroundings.

Next, these shattered dream realms gathered into new Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies as they attacked Fang Yuan instead.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he was secretly shocked.

He did not expect that Heavenly Court would obtain such methods already.

Even though he knew it was a matter of time, he did not think it would be so fast.

But soon, his dejected feelings vanished, he regained his calm and icy temperament.

Thoughts appeared and clashed in his mind, he rapidly tried to think of a solution to this.

"They can actually reverse my control over the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and the transformation? Is it because Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was captured and his memories were obtained by them?" Fang Yuan was approached by several Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies as he quickly retreated.

He had many powerful killer moves but against the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, they were quite lackluster.

This move was quite invincible in this world, back then, Heaven Overseeing Tower and even Duke Long and Purple Mountain True Monarch were forced to avoid the dream realm.

But thankfully, Fang Yuan was not helpless.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture, the time path clone was bathed in the light of wisdom, it continued to make deductions for him.

Even though Fang Yuan did not have shatter dream killer move to deal with the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, he was very familiar with the killer move pure dream reality seeker transformation.

Even Heavenly Court could not truly comprehend pure dream reality seeker transformation in just a few years. The likely reason was that they had obtained Spectral Soul's memories.

Precisely so, Fang Yuan could use his original pure dream reality seeker killer move to retaliate and use the light of wisdom to create a counter killer move instead.

"The time path clone's deductions will take some time." Fang Yuan considered his countermeasures as he flew into the sky.

Several Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies chased him relentlessly, while a few went towards unlimited wind and the other Gu Immortals.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies self-detonated as unlimited wind was greatly affected, its power was falling rapidly.

Prince Feng Xian and the rest had no choice but to dodge.

Fang Yuan contacted Wu Yong but his first sentence made Wu Yong shook: "Northern Plains' Prince Feng Xian is a spy of Heavenly Court!"

Wu Yong attacked the formation as he asked: "Evidence?"

"My words themselves are evidence. In this situation, I have no reason to lie!" Fang Yuan immediately answered: "I do not have enough dream realms now, I need to gather more dream realms from Southern Border and create Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies to fight. Quickly inform the Gu Immortals there to support me."

Fang Yuan and Heavenly Court were opposing enemies, his accusation towards Prince Feng Xian had no evidence, but it was like he said, his words were clear evidence.

After all, the world knew about his Spring Autumn Cicada.

This secret had once caused Fang Yuan great problems when it was exposed, but now, it gained Wu Yong's trust.

At the crucial moment, Wu Yong did not hesitate, since he was working with Fang Yuan already, they might as well enter a deeper cooperation, Heavenly Court was the true enemy now!

"Alright, I will tell the others, you can go now." At this moment, Wu Yong felt a complex emotion. He had never thought that one day, he would purposely give the orders to receive Fang Yuan's arrival!

At this moment, Chi Qu You's voice resounded in Wu Yong's ears: "I have already deciphered this formation, quickly attack this place, it is the true formation core!"

Wu Yong was overjoyed, he forgot about Fang Yuan for a moment as he gave orders to attack the location that Chi Qu You pointed out, after destroying the formation core, this formation became much slower and duller.

Black Extremity Sun Ming Lu looked at them with great admiration and surprise.

After entering the formation, Chi Qu You had always outperformed him and comprehended the profundities of the formations using a shorter time, he had no choice but to feel admiration.

"We should follow Lord Chi Qu You's arrangements, let's assist these Southern Border allies." Black Extremity put down his competitive spirit as he suggested towards Yao Huang who was beside him.

Yao Huang frowned but agreed.

Fang Yuan easily got rid of his pursuers, these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were inferior to Li Huang and Qing Ye.

Using Fixed Immortal Travel's killer move, Fang Yuan went back to Southern Border and obtained a large number of dream realms, with them, he created more Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and went for Heavenly Court's formation.

In this situation, dealing with the enemy's Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies was secondary, the main goal was to destroy the formation and stop Heavenly Court from repairing fate Gu.

Fang Yuan had never forgotten his true motive.

However, all the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies who got close to the formation shattered and were turned into enemies as they attacked Fang Yuan once again.

Furthermore, these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies could communicate, Fang Yuan's side was suffering more losses than gains.

These situations started to make Fang Yuan realize: "It seems that Heavenly Court has already modified the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies!"

At this time, Wu Yong transmitted: "Fang Yuan, continue to send more Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies at the formation, we have already found many flaws of the formation."

Fang Yuan thought in his mind: "It seems that Heavenly Court did not truly merge dream path methods with this formation. Each time they deal with my Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, they are also disrupting with the formation's operations itself, causing flaws to form."

These flaws were simply too obvious to Chi Qu You and Black Extremity. Using these chances, Wu Yong and the rest attacked with great results.

But this way, Fang Yuan's dream realms would continuously be turned into Heavenly Court's resources, they will gain an increasing number of Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

"It seems that I really need to unravel their Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies!" Fang Yuan's heart sank slightly, this was a problem that he could not avoid resolving.

It was not that he did not want to enter the formation to help out, but there were already Chi Qu You, Wu Yong, and others, with his monopoly over dream path methods, he was much needed outside.

Fang Yuan started to fight against these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

At the same time, he transmitted to the rest: "There is an important thing now, Heavenly Court's human path killer move, can anyone get rid of these white lights?"

Nobody answered.

In the end, Yi Hao Fang answered dejectedly: "Human path's specialty is in support, because human path dao marks will not interrupt other paths' dao marks or conflict with them. Unless we use human path methods that are at least rank eight, we cannot resolve this."

Yi Hao Fang cultivated transformation path but he was also very skilled at supporting others. This was because of his signature killer move — Human Transformation. With his words, Fang Yuan gave up on this aspect.

They could not unravel heroes among people, while Prince Feng Xian was also a huge threat.

Fang Yuan, Wu Yong, and the rest did not want to expose him for now. Killing a rank eight was too difficult.

They might as well pretend to not know and focus on breaking the formation instead, preventing Heavenly Court from succeeding was more important.

As time passed, Fang Yuan finally gained some breakthrough in his deductions.

He took a risk and captured an enemy Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body successfully, experimenting on it.

"This is actually a complete Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body! It has been modified entirely, it is now truly the eleventh extreme physique." Fang Yuan sighed at his great gains.

He quickly modified pure dream reality seeker transformation as he started to learn Heavenly Court's method.

As his Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies became modified again, they accompanied Wu Yong and Yao Huang, destroying many formations in succession.

"There are still more?" Yao Huang frowned deeply.

One formation after another formation, it was as if Heavenly Court had an unlimited number of formations.

This scene made Wu Yong and the rest feel a little dejected.

"Strange, how can Heavenly Court possibly set up so many immortal formations? Unless…" Black Extremity hesitated.

Chi Qu You pondered as he said: "I understand, this is the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation!"

"Nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, this name is quite familiar…" Wu Yong had a bad feeling.

Chi Qu You sighed: "Legend says that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable predicted Heavenly Court's problem in the future and set up the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation. When Limitless Demon Venerable attacked Heavenly Court, he entered this formation and only broke out after destroying a hundred formations."

"This formation is actually a giant compound formation, it can mix and match using its nine sub-formations, the true problem is that when we destroy a formation, Heavenly Court would be able to set up a new one at the core area, as long as our breaking speed is not as fast as their setting up speed, this will be endless."

Chi Qu You's words were like a cold bucket of water poured onto these immortals.

What should they do now?

Chapter 1730: Situation

Wu Yong, Yao Huang and the rest were a little lost.

The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to deal with Limitless Demon Venerable. According to legends, Limitless Demon Venerable had to break a hundred formations before he escaped.

How could they possibly do the same?

And the most unsettling thing was, they needed to fight against time, once fate Gu recovers completely, there would be zero chance of victory.

"What do we do?" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu frowned.

"This is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's arrangement, no wonder! No wonder!" Black Extremity realized at once.

Chi Qu You was very troubled: "Even if we gather all the formation path Gu Immortals in the world to deduce this formation, I'm afraid the chances of victory are slim. Moreover, we have less and less time now…"

This formation path great expert who had displayed great value in this battle as one of the Southern Alliance's leaders had the intention of backing down.

Wu Yong suddenly laughed loudly.

"Alliance Leader, why are you laughing? Do you have any way to break this formation?" Chi Qu You asked in perplexity.

Wu Yong shook his head: "Even though I have no method to do so, I have already seen through Heavenly Court's facade. Don't worry too much, in my opinion, we are overestimating this difficulty."

"Why? Think about it."

"Back then, the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. It was used by countless Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to resist Limitless Demon Venerable. But it was unable to succeed, Limitless Demon Venerable broke out in the end. Since it was broken before, this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation had already been damaged once in a brutal manner."

"Even if Heavenly Court had immense foundations and repaired all of the Immortal Gu, in the worst case scenario, we are facing the complete and even modified nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation. But the defending Gu Immortals are not all Heavenly Court members. In fact, there might be few Heavenly Court members here. Li Huang and Qing Ye are at Emperor City, Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, Yuan Qiong Du, Che Wei, and Cong Yan are fighting in Heavenly Court. Central Continent is being attacked by all four regions now, they were forced to set this formation here, it shows that they are low in manpower, their members are too sparsely distributed, they can only go on the defensive now."

Wu Yong's eyes were shining with bright light, he displayed overwhelming confidence and great wisdom in his grasp over the situation.

He continued: "And most importantly, they've already shown how weak they are! Earlier, Chen Yi and Bai Cang Shui came to fight us, Chen Yi was nearly beaten to death. Everyone, if this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation is truly impenetrable, why would Chen Yi and Bai Cang Shui risk their lives? They must be stalling time for more formations to be set up."

"Earlier, our attack caused them to take this huge risk. Right now, we have the help of our Northern Plains friends, this is a great opportunity. Even though this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation is powerful, it still depends on who is controlling it, and who is attacking!"

"That's right, that's very logical!"

"Haha, indeed, the urgent matter now is to attack quickly. Heavenly Court's defenses are not as strong as they seem."

"I am ashamed, I was actually fear-stricken due to the reputation of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable."

Wu Yong's words raised everyone's morale, their offenses became stronger, they were more determined now.

Wu Yong smiled but he mentally sighed.

Everyone here was an elite, but they were actually intimidated by this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, it was not because they were stupid, but because they were facing huge pressure.

Bing Sai Chuan notified many people of the situation, they worked together and attacked this formation, desperately holding onto this final hope, but this action had a weakness, it made everyone aware of the urgency of this situation.

If they were careless, they would incur huge losses as Heavenly Court retaliates.

This was Central Continent after all.

They did not have Fixed Immortal Travel's killer move, even if they did, Heavenly Court had methods to counter them.

Thus, it was difficult for the immortals to retreat.

To play safe, now was the time to retreat. The longer they dragged it, the harder it would be to leave Central Continent.

"Eastern Sea's and Western Desert's Gu Immortals are probably already retreating. These two regions are in disunity, they are not like our Southern Border and Northern Plains which can gather the strength of many righteous path forces."

"Now, it will depend on us, whether we can rapidly break the formation and intercept the final batch of success dao marks."

"Sigh! We were still banking on Fang Yuan's dream path methods earlier to deal with this formation. To think that Heavenly Court also had methods to control the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies. Was it because they captured Spectral Soul?"

"I wonder who the person inside this formation that stopped Fang Yuan is?"

Wu Yong continued to guess and evaluate the situation.

Inside the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, Feng Jiu Ge had a pale expression but he smiled warmly.

"Huang Er, good job!" He looked at Feng Jin Huang as he smiled, feeling extremely proud.

The one who stopped Fang Yuan was none other than Feng Jiu Ge's daughter — Feng Jin Huang!

Feng Jin Huang pursed her lips as she said: "Father, I do not dare to claim credit, I could use the Immortal Gu and activate an immortal killer move because of this formation's help."

"Even so, resisting Fang Yuan is an incredible feat, Feng Jin Huang, you have already done an amazing job for Heavenly Court." Bai Cang Shui smiled.

Chen Yi nodded as he looked at Feng Jiu Ge and Feng Jin Huang: "She truly takes after her father."

Feng Jiu Ge saved his life while Feng Jin Huang was shockingly talented, this made Chen Yi feel a sense of gratitude and admiration towards this pair of father and daughter.

Heavenly Court.

A round of ferocious attacks had ended.

Duke Long's rapidly breathing slowed down.

He looked at the Seven Extreme Desolation, which was covered in injuries but remained standing, as he snorted coldly.

"I did not destroy it after all. Is it because of my injuries…"

Normally speaking, Duke Long with the support of heavenly dragon's last stand had incredible power, he could definitely defeat the Seven Extreme Desolation. Even if this ancient battle formation was in its strongest form in history.

But Duke Long was restrained by his injuries.

These were mostly old injuries that were sustained earlier when Duke Long snatched Dragon Palace, he was hurt by the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

"Without these injuries, I would have destroyed the Seven Extreme Desolation already. My estimations were slightly off, but as time passes, it will not obstruct me anymore!"

Duke Long snorted coldly in his mind.

Earlier, he ignored his own injuries to fight, but now, he had to face the Seven Extreme Desolation.

The contest between experts usually depended on minor details like this.

Even though Duke Long could suppress the Seven Extreme Desolation, he was initially stuck at a passive spot, but even now, he could not gather enough strength to destroy it.

After an intense eruption of attacks, Duke Long's offenses became weaker, he started to move around.

Bing Sai Chuan and the rest found some relief, Duke Long was giving them too much pressure.

Fairy Zi Wei and the rest had complex expressions. More and more Heavenly Court members learned that Duke Long's time was almost up. This was the final battle of his life! He was like a firework, he could only shine right before he fades away for good, after this battle, Heavenly Court would lose this legendary great expert!

Suddenly, Fairy Zi Wei received Duke Long's transmission.

"Fairy Zi Wei, how is the situation?"

Fairy Zi Wei quickly answered.

"Emperor City was destroyed, countless mortals died… Li Huang and Qing Ye are rushing to Infallible blessed land… over at Hidden Dragon Cave, the Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals are fighting intensely as well…"

Duke Long muttered to himself for a while before he said to Fairy Zi Wei: "Very good, I was not wrong about you. Thanks to your arrangements and planning, we managed to secure all three locations. Emperor City was destroyed by a natural disaster, it was not your fault."

Duke Long did not stint on his praise towards Fairy Zi Wei. He knew that although he was putting up an incredible fight now, it was thanks to Fairy Zi Wei who kept control of the situation from the background.

Fairy Zi Wei felt even more admiration towards Duke Long, she said sincerely: "This was all thanks to Lord Duke Long, you obtained Dragon Palace. Who would think that Dragon Palace actually contains the rank eight dream path Immortal Gu — Dream Token, it allows Dream Token to enslave rank eight Gu Immortals! With Zhang Yin and the rest, our weakness in manpower was eliminated. Lord Duke Long even sustained huge injuries to conceal the identities of Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, and the rest. This allowed our plan in Eastern Sea to succeed, otherwise, if these Eastern Sea rank eights joined any of the three battlefields, we would be in trouble."

Duke Long: "That's right, I was also surprised by the existence of Dream Token."

He thought back to the battle in Eastern Sea.

Zhang Yin and the rest appeared together, it was a surprise to Duke Long. They were either lone immortals or demonic cultivators, they were lofty and proud rank eight existences, to think that they would be working together despite having no relationship in usual times.

Duke Long became more suspicious at the later parts of the battle.

Zhang Yin and the other immortals trusted each other deeply during the fight!

And what truly made Duke Long confident of his guess was that after Duke Long defeated the four Gu Immortals, Dragon Palace flew away. The four returned and did not chase after Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace, instead, they continued to attack Duke Long.

If they all had their own intentions and wanted Dragon Palace, how could they stay to deal with Duke Long in such a manner?

Normally speaking, with Duke Long's battle strength, these four would chase after Dragon Palace. After all, Dragon Palace had flown away with great commotion, there were possibly other Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals too. By fighting Duke Long, it seemed like they were helping Dragon Palace stall for time. (Refer to Chapter 1689)

Duke Long had sensed acutely that these four Gu Immortals were related to Dragon Palace. After he obtained Dragon Palace and refined it, his guesses were confirmed.

Because he was prepared for it, he did not let Zhang Yin and the rest get exposed. If they were exposed then, the other Eastern Sea Gu Immortals might not die anyway, the main matter for Heavenly Court now was to repair fate Gu.

Thinking about it, Duke Long instructed Fairy Zi Wei: "Pay more attention to Hidden Dragon Cave, we cannot be careless. The five regional walls are vanishing, the regions are becoming one, by then, there will be chaos and huge battles, Di Zang Sheng's battle strength will reach a terrifying level, he will be on par with me."

Towards Di Zang Sheng, Duke Long had a clearer understanding than Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei immediately understood Duke Long's intent.

The situation was turning more stable now, Infallible blessed land, Heavenly Court, and Hidden Dragon Cave were under Heavenly Court's control.

Li Huang, Qing Ye, and the Immortal Gu Houses were about to reach Infallible blessed land.

The only possible problem was Hidden Dragon Cave.

Duke Long was not afraid of Dragon Palace changing owners, he placed Dragon Palace there as a trap to begin with. The design of Dragon Palace was such that only dragonmen could control it. It was impossible to work around this limitation, unless they took apart Dragon Palace. Even most transformation path methods were not effective.

Duke Long was afraid that Dragon Palace would destabilize and release Di Zang Sheng.

Di Zang Sheng hated Heavenly Court and Duke Long immensely. With a boost in strength, it would definitely take revenge.

Duke Long was going to die soon but Di Zang Sheng was virtually undying.

If Fang Yuan and the rest made use of this battle strength, there would be huge problems!

Chapter 1731: Five Regional Formation

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

The tornado resembling a heavenly pillar whipped up a storm as it crashed towards Heavenly Court's formation.

Prince Feng Xian and Ba Shi Ba, who were outside, stared at the horizon.

There, two specks of light tore through the sky, the figures of two rank eight Gu Immortals were shown gradually.

They were Li Huang and Qing Ye.

"We finally arrived!"

"Not bad, we were not late."

Li Huang and Qing Ye had finally arrived.

"Where is that scoundrel Fang Yuan?" Li Huang's eyes shined with orange-red light, he tried to investigate.

He was filled with grudge towards Fang Yuan.

Earlier when Fang Yuan retreated, he purposely chose the opposite direction of Infallible blessed land, he made Li Huang and the others go very far away.

After that, Fang Yuan found a chance to use Fixed Immortal Travel and arrived at Infallible blessed land, Li Huang and the rest were left in the dust.

Central Continent's Heavenly Court did not have Beacon Towers, Li Huang and Qing Ye had to rush to Infallible blessed land through a very long distance.

"They should be inside the formation." Qing Ye responded, his gaze swept past the formation and landed on the unlimited wind.

"This killer move is very strong! It is very threatening to our formation, we should get rid of it."

"This Wu Yong has such a killer move and farewell friend wind, if possible, we should try to kill him! If he returns to Southern Border, he will be a huge problem for Heavenly Court in the future!"

Li Huang and Qing Ye discussed before they changed directions, moving towards the unlimited wind killer move.

Prince Feng Xian and Ba Shi Ba had sensed them already, they also rushed there.

"Go." Prince Feng Xian shouted as he waved his sleeves, hundreds of fireballs blew out.

"You're using fire to attack me? Laughable." Li Huang snorted and did not dodge, verdant sun flame cloak was blazing on his back.

Prince Feng Xian's fireballs landed on Li Huang but did not cause any damage, it even increased the power of verdant sun flame cloak.

Prince Feng Xian's expression did not change, he pointed at Li Huang.

Whoosh.

The flames on Li Huang turned purple instantly. The purple flames infiltrated the orange-red verdant sun flame cloak as it tried to disintegrate the defensive killer move.

Li Huang's expression changed.

Prince Feng Xian wanted to keep him busy, he charged towards Li Huang.

The two fought in the sky, causing blazing flames to emerge and scorch the earth, the temperature of the battlefield was rising.

Ba Shi Ba watched Prince Feng Xian's battle as he thought: "Hmph, this Prince Feng Xian is still acting, he is really well concealed."

Fang Yuan's side left Prince Feng Xian and Ba Shi Ba outside to guard the formation.

Ba Shi Ba had already been informed of Prince Feng Xian's identity through Wu Yong, but he pretended to not know.

It was like how Wu Yong and Fang Yuan predicted, unless it was necessary, Prince Feng Xian did not want to expose his identity. The truth was, Heavenly Court would rather make some sacrifices than to expose Prince Feng Xian. During the five regions chaotic war, he would have more value.

Prince Feng Xian and Li Huang were fire path rank eights, the two fought in the sky before fighting on the ground, they dyed the sky red, they made rivers dry up, the ground cracked from their attacks, clouds vaporized, countless lifeforms fled for their lives.

Ba Shi Ba and Qing Ye cultivated rule path and dark path respectively. Even though their fight did not cause as much of a commotion as Li Huang and Prince Feng Xian, it was much more ruthless.

Li Huang knew about Prince Feng Xian's true identity, they were just acting even though the commotion was huge.

But Ba Shi Ba and Qing Ye were true enemies.

Ba Shi Ba shrieked in a strange tone as many profound lights stabbed or slashed towards Qing Ye like blades or swords.

Three consecutive hits!

Four consecutive hits!

Five consecutive hits!

…

Each profound light had moderate power, but when they landed on Qing Ye, the damage accumulated rapidly.

This was the consecutive attack method that Ba Shi Ba trained in his life.

This kind of rule path supplementary killer move could allow a certain killer move to gain a huge boost in power.

The condition was that Ba Shi Ba had to use that killer move and could not change to other methods.

Qing Ye was forced to retreat gradually, sweat appeared on his forehead: "I cannot let him continue, once he reaches eighteen consecutive hits, my defenses will fail."

Qing Ye's activated an immortal killer move, his figure vanished and turned into darkness.

In the sky, it was like a blob of ink had landed in water and expanded endlessly.

Ba Shi Ba saw this and hesitated: "This is likely Qing Ye's signature killer move — Expanding Night Sky."

Both sides had information about each other, Ba Shi Ba and Qing Ye had a certain level of understanding of each other.

Expanding night sky was an immortal battlefield killer move, it was quite special. Normal immortal battlefields were formed after some preparation. Meanwhile, expanding night sky would continue to increase in size and range, this move had no limit in theory.

As long as Qing Ye had enough time, he could even spread this immortal battlefield killer move to cover the whole of white heaven!

Ba Shi Ba flew backwards.

He thought about it and decided to avoid the enemy.

Expanding night sky was an immortal battlefield, if Ba Shi Ba went in, his rule path would be weakened by the dark path environment.

Of course, the bigger reason was Prince Feng Xian.

Ba Shi Ba knew that Prince Feng Xian was a traitor, if he went into the immortal battlefield, he would not be able to see anything outside. Qing Ye might even let Prince Feng Xian and Li Huang into the battlefield to deal with Ba Shi Ba.

By then, Ba Shi Ba would have to fight three enemies, it would be dangerous.

The battle of two pairs of rank eights went into a short deadlock.

A moment later, many Immortal Gu Houses appeared on the horizon.

Among them were Frost Dragon Manor and Wind Sweeping Building.

These Immortal Gu Houses were originally protecting Emperor City, now that Emperor City was history, the Immortal Gu Houses carried all their Gu Immortals and arrived here as reinforcements.

Frost Dragon Manor was at the front, it started to shine in a light blue aura.

The light formed into a dragon shape, it was a hornless dragon!

The light blue hornless dragon opened its mouth as countless hailstones shot towards Ba Shi Ba.

Ba Shi Ba's speed fell drastically, he snorted coldly, avoiding Qing Ye as he used his killer move on Frost Dragon Manor.

Boom boom boom!

Frost Dragon Manor continued to take a beating, its walls were cracking, tiles were sent flying.

As it resisted, the second light blue hornless dragon formed, it coiled around the first one before coiling around the entire Frost Dragon Manor.

Frost Dragon Manor's defense surged as a result, while the light blue hornless dragon opened its mouth and shot out a tattered mysterious light.

"This Immortal Gu House has the power to expel my killer move's damage!" Ba Shi Ba's expression sank a little, he could not destroy this Immortal Gu House in a short time, if they continued, expanding night sky would trap him, he had to retreat and pull some distance now.

At this time, Wind Sweeping Building entered the battlefield as well.

It did not assist Qing Ye or Li Huang, instead, it directly entered the unlimited wind killer move reaching towards the sky.

"Good wind, good wind, give me some time, I will be able to make this wind my own!" The current generation Wind Sweeping Building Lord laughed loudly.

Due to Wind Sweeping Building's interference, unlimited wind started to weaken again.

More and more Immortal Gu Houses joined the battlefield, Fang Yuan's side was getting more perilous.

"Hold on, we're coming!"

At the crucial moment, a crack formed in the Heavenly Court formation, many Immortal Gu Houses flew out, there were Southern Border's Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, Great Space Temple, Bay Pavilion, Unfixed Manor, as well as Northern Plains' Fingerprint Bridge, Demonic Ape Hall, and Minor Sun Building.

With these seven Immortal Gu Houses helping, Ba Shi Ba's pressure fell greatly.

Both sides entered a chaotic battle, Immortal Gu Houses rampaged and exchanged killer moves, intense fireworks that had dazzling colors were created, at once, the battle was stuck in a deadlock yet again.

Within the formation.

Wu Yong and the rest had dark expressions.

Even though they opened a crack in time and sent out the Immortal Gu Houses, stabilizing the situation outside, they had also expended their trump card in advance.

The situation was getting more disadvantageous.

Prince Feng Xian was a problem, Heavenly Court's battlefield was also hopeless, it all depended on whether Fang Yuan and the rest could destroy the formation now.

"At our speed, the chance of victory is becoming increasingly slim." Fang Yuan sighed as he asked: "Is Tao Zhu's five regional true inheritance able to deal with this formation?"

Back then, he had set a trap in the five regional mountain range to target the Southern Border and Heavenly Court Gu Immortals. During the battle, Wu Yong destroyed the entire five regional mountain range and accidentally awakened Tao Zhu's will, he had a chance to inherit the five regional true inheritance.

Fang Yuan had to retreat at that time, so the five regional true inheritance ended up in the hands of the Southern Border Gu Immortals.

According to Fang Yuan's deductions, the five regional true inheritance could mimic the five region's regional walls. Within the regional walls, Gu Immortals would be suppressed, they would face a backlash whenever they used any immortal killer move.

Be it Immortal Gu House or immortal formation, they were immortal killer moves in essence.

Fang Yuan thought about it, if they could use the methods in the five regional true inheritance against Heavenly Court's formation, it might have some effect.

Wu Yong and Chi Qu You looked at each other, Wu Yong said: "I obtained the five regional true inheritance, there is indeed a method to create the five regional walls in the true inheritance, but…"

Chi Qu You added: "But this method uses the earth veins to set up the formation, it is very troublesome and complicated."

Tao Zhu was able to create the five regional mountain range back then because he used the earth vein and a formation.

After Fang Yuan left the battlefield, Wu Yong obtained the five regional true inheritance, but he found that the essence of it was the five regional formation.

Wu clan was not proficient in formation path, Wu Yong thus worked together with Chi Qu You, as the latter also learned about the profundity of the five regional formation.

"Do we really need the earth vein to set up the five regional formation?" Fang Yuan frowned deeply: "Wait, I heard that not long ago, Hou clan's Gu Immortal obtained a wild earth vein Immortal Gu from the Earth Trench? Can we use that Gu in place of the earth vein?"

The immortals heard this as they shook.

Wu Yong and Chi Qu You looked at each other, sighing at Fang Yuan's quick thinking.

Chi Qu You shook his head: "The truth is, I have already obtained earth vein Immortal Gu through a transaction with Hou clan. But to use this earth vein Immortal Gu in place of the actual earth vein, we will need to modify the five regional formation. I have been trying and have made some progress, but I am still far from success."

Often, Gu Immortals took years to modify one immortal killer move.

Even though Chi Qu You had high formation path attainment level, his wisdom path methods were lacking, he could not make rapid progress.

Fang Yuan's eyes flickered with bright light: "This five regional formation is likely our breakthrough chance! Chi Qu You, even though you cannot do it alone, with me and Black Extremity, there is a chance, let's try."

Chapter 1732: Calamity Luck Altar's Counterattack

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

"What are they trying to do?" Chen Yi and the rest discovered the irregular behavior of Fang Yuan's group.

Feng Jiu Ge was still pale, he sized up the situation and frowned: "They are actually setting up a formation!"

"Formation within a formation?" Bai Cang Shui snorted: "They are simply underestimating us."

Arranging a formation within a formation was very difficult, and this difficulty was further raised when trying to arrange the formation within an enemy's formation.

Different from Immortal Gu Houses, immortal formations had requirements towards their surrounding environment. The surrounding natural dao marks would have a great influence on most immortal formations.

Heavenly Court's side naturally would not let Fang Yuan's group do as they wished. They immediately activated the formation, waves after waves of attacks charged towards the newly created formation base.

"You wish!"

"With us here, you can set up the formation with peace of mind."

Wu Yong, Yao Huang and others guarded the four directions around the formation base, blocking Heavenly Court's offenses.

Within the formation base, Chi Qu You, Black Extremity, and Fang Yuan were setting up a formation with urgency.

"Three hundred and sixty fire crow Gu have been placed!" Black Extremity wiped the sweat on his forehead.

"We are still lacking forty-four rank five sole blade Gu, when are they coming?" Chi Qu You spoke while contacting other Gu Immortals, treasure yellow heaven had become their most effective form of goods transportation.

Fang Yuan's body shook slightly, the Immortal Gu in his hand scattered down like rain that caused splattering noises.

Several breaths later, he let out a breath of air and stopped his movement: "Rank six instant chain Immortal Gu has been placed properly."

Chi Qu You and Black Extremity took a quick glance at him while thinking: "Unbelievable! Fang Yuan's wisdom path and formation path attainment levels are so high. Not only did he deduce a completely new five regional formation in such a short period of time, he is also setting up the immortal formation with such fluid movement."

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was at grandmaster which was lower than Chi Qu You's and Black Extremity's, but he had plenty of experience in setting up formations.

Self cleansing formation, Omni-directional Travel ancient battle formation, dragon scale sea's food path immortal formation, coiling thread Gu formation, immemorial year beast fishing formation, flood discharge formation, self will heaven sealing formation, year essence pool, and so on had been personally set up by him.

Thus, although it was his first time setting up the five regional formation, he was not overwhelmed but worked with great proficiency.

"If I had to set up the formation alone, it would take a lot of time. But with Chi Qu You and Black Extremity's help, we can set up five regional formation quickly. We need to finish this quickly!" Fang Yuan was fully focused and made use of every second.

Heavenly Court battlefield.

"Li Huang, Qing Ye, and others have already reached Infallible blessed land. Wu Yong's unlimited wind is suppressed by Wind Sweeping Building. Prince Feng Xian's identity has not been exposed. But I don't understand the intention of Fang Yuan's group in trying to set up a formation within a formation. Additionally, our reinforcements are about to reach Hidden Dragon Cave." Fairy Zi Wei reported the situation to Duke Long.

Duke Long responded while fighting: "Although Prince Feng Xian's identity is not exposed currently, we cannot rule out the case that Fang Yuan knows about it but kept silent. You need to pay attention to this point, let Chen Yi and the rest take note of the situation and be prepared to help out Prince Feng Xian at any time."

Fairy Zi Wei: "Yes."

Knowing that the situation was still in their grasp, Duke Long concentrated on Seven Extreme Desolation again.

"It is time." Duke Long clenched his claws, feeling the vast force within his body.

Immortal killer move — Heavenly Dragon's Last Stand!

After using this killer move, his lifespan could only decrease and could not be increased. At the same time, it would provide Duke Long with increasing battle strength as time passed!

In a short period of time, Duke Long's battle strength had soared once again and reached an astonishing level.

Roar!

A dragon roar resounded as purple-gold dragon-shaped qi erupted.

Boom—!

Seven Extreme Desolation simply could not react in time, it only saw Duke Long suddenly disappear into thin air, before it flew away like a meteor stuck by boundless force.

Seven Extreme Desolation was sent flying and crashed into the qi wall violently, countless cracks appeared on the giant's body.

"Damn it, his speed increased again!"

"All our investigative killer moves are blocked by Duke Long, we are simply unable to catch his trace."

"We will be caught in a passive state if this goes on."

"If this continues any longer, Duke Long's battle strength will start suppressing us completely."

"In that case, let's use offense as defense, we will be able to hit Duke Long as long as we attack in every direction with our killer moves!"

The Seven Big Dipper Immortals conversed quickly, the Seven Extreme Desolation giant rose and was about to step into the battlefield again.

Duke Long suddenly appeared above the giant.

"Still want to stand up?" Duke Long gave a ferocious smile while slamming his right dragon claw down.

Boom—!

The dragon claw was tiny like an ant compared to the giant Seven Extreme Desolation, but it inflicted an enormous injury on the giant.

As air currents surged, the Seven Extreme Desolation giant's head was smashed into paste. The headless giant was forced down to the ground, creating a human shaped crater.

Dust and stones were sent flying as the surroundings shook.

"Ah…" Duke Long slowly retracted his claw while hovering in the air, letting out a satisfied grunt.

Renewed strength spread throughout Duke Long's body again, his muscles expanded once again and bones grew rapidly. His dragon scales became bigger and tougher, his crown-like dragon horns turned increasingly ferocious as spikes extended everywhere.

Duke Long's whole body, that had already surpassed normal people's height, expanded once again. A thatched hut's ceiling would probably only reach his waist.

His long purple hair had been soft and elegant, but now each strand was thick and strong and reached until his feet. Purple-gold lightning flickered in between his hair.

His dragon tail grew longer, it had been less than ten feet before but now it was tens of feet long.

"Duke Long, go and die!" A Northern Plains' rank eight suddenly appeared behind Duke Long. He was determined to succeed as he smashed a killer move which he had prepared for a long time at Duke Long's back.

Snap.

In just an instant, Duke Long's dragon tail whipped and sent this rank eight Gu Immortal flying.

Guh.

The Northern Plains' Gu Immortal coughed out mouthfuls of blood, his spine was instantly broken and his organs were displaced. The most fatal thing was the backlash from his own immortal killer move which sent him to the verge of death.

At the next moment, three Northern Plains' Gu Immortals made their move at the same time, three killer moves struck Duke Long in succession.

"We hit him!"

But the joy on these three Northern Plains' Gu Immortals' faces froze immediately.

As dust dissipated, Duke Long could be seen standing upright. Purple-gold dragon scales that flickered with metallic luster covered his whole body.

There was not even a scar.

"What?!"

"We had already calculated it, our three killer moves coordinated with each other and increased each other's power!"

"What kind of defense is this!"

The three Northern Plains' Gu Immortals were shaken before they felt uneasy and retreated immediately.

"Are you scratching my back?" Duke Long slowly turned around, his expressionless dragon eyes stared at the three retreating Gu Immortals.

The three Gu Immortals immediately felt alerts ringing in their mind, an intense sense of danger suffocated them as if a mountain was pressing on them!

"Duke Long, don't try to leave, we are your opponent!"

The Seven Extreme Desolation giant had obtained a brief respite and stood up once again. Their smashed head had already mostly recovered.

"Hmph, Seven Big Dipper Immortals, you are no longer able to obstruct me." Duke Long sneered as he gave an indifferent glance to Seven Extreme Desolation before moving his gaze to Calamity Luck Altar.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable's call of the ancient killer move was reliant on Calamity Luck Altar. As long as Calamity Luck Altar was bombarded and dealt a certain amount of damage, call of the ancient would be destroyed.

Without the interference of these past Northern Plains experts, Heavenly Court members would immediately have the advantage in numbers and Longevity Heaven would no longer have strength to retaliate.

Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan's forehead was filled with sweat.

"Damn it, fate Gu has recovered a little again, the Northern Plains experts from call of the ancient are greatly weakened."

"On the contrary, Heavenly Court members are being strengthened by the human path killer move."

"Most importantly, Duke Long cannot be stopped, his battle strength has already greatly surpassed the realm of rank eight, even the human path killer move has no amplification effect on him…"

While Bing Sai Chuan was thinking, Duke Long had once again smashed down on Seven Extreme Desolation.

After getting rid of the hindrance, Duke Long directly charged towards Calamity Luck Altar.

"Huff!" Bing Sai Chuan breathed out heavily as a resolute light shone in his eyes: "This is our final attempt!"

Boom—!

Calamity Luck Altar suddenly erupted with an extremely intense light that resembled the sun.

All the Gu Immortals had no choice but to shut their eyes. Even Duke Long had to squint his eyes.

He was puzzled: "Bing Sai Chuan is activating Calamity Luck Altar's ability so intensely, is he not afraid of affecting call of the ancient?"

Call of the ancient was only attached to Calamity Luck Altar, this time path killer move and Calamity Luck Altar conflicted with each other.

Calamity Luck Altar did not use its powerful abilities so that it could sustain call of the ancient. So it was surprising to see Bing Sai Chuan suddenly activating its ability.

The intense light of luck path temporarily obstructed everyone.

Within the light, Calamity Luck Altar was like a beast let out of its cage as it ferociously smashed towards the refinement path formation.

"Quick, stop him!" Fairy Zi Wei cried out.

"Hmm?" Duke Long discovered to his surprise that call of the ancient was still working.

The River of Time phantom image was already imprinted in the battlefield. Although it was dissipating, its speed of dissipation was extremely slow and could clearly last for a long period of time.

"Red Lotus!" Immediately, Duke Long was surprised and furious.

He realized he had fallen into Red Lotus Demon Venerable's scheme.

His understanding of call of the ancient came from the other half of its set, the killer move support of the future.

Back then, in the battle with Red Lotus Demon Venerable, he had attacked Red Lotus many times and disrupted support of the future.

"Master, you are very perceptive, you actually saw through this move's flaw." In his memories, Red Lotus Demon Venerable was bleeding but still had a smile on his face and radiance in his eyes.

"This defiant disciple, he said it intentionally! There is also this Bing Sai Chuan, he is truly crafty, he could move freely but purposely restrained himself." Duke Long was furious, this had happened too suddenly and caught him off-guard.

Calamity Luck Altar had already prepared the move for a long time so it erupted with shocking might.

The Heavenly Court members were strengthened by heroes among people and were suppressing Northern Plains' immortals, unknowingly, the tight defense line had become dispersed.

Looking at Calamity Luck Altar's charge, several Heavenly Court members activated immortal killer moves without dodging.

But under the intense light of luck path, most of their killer moves failed miserably and they suffered from powerful backlash.

Only a few killer moves activated successfully and struck Calamity Luck Altar, but were not even able to move Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar kept on charging straight, heavily injuring several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals in its path, it collided with the refinement path formation like a crashing meteor.

Boom!

The refinement path formation suffered serious damage and was mostly shattered.

Heaven Overseeing Tower's peak was finally exposed to plain sight.

Chapter 1733: Giant Sun's Greatness

Plop.

Yuan Qiong Du, who had been in charge of the restoration work, blacked out and fell to the ground.

He had already been injured before and with the backlash from the damage to the refinement path formation, he immediately fainted.

Without him, although success dao marks were still arriving in small portions, fate Gu's recovery was immediately paused.

Even Cong Yan was affected.

This rank eight Gu Immortal had collaborated with Che Wei to defend against Northern Plains' Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster.

Cong Yan had already been prepared when Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster attacked the refinement path Gu formation, he bore the damage done to the refinement path formation with his own body.

Now with Calamity Luck Altar destroying most of the refinement path formation, Cong Yan also had to endure a large portion of the damage.

Cong Yan was dizzy, his ears kept on buzzing and his seven orifices were bleeding, he had almost collapsed to the ground.

Fortunately, Che Wei provided timely assistance and protected him.

"How is your condition?" Che Wei defended against the joint attacks of Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster while asking.

"I'm still, still not dead…" Cong Yan coughed out a mouthful of blood.

"Go reinforce them quickly!"

"Who can reconstruct the refinement path formation?"

"Yuan Qiong Du had been in charge of restoring fate Gu, others won't be able to continue the work within a short period, it is better to wake him first!"

The light of luck path started dissipating, Heavenly Court's immortals charged towards it like they had gone crazy.

"We failed to destroy it completely…" Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan's gaze shined coldly.

His gaze turned and he immediately gave a firm order: "Bull Demon, Five Elements Grandmaster, return immediately."

The light of luck path could not last for long and was dissipating quickly. The Heavenly Court immortals were all charging over, it would definitely be dangerous for Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster if they were to remain outside.

Previously, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had been afraid of the refinement path Gu formation not being able to support many Gu Immortals and so had not reinforced Cong Yan and Che Wei.

Bull Demon and Five Elements Grandmaster understood the situation and quickly retreated to Calamity Luck Altar.

Che Wei was helpless and could only watch.

Bull Demon entered Calamity Luck Altar with a worried expression: "Flower Lady is still trapped in Heaven Overseeing Tower, the situation there is unknown."

Bing Sai Chuan nodded, his expression was resolute: "We shall completely destroy this refinement path formation and then rescue…"

Boom!

Bing Sai Chuan had yet to finish speaking when Calamity Luck Altar shook intensely, the three inside the altar could not stand stably and shook along with the altar.

A gigantic figure had ruthlessly stepped on Calamity Luck Altar.

Because of this action, most of Calamity Luck Altar sank and got buried in the ground.

It was Duke Long!

"With me here, this is as far as you will go." Duke Long's expression was solemn, his gaze was cold. The anger from earlier had completely turned into ruthlessness, his killing intent pervaded the air and suffocated others.

Boom boom boom!

Duke Long started punching Calamity Luck Altar.

A torrent of fists rained down on Calamity Luck Altar like a storm.

Calamity Luck Altar shook endlessly, sinking down into the ground inch by inch. Cracks quickly appeared on Calamity Luck Altar's surface and started expanding before forming holes.

Large amount of Gu worms died. Bing Sai Chuan immediately distributed the work, he started preparing a killer move to retaliate, Bull Demon was put in charge of repairing Calamity Luck Altar, and Five Elements Grandmaster, who specialized in formation path, was given the work of deducing the half-destroyed refinement path formation.

"The speed of destruction is too fast, I have no time to repair Calamity Luck Altar at all!" Several breaths later, Bull Demon shouted.

Five Elements Grandmaster's head was soaked with sweat as he tried to deduce the formation with all his strength.

Bing Sai Chuan said through clenched teeth: "Persevere!"

Duke Long was extremely powerful, the rank eight Calamity Luck Altar, an Immortal Gu House created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally, was already unable to endure Duke Long's endless punches.

"Rise—!" Bing Sai Chuan shouted, Calamity Luck Altar once again erupted with piercing light as it flew towards the sky.

Duke Long who had been punching continuously felt a powerful force coming from Calamity Luck Altar.

"Go down!!" Duke Long shouted, he raised his fists above his head and smashed down like a giant hammer.

Immortal killer move — World Shaking Dragon Hammer!

With a loud bang, Calamity Luck Altar which had just ascended was smashed down like a ball.

A huge amount of Gu worms died, their carcasses flying everywhere. A large hole was smashed open on the surface of Calamity Luck Altar from which one could see Bing Sai Chuan.

Bing Sai Chuan could not hide his shock.

Duke Long's strength had already surpassed his wildest imagination.

Even Heavenly Court's members were dumbfounded.

"Everyone, charge!" At this moment, the Northern Plains Gu Immortals who were created by call of the ancient rushed to reinforce.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals did not dodge or evade, meeting the Northern Plains' Gu Immortals head-on.

Chaotic battle erupted once again.

And in the rear of this chaotic battle, Duke Long was continuously bombarding Calamity Luck Altar.

Behind Duke Long was the refinement path formation that was being repaired hurriedly.

Seven Extreme Desolation fought and killed, finally paving a path of blood as it arrived before Duke Long.

"Calamity Luck Altar cannot defend against Duke Long on its own." Bing Sai Chuan had to acknowledge this fact.

After obtaining the reinforcement of Seven Extreme Desolation, Bing Sai Chuan finally had a chance to catch a breather, with some difficulty, he manipulated Calamity Luck Altar and fought Duke Long together with Seven Extreme Desolation.

Immortal killer move — Spiraling Dragon Fang!

Duke Long opened his mouth as his teeth flew out.

One hundred sharp teeth expanded along with the wind, becoming a group of snow-white dragon fang blades that slashed at Calamity Luck Altar.

Chink chink chink!

The dragon fang blades struck Calamity Luck Altar and produced intense sounds like the collision of hundreds of weapons.

Calamity Luck Altar was like a hut in the storm, unable to even retaliate.

Duke Long sneered. In just a short moment, teeth grew again in his mouth.

They flew out once again, turning into snow-white blades that shrouded Calamity Luck Altar and Seven Extreme Desolation.

Soon, Seven Extreme Desolation became heavily damaged while Calamity Luck Altar was filled with holes.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Claw Strike!

Immortal killer move — Chaotic Dragon Fist!

Fist shadows flew in all directions and claw marks appeared everywhere. Seven Extreme Desolation's head was destroyed again and again, while Calamity Luck Altar was in ruins and Bull Demon was simply unable to repair it.

Immortal killer move — Nine Dragons Protection!

Nine huge purple-gold dragon shadows coiled around Duke Long.

It was not that Seven Extreme Desolation and Calamity Luck Altar did not retaliate, but their attacks were all blocked by nine dragons protection.

The situation was obvious; Duke Long had an extremely huge dominance.

As time continued to pass, Longevity Heaven's side would definitely fail.

"You have the guts to invade my Heavenly Court, you are going to pay for it with your lives!" Duke Long snorted.

"What are you still resisting for? You have no hope left." Duke Long stepped and activated a killer move, pushing down the whole Calamity Luck Altar into the ground, he then punched with both hands and sent Seven Extreme Desolation flying far away.

"I already told you, this is as far as you can possibly go."

"You will all fail, Heavenly Court will remain invincible for all eternity!"

Duke Long's voice reverberated throughout the whole battlefield, stirring everyone's hearts.

"What methods do you still have? Use them all, I will personally send you into the abyss of despair." He spoke slowly and steadily, his expressionless dragon eyes and cruel voice gave chills to others.

Bing Sai Chuan was in a miserable state, Calamity Luck Altar could no longer provide comprehensive defense, he was filled with injuries.

This was the result of spiraling dragon fangs.

The situation was getting increasingly dangerous, but the light in his eyes had never been extinguished.

He still held hope.

In the depths of his mind, there was a memory which he would never forget.

"This is Eighty-Eight True Yang Building? So amazing! It is truly worthy of being lord's creation." Bing Sai Chuan stood beside Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and said with reverence.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled, he had a satisfied expression: "With this Immortal Gu House, all my children will become strong."

"Lord, you are truly considerate." Bing Sai Chuan praised.

"However." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable changed his tone: "I feel more anticipation towards the time it collapses."

"Wha… what?"

"I created this building so that it would collapse one day. Bing Sai Chuan, you are a time path Gu Immortal, go hibernate. When Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapses in the future, it will be a sign that the opportunity to attack Heavenly Court has arrived."

…

Inside Calamity Luck Altar.

"Even if my injuries are fatal, even if the situation is desperate, even if we have used all our trump cards, I won't give up. Because this plan is Ancestor Giant Sun's arrangement!"

"Oh Heavenly Court, the victor will be us!"

Bing Sai Chuan shouted.

"Blind confidence." Duke Long gave a disdainful scoff: "You will only extend your suffering if you continue persevering."

Bing Sai Chuan snorted: "You will never understand that man's greatness!"

Not far away.

Whoosh!

Dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu suddenly turned into smoke and disappeared from the scene.

"We finally got rid of the killer move perfect pair!"

"It is indeed worthy of being Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's creation."

"Fortunately, this is Heavenly Court. With four rule path Gu Immortals and with detailed information on perfect pair in our records, we could decipher it. If this were a normal situation, it would have been troublesome."

The dog tail life extending ferret had been engaging in a fierce battle against two legendary immemorial desolate beasts of Heavenly Court, Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five.

With perfect pair, the dog tail life extending ferret and its clone were able to suppress them.

But with Heavenly Court's members waking up, many people began to target perfect pair and were finally able to break it.

"Try to act wild again!"

"Little dog, you pounced on me so many times that my feathers are all plucked out."

Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five surrounded Mao Li Qiu, along with several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Mao Li Qiu might have outstanding strength, but falling into this situation, it was not able to fight against many and was soon filled with injuries with blood gushing out rapidly.

But Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five were also not in a good state.

Mao Li Qiu's counterattack was specially targeted at these two.

Although Mao Li Qiu's injuries kept on increasing and was becoming increasingly weak while Heavenly Court's dominance was increasing, Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five were still shaken and bewildered.

"This lunatic is not afraid of death!"

"Even if it dies, it will probably bite a piece of my flesh off during its last attack."

Heavenly Court's two legendary immemorial beasts could not help but feel apprehensive, one of them shouted: "Mao Li Qiu, why are you wasting your life for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable? He raised you because of your innate ability and wanted to kill you to prolong his life."

Mao Li Qiu was standing in a pool of blood, its injuries were horrifying and many were so deep that its bones could be seen. Its glossy fur was now stuck together because of the blood.

Its eyes had blacked out, its body was shaking as if it would collapse at the next moment.

It knew about its body condition, it would probably die here.

"And so what?!" Mao Li Qiu gave a soundless laughter as it opened its mouth.

A memory surfaced in its mind.

Under the setting sun, on a mountain, Mao Li Qiu curled up like a puppy beside Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's feet.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stroked its head, but it was shivering.

It had already heard of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's plan, now that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was near the end of his lifespan and had summoned him, he probably wanted to kill it to extend his life.

But Mao Li Qiu did not dare to resist, it was extremely clear: Even if it possessed peak rank eight battle strength, it was not Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's match. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not even need to attack for it to die.

"Don't be afraid, Mao Li Qiu. I won't kill you to prolong my life." Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chuckled.

Mao Li Qiu's body stiffened.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gazed at the evening sky that was dazzling like fire: "I still remember the first day I took you in, hehehe, how time flies, you have already grown to this extent."

"Speaking from the bottom of my heart, you are my child too, how different are you from my sons and daughters?"

"As a parent, how can I harm my own children?"

Mao Li Qiu knew Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's temperament, he would not lie because there was no need to do so.

Mao Li Qiu asked in a daze: "But master, you can extend your lifespan by killing me."

"Extend my lifespan?" Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed: "I will only be dragging on the inevitable. People die in the end, isn't that so?"

He shook his head: "What meaning is there to continue living under fate? Death is not that hard to accept, furthermore, children are destined to leave their parents and only then can they truly grow up."

"Master…"

"Promise me, you must continue to live well. Do what you like, I won't give you any orders, be yourself and live happily."

"Master…"

The memory faded away as Mao Li Qiu looked at the surrounding enemies.

It raised its head and laughed wildly, its aura suddenly surging: "Master, even if I die, I will repay the gratitude of raising me!"

"It is already dying!"

"Right, it is only overexerting itself."

"But be careful of its final counterattack."

The Heavenly Court immortals had cold expressions as they encircled it.

Black heaven.

Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

Giant Sun immortal zombie was sitting cross-legged without moving like a statue.

He looked towards the south, the scenes of the battle in Heavenly Court were reflected in his eyes.

His face showed no sadness or joy as he slowly raised his palm.

Chapter 1734: Chen Yi Removes Formation

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

Nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

"Their formation…"

"Our side is suffering from a strong backlash!"

"First group, come back and recuperate; second group, take over the first group, third group, be on standby!"

Chen Yi and Bai Cang Shui controlled the formation while orderly commanding the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

"Who could have thought they would have such a strange move." Feng Jiu Ge frowned slightly as he gazed at the five regional formation within the formation: "This is troublesome, if we don't handle it well, the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation might…"

Feng Jiu Ge had a bad feeling.

The five regional formation constantly spread five colored smoke to the surroundings under Chi Qu You's control.

The smoke constantly spread out while becoming increasingly transparent as it invaded the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

"Good, this is the way!"

"The others shall target the formation, make the Central Continent Gu Immortals use it frequently, the more they use it, the stronger the backlash they will suffer."

"Hahaha, the stronger this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation is, the greater the injury these Gu Immortals will have to suffer! This is truly wonderful."

The morale of the Southern Alliance and Northern Plains immortals soared.

They changed their battle tactic.

They had already seen through this formation and could clearly target the flaw to destroy the formation, but now, they were not in a hurry to do so.

The five regional smoke constantly spread and they used this to deal with the Central Continent Gu Immortals who were inside the formation.

In a way, nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation had instead become the strong weapon for Fang Yuan's group to attack Central Continent and Heavenly Court's experts.

"How should we deal with this? Do we send people to destroy their formation?" Bai Cang Shui looked at Chen Yi.

The leader of this group was Chen Yi.

Chen Yi looked unsightly as he said: "This formation should have originated from the five regional true inheritance, it is the method of Southern Border's Tao Zhu."

Heavenly Court had interfered in the five regional mountain range battle, Jun Shen Guang was captured alive by Fang Yuan in this battle. Thus, Heavenly Court knew detailed information about Tao Zhu's true inheritance and the five regional mountain range battle.

"Tao Zhu could create the five regional mountain range, so this five colored smoke that is pervading the formation is clearly imitating the five regional walls and is making our side suffer from backlash."

Chen Yi's tone was quite bitter: "The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation is a multi-layered formation, we can easily get rid of or add a sub-formation and hence sustain it indefinitely. Back then, Limitless Demon Venerable had to break a hundred formations to get out of this formation."

"But Tao Zhu's method gets around the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation and targets our Gu Immortals instead!"

"Not only are they avoiding the formation but the stronger our formation is, the stronger the backlash to the Gu Immortals in charge of the formation."

"If we activate the formation to deal with the enemy's formation, we will fall into the enemy's trap, we cannot do that."

"But if we temporarily stop the formation and send our people out of the formation, we will be giving up our advantage and fighting with our weakness. Moreover, the enemies include ruthless people like Wu Yong and Fang Yuan, the Gu Immortals we send out will be in huge danger."

Chen Yi had been struck by Wu Yong's farewell friend wind and was saved by Feng Jiu Ge, he still felt lingering fear.

More importantly, they only had three rank eights: Chen Yi, Bai Cang Shui, and Feng Jiu Ge. Moreover, they all had some level of injuries and were not suited to be sent out.

Chen Yi sighed deeply as he analyzed until here: "Who could have thought the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation would be countered by the enemy!"

Tao Zhu was only an ordinary rank eight Gu Immortal who could not even be mentioned alongside Wu Yong and Fang Yuan, while the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was created by the famous and mighty Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

The five regional true inheritance was able to counter nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, this was Tao Zhu's glory!

While alive, Tao Zhu was not prominent among rank eight Gu Immortals or even remotely famous, he only created the five regional mountain range.

No one had expected his research to truly succeed.

After this battle, Tao Zhu's name would spread throughout the world despite him having been dead for a long time already.

Each generation brings forth new geniuses and each will rule their domain for years to come.

Like how Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's perfect pair killer move was countered in the battle in Heavenly Court, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was also countered by geniuses of the future generations.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had died too long ago while the eras continued to progress. Their methods were powerful, but they could not escape from the trials of time as it flows continuously.

"Remove that sub-formation." Chen Yi ordered resolutely.

The Gu Immortals beside him were shocked.

Chen Yi actually sent the command to remove the formation, did he get muddle-headed?

But soon after, Feng Jiu Ge was the first to react, his eyes shining brightly as he praised: "Great idea."

"They actually removed the formation, hahaha." Inside five regional formation, some Northern Plains Gu Immortals started laughing heartily at this sight.

Wu Yong and Fang Yuan, however, had slightly sunken expressions.

"This is not good, Chen Yi is truly crafty."

"If we are inside their formation, the five colored smoke can invade faster and deeper. Now that they have removed the sub-formation, its efficiency will decrease greatly."

"Indeed. Over at Heavenly Court's battlefield, Longevity Heaven is already unable to hold on and Heavenly Court is firmly occupying the upper hand. Chen Yi probably considered this so he adopted the delaying tactic."

Fang Yuan's group would have been happy to see Chen Yi's side activating the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation or sending people to attack their formation.

But now, Chen Yi took the initiative to remove the sub-formation, choosing to defend passively.

The five colored smoke's invasion slowed down greatly, Central Continent immortals only maintained the formation and did not activate it so they suffered from weaker backlash.

On the contrary, Chen Yi was still behind the formation, continuing to arrange immortal formations!

Fang Yuan's group needed even more time to destroy this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation as a result.

The most crucial thing was that Fang Yuan's group had to fight for every second, they could not delay for even one moment. Once Heavenly Court eliminates Longevity Heaven's forces, they would rush here to deal with Fang Yuan's group.

Chen Yi was very calm with his deep experience.

He purposely backed down, it was only a small step back in the overall picture, but it instead became an even more terrifying offensive move.

He directly forced Fang Yuan's group towards the edge of the cliff.

"Sigh, if I had known this, I would have made Formation Spirit and formation flag Immortal Gu take part in the five regional formation. With that, five regional formation could be mobile and would not have to be fixed in one place."

Fang Yuan mentally sighed.

This was not his mistake, and it was not that he was unwilling to contribute.

If Formation Spirit and formation flag Immortal Gu were to be joined with the five regional formation, the amount of things to deduce would increase sharply and it would consume a lot of Fang Yuan's time.

In fact, even if the five regional formation could be moved, Fang Yuan's group would not be able to resolve the current crisis.

Chen Yi took the initiative to dispel the sub-formation and retreated to a defensive position. The five regional formation inside the sub-formation was now exposed.

There was already a chaotic battle going on outside the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Four rank eight Gu Immortals, Qing Ye, Li Huang, Prince Feng Xian, and Ba Shi Ba, were engaged in a ferocious fight. Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, Frost Dragon Manor, Wind Sweeping Building, and other Immortal Gu Houses were rampaging in the battlefield, occasionally colliding against each other or erupting with immortal killer moves, dazzling lights and explosions resounded everywhere.

"Not good, unlimited wind is getting out of my control." Wu Yong's expression changed.

Previously, he had been inside the formation and had not clearly sensed it. Now that Chen Yi had removed the formation, Wu Yong clearly felt something wrong.

Without any delay, Wu Yong flew out of the five regional formation and charged at Wind Sweeping Building.

Yao Huang, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and others also made their moves.

With their support, Li Huang, Qing Ye and others felt huge pressure. They had to retreat again and again, and soon, they along with Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses were getting suppressed.

Fang Yuan quietly moved out before suddenly using great thief ghost hand.

Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses immediately met with disaster as Fang Yuan stole a large amount of Gu worms.

Fang Yuan grabbed repeatedly and soon obtained three Immortal Gu. Adding on his gains from the battle in Emperor City, he had already stolen over ten Immortal Gu from Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses.

As for these Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan recognized some of them while there were some which he did not recognize.

His time path clone was staying inside the light of wisdom, continuously deducing the ways in which these Gu worms could be used.

Seeing that the situation was going awry, Li Huang got away from Prince Feng Xian and hurried to fight Fang Yuan.

The previous scene in Emperor City played out once again.

Fang Yuan was entangled by Li Huang and was unable to easily target Immortal Gu Houses.

"Hmph, this Prince Feng Xian is acting so well, intentionally letting go of Li Huang without commotion." Fang Yuan mentally snorted.

Prince Feng Xian was a problem.

What made Fang Yuan feel even more problematic was Heavenly Court's rank nine human path killer move — Heroes Among People.

With the amplification from heroes among people, Li Huang, Qing Ye, as well as Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses had their strength increased by several times. Thus they were able to block the joint offense of Southern Border and Northern Plains.

"We don't have time to continue such a chaotic battle! Let's retreat to the formation." Fang Yuan called out.

Wu Yong and the rest slowly moved back and collected their Immortal Gu Houses before retreating to the five regional formation.

The five regional formation was activated completely, large amounts of five colored smoke quickly spread and shrouded the whole battlefield.

Inside the five colored smoke, Central Continent's Gu Immortals felt a powerful suppression.

Like the awkward state of Chen Yi before, these people who had been strengthened by heroes among people had their killer moves amplified as well which caused the backlash to increase steeply.

"I did not expect Tao Zhu's method to be so profound!" Inside the formation, Ba Shi Ba was moved and sighed.

Wu Yong was silent.

This situation was within his expectations.

Because he had already discovered this, he did not stint on exposing the contents of the true inheritance and seeking to collaborate with Chi Qu You.

Chi Qu You also knew this was a good thing but did not have a method to use it before. Now that the formation was modified and successfully arranged, it immediately showed its effects.

"It is a pity this five colored smoke does not distinguish between enemies and allies, Central Continent is suppressed but we can also suffer from backlash."

"Only Fang Yuan can move freely." Yao Huang said encouragingly.

Many people looked at Fang Yuan, revealing envious expressions.

"Such a pity." Fang Yuan inwardly sighed, if he could obtain Tao Zhu's true inheritance, relying on the light of wisdom as well as his powerful formation path and wisdom path attainment levels, his battle strength would rise sharply.

For example, he had no way to deal with heroes among people, but if he had the five colored smoke, Li Huang's group would suffer from an even greater suppression. Who was to say if Fang Yuan might be able to suppress the battle in Emperor City singlehandedly?

Back then, when he had escaped from the five regional mountain range and could not take five regional true inheritance, he had felt it was a huge loss.

Looking at it now, his premonition back then was not wrong.

Chapter 1735: Giant Sun Versus Star Constellation

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

"The enemies entered their formation, looks like they want to make full use of the five colored smoke. Li Huang and the others are in trouble." Chen Yi had been paying close attention to the battle situation.

"Should we go reinforce them? We can work together with them, maybe we can destroy the enemy's formation. As long as their formation is destroyed and one or two of the core Immortal Gu are dead, they might have no way left to make a comeback." Bai Cang Shui suggested.

Chen Yi considered before shaking his head: "No need to take a risk, the current situation is very favorable to us. Bring them into the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation."

Chen Yi was not willing to attack and even wanted to pull back Li Huang and others.

He was determined to continue his plan of stalling for time.

Fang Yuan flew out of the formation and began to fight Li Huang's group.

Inside five colored smoke, Li Huang's group was greatly restricted when fighting with Fang Yuan.

After suffering many losses, Li Huang gave the order to retreat and entered the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

In an instant, both sides had entered their respective formations, the noisy battlefield was only left with the sounds of unlimited wind.

Wu Yong and Fang Yuan remained outside the formation.

The former carefully controlled unlimited wind to evade five colored smoke and target Heavenly Court's formation.

The latter was hiding in the five colored smoke, slowly approaching Heavenly Court's formation as the five colored smoke spread out further.

"Let's continue to hold on, as long as the battle in Heavenly Court ends, we will win." Inside nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, Chen Yi roused the morale of everyone.

But he had just finished speaking when they heard a loud explosion.

The immortals quickly looked and saw surging five colored smoke, the five regional formation on Fang Yuan's side suddenly exploded. A figure flew out like an arrow from within the dense five colored smoke.

"Prince Feng Xian, what did you do?!"

"Kill him, he is definitely Heavenly Court's spy!"

"Lord Chi Qu You, are you okay? Quick, someone save Lord Chi!"

A change happened suddenly, Southern Border and Northern Plains' Gu Immortals were in chaos.

"Prince Feng Xian, don't even dream about escaping!" Fang Yuan and Wu Yong who were outside turned around and stopped Prince Feng Xian.

Bai Cang Shui was exulted: "So it was Prince Feng Xian who destroyed the enemy formation from inside! Great job!"

Some Gu Immortals who were unaware of the inside information were dumbstruck at this sight.

"Quick, Prince Feng Xian is our Spirit Affinity House's member! Go save him!" A Spirit Affinity House's supreme elder urged.

Even without his words, Chen Yi had already sent the command.

Li Huang, Qing Ye, and Bai Cang Shui flew out of the formation to bring back Prince Feng Xian.

Fang Yuan and Wu Yong were obstructed by these three.

Prince Feng Xian was not weak and with help from the reinforcements, he entered the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation successfully.

Heavenly Court's immortals, however, did not know: this Prince Feng Xian who was brought into their formation was a fake!

"I finally got in." Fang Yuan sneered inwardly with surging killing intent.

Immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

This killer move was given a major modification by Fang Yuan, and adding on the transformation path dao marks he obtained from annexing Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, its might had increased by several times.

Even if Heavenly Court had made preparations, they could not discover Fang Yuan's true identity!

At this moment, the true Prince Feng Xian was actually still inside the five regional formation.

The five regional formation had been modified by Fang Yuan and he had naturally put in another formation inside. This inner formation was a cage to trap Prince Feng Xian and its formation core was being guarded by several rank eight Gu Immortals.

As for the 'Fang Yuan' inside the five colored smoke, it was Yi Hao Fang's disguise.

Southern Border's rank eight Gu Immortal Yi Hao Fang was a transformation path Gu Immortal.

Although he did not have a method like familiar face, he was inside the five colored smoke which protected him from the investigative killer moves of other rank eight Gu Immortals.

As for the five regional formation, it had truly been detonated. Countless mortal Gu died and the Immortal Gu used in the formation also suffered varying severity of damage.

Only by doing this could they deceive Chen Yi's side.

Chen Yi was still in the dark because of another reason as well, Fairy Zi Wei had sent a notification to them.

Chen Yi's group knew Prince Feng Xian's true identity which made them place attention on him constantly during the battle.

Once there was any movement over on Prince Feng Xian's end and he backstabs the enemy, they were to actively cooperate and achieve greater success in the battle.

Right now, Prince Feng Xian had directly destroyed the enemy's formation, this was a huge battle merit!

Chen Yi's group had already been mentally prepared so they immediately accepted Fang Yuan.

"Since the secret that I was reborn has been exposed, Heavenly Court is definitely wary of Prince Feng Xian's identity being exposed as well. Currently, this war pertains to fate Gu, at the crucial moment, Heavenly Court will definitely use Prince Feng Xian to maintain the situation! This is something I can exploit."

Fang Yuan sneered inwardly. He was disguised as Prince Feng Xian with a heavily injured look. Under the expectant gazes of Heavenly Court immortals, he entered the core of nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation confidently.

A Spirit Affinity House supreme elder welcomed him first, she smiled: "Welcome home."

Fang Yuan was ready and prepared to make a move.

"I am not the real Prince Feng Xian, I will be exposed when I converse with them."

"And I don't have Wu Yong's concealing methods, my killer move's aura will definitely leak when I prepare it."

"So the perfect time to make a move is at this moment when I have just entered the formation! Because I was chased, the killer move aura on my body has yet to dissipate."

Fang Yuan was about to make a fatal move when a change occurred!

Everyone in the whole battlefield had a change in their expression.

"What… what is that?"

"Rank nine killer move! It seems to have come from Northern Plains!"

Luck path's aura."

"Its direction… seems like Heavenly Court!"

Both enemies and allies forgot about fighting as they all looked up at the sky.

An enormous beam of light flew through the sky and shot towards Heavenly Court's direction at an extreme speed.

This beam of light was so gigantic, like a large river that spanned across heaven and earth.

Wherever it went, it pushed aside all the air, the light pillar's movement was accompanied by a deafening and majestic sound.

Such a grand and powerful killer move shocked everyone and sent them into a daze.

Chen Yi, Wu Yong, and even Fang Yuan felt how small and insignificant they were at this moment!

Unstoppable! Invincible!

The light pillar started from black heaven above Northern Plains, piercing through the regional wall and directly bombarding Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court shook intensely, the world seemed to tremble as countless Immortal Gu Houses cracked and broke.

"This is?!" Duke Long looked up fiercely. The previous moment, he had been in high spirits and with his awe-inspiring might, he had beaten Seven Extreme Desolation and Calamity Luck Altar to the point where they did not even know their bearings.

But when the light pillar charged towards him, he paled in horror; in an instant, he had become fish on the chopping board.

He could not move, he was locked firmly by the beam like an insect trapped in amber, he could only watch quietly as the pillar of light crashed, even though his current strength could make all other rank eight Gu Immortals feel helpless and lament.

"Rank nine killer move! This is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's method!"

"Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind a backup method after all! No, he is not targeting me, he is going after fate Gu."

Duke Long suddenly realized as his face turned malevolent, he struggled with all his strength, trying to activate his immortal killer moves desperately.

But what he feared still happened, his killer moves did not even activate once. The continuous failure in activating killer moves inflicted heavy backlash on him, his mouth and eyes were both bleeding.

The Heavenly Court immortals were confused and shocked, some who overestimated their own strength tried to obstruct the beam but were all incinerated into ashes!

No rank eight Gu Immortal could block the advancement of the light pillar.

"Lord Ancestor Giant Sun!"

"Master…"

At this moment, Bing Sai Chuan and Mao Li Qiu's eyes shined brightly.

But right as the beam of light was about to strike the refinement path formation, suddenly, everyone heard a deep sigh.

Following that, the image of two venerables playing chess appeared once again in Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, who was playing chess with Limitless Demon Venerable, grabbed a chess piece and tossed it out.

Instantly, countless starlight specks flickered and gathered, they were so dazzling that they did not lose to the huge yellow beam!

Starlight specks formed a giant web that obstructed the beam's advancement.

The beam of light became slower and thinner, the starlight specks that were surrounding it were absorbing and transferring the strength away.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!"

"This is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were exulted, they looked at Imperfection Regret Pavilion with reverence and excited emotions.

Duke Long gasped for breath, the beam of light had approached him closely, almost touching his face. But in the end, the beam was completely stopped and trapped by the starlight web.

"Damn it, we were so close." Bing Sai Chuan was very upset.

Duke Long was Heavenly Court's strongest battle strength, he was also their leader and banner. If he died, Heavenly Court's morale would definitely fall greatly while Longevity Heaven, which still had Calamity Luck Altar and Seven Extreme Desolation, would have hope left!

"Star Constellation, this bitch…" Mao Li Qiu clenched its teeth fiercely.

The beam of light suddenly changed abruptly, it started to rotate and got faster and faster, forming circles of whirling currents on its surface.

Inside Imperfection Regret Pavilion, a surprised look appeared on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's face.

With a loud sound, the beam exploded, splitting into hundreds of enormous yellow qi currents that plunged into Bing Sai Chuan, Mao Li Qiu, and the other Northern Plains' experts.

Mao Li Qiu was dumbfounded.

It had already been prepared for death but after this yellow qi current moved through its limbs and bones, all its injuries were healed and immortal essence was condensing within its immortal aperture out of nowhere.

A golden-white halo appeared on Longevity Heaven's members, giving them a huge amplification.

This amplification was several times stronger than heroes among people!

After the light pillar got obstructed by the starlight web, it transformed into another effect and helped Longevity Heaven's members instead.

"Duke Long, let's fight again!" Bing Sai Chuan shouted, having recovered to his peak condition.

Calamity Luck Altar was also shrouded in a layer of radiance, and under Bing Sai Chuan's control, it flew out.

Duke Long did not dodge but faced Calamity Luck Altar head-on.

Calamity Luck Altar's momentum was blocked but Duke Long was sent flying like a cannonball. He smashed through five to six thick walls before being stopped by the qi wall.

Guh.

Duke Long's face turned pale as he spat out large mouthfuls of blood.

His chest had caved in and almost all his ribs were broken!

Chapter 1736: Northern Plains' Upper Hand

Heavenly Court battlefield.

"Kill!"

Deafening battle roars resounded, the morale of the Northern Plains immortals soared to an unprecedented height!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had made his move, it had extraordinary meaning, his descendants all felt a huge rise in their morale along with great increase in their strength.

"How can this be?" A Heavenly Court immortal suddenly stiffened in the air, unable to move.

Before him, a famous expert of Northern Plains, wisdom path Gu Immortal Liu Hui, let out a breath of air: "I was almost killed by you, you were really so close, it is such a pity."

Cold sweat dripped down the Heavenly Court Gu Immortal's forehead: "Your killer move was clearly unable to bind me. Hmph, the amazing one is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, you take no credit in this!"

Liu Hui sneered: "Then what about earlier when our side was suppressed by fate? Moreover, who cares about who the credit belongs to? Life or death, victory or defeat, these are the only important things, go die."

He waved his hand lightly, taking the enemy's life.

His eyes were narrow and his gaze was chilling as he sized up his surroundings with ill intentions: "Who should be next?"

…

"You cannot break my defense, don't waste your effort." A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal stood steadfast and unmoved, his whole body covered in an extremely tough barrier.

Northern Plains Gu Immortal Yu Yang Zi took in a deep breath, he felt the vast new strength in his body, his dejectedness from earlier vanished as his confidence soared: "The current me is not the same as before. Immortal killer move — Decomposition!"

Yu Yang Zi's original name was Ye Lui Wa and he cultivated rule path. After becoming a Gu Immortal, he achieved remarkable feats repeatedly, but Ye Lui tribe did not give him the treatment he deserved. In a fit of anger, he defected from the tribe and became a demonic path Gu Immortal.

In his later years, Ye Lui tribe was jointly pushed aside and suppressed by many Huang Jin tribes, Ye Lui Wa who had become rank eight was welcomed back to become Ye Lui tribe's first supreme elder in a grand manner and returned to the righteous path.

He relied on his own strength to achieve feats that was unattainable for ordinary Gu Immortals, making the entire tribe lower its head and admit its past mistake.

Ye Lui Wa's life history was painted with legendary tales that stimulated countless future generations. But even after returning to Ye Lui tribe and taking the position of first supreme elder, he did not use his original name and still went by Yu Yang Zi.

"How can this be?!" The Heavenly Court Gu Immortal was pale from shock, the defense that he prided himself on continued to break apart before disintegrating completely.

With the help of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Yu Yang Zi directly reversed the position of the strong and weak.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortal fighting against him soon died a miserable death.

…

Chink chink chink!

Three Heavenly Court immortals were fighting Yuan Ben.

Yuan Ben was a rank eight Gu Immortal who primarily cultivated bone path and had shocking battle strength. While he was alive, he was considered the number one battle strength in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, even the other four regions often heard of his famous name.

His physique was not strong-built, instead he was slightly on the bony side. But his whole body was covered in extremely tough white bone armor. He held a white bone spear in his right hand which created a storm when he waved it, in his left hand, he held a bone sword, the sword light it gave off was cold and dark.

Yuan Ben roared loudly when he received a portion of the yellow light, his armor suddenly shot out countless bone spikes.

One Heavenly Court Gu Immortal who was surrounding him could not dodge in time and died miserably after being pierced by hundreds of spikes.

Yuan Ben took the chance to rush forward and pierced the second Gu Immortal's heart with his spear while slicing off the third Gu Immortal's head with his sword.

But he did not feel any excitement or joy, instead he looked slightly sad: "It is unfortunate you did not have all your Gu worms and could not display your full strength. Furthermore, I obtained ancestor's help, this battle… there is no honor in winning!"

…

Boom!

With a loud bang, Duke Long was sent flying like a cannonball.

Dragon roars resounded as Duke Long quickly stabilized himself.

Suddenly, an enormous shadow shrouded over him.

Duke Long quickly raised his head and saw Calamity Luck Altar pressing down like a mountain.

Duke Long gave a cold grunt and clenched his fists with no intention to dodge.

"Lord Duke Long, let me lend you a hand!" Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Wu Shuang activated a killer move against Duke Long.

Immortal killer move — Peerless!

Duke Long took a deep breath and punched at Calamity Luck Altar.

Immortal killer move — Chaotic Dragon Fist!

Peerless — Chaotic Dragon Fist!!

Fist shadows flew and set off a violent gale. Calamity Luck Altar swayed unsteadily as it was struck by tens of millions of fist shadows.

"This Duke Long is still so absurdly strong!" Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth.

Calamity Luck Altar had also received Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's amplification, its strength had risen by several times but was still unable to suppress Duke Long.

But right at this time, a giant flew over and joined the battlefield.

It was Seven Extreme Desolation!

"Die, Duke Long!" The Seven Extreme Desolation giant roared as it spat out countless pitch-black needles that shot towards Duke Long.

"Damn it!" Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Wu Shuang stared with a furious expression, he wanted to help but was blocked by other Northern Plains Gu Immortals.

Northern Plains Gu Immortals had rich battle experiences, and these Gu Immortals summoned by call of the ancient were experts of their eras. After fighting for so long, they were already able to tacitly coordinate.

Duke Long was using chaotic dragon fist to block Calamity Luck Altar but suffered from Seven Extreme Desolation's attack at the same time.

These pitch-black needles were extremely powerful and had explosive momentum, Duke Long felt a chilling sensation of pain before they even touched him.

A sharp light flashed past Duke Long's eyes.

Immortal killer move — Clear Dragon Vision.

With the activation of the investigative killer move, he immediately saw through many details of the pitch-black needles and knew this move contained the essence of dark path and was used to counter defensive methods. If he only used his dragon scales or nine dragons protection, he would probably have countless holes in his body and be heavily injured!

"Then let's use offense against offense!" Duke Long opened his mouth and breathed out heavily.

Qi currents surged as they instantly formed an immortal killer move!

Immortal killer move — Qi Current Scissors!

Countless white qi currents charged towards the pitch-black needles.

Qi currents cut through the air like sharp blades, cutting apart all the black needles in their path.

Qi current scissors collided with pitch-black needles, each side dissipated by more than half of their original quantity.

But there were some that escaped the collision and flew towards Duke Long and Seven Extreme Desolation.

Almost at the same time, Duke Long gave a muffled grunt after being pierced by over ten pitch-black needles, while several bones and muscles of Seven Extreme Desolation's body were cut by qi current scissors.

These injuries were shared by the Seven Big Dipper Immortals inside Seven Extreme Desolation.

They endured the pain as they coordinated their efforts in activating Seven Extreme Desolation to directly go after Duke Long.

Duke Long sighed, he could only retreat!

Since the battle started, this was the first time he had retreated on his own initiative.

The enemy's momentum was so strong that Duke Long had no choice but to retreat.

His killer move heavenly dragon's last stand could indeed let him be tyrannical among rank eights, especially during the last moments of his life, he would have complete dominance over rank eight Gu Immortals.

But, in front of a rank nine killer move, heavenly dragon's last stand paled greatly, losing much significance.

Besides the might of the killer move itself, there was also a mysterious and profound change that was occurring.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attack had been an offensive killer move which originated from Northern Plains and struck Central Continent's Heavenly Court, it crossed two regions without any decrease in its power.

Heavenly Court's own defense was extremely strong but it was not a match against Giant Sun's attack.

Fortunately, during the critical moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a move and blocked Giant Sun's attack.

But after being blocked, Giant Sun's attack changed its nature and transformed into an amplification method which overturned the whole battle situation.

There were four main kinds of special techniques regarding the usage of killer moves: consecutive moves, variation moves, attached moves, and split moves.

The so-called variation move used a certain killer move as the base and added in new attributes to achieve a different effect. For instance, Fang Yuan's myriad self killer move was the base for strength path giant hand.

But if Fang Yuan activated the killer move, myriad self absolutely would not transform into strength path giant hand, these two had their own differences.

In contrast, Giant Sun's attack seemed to be able to transform at will, one moment, it was an offensive killer move, while immediately after, it became an amplification method.

The attainment that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable possessed in using the variation move technique had already surpassed Duke Long's level of understanding!

"My strength seems to be dissipating."

"Looks like Ancestor Giant Sun's amplification cannot be maintained for long!"

"We need to stop focusing on fighting, and while the amplification still exists, we need to break through the enemy's defense line and seize fate Gu!"

As time passed, the Northern Plains Gu Immortals gradually realized something.

Giant Sun's attack transformed and became a powerful amplification method, but this strength was quickly dissipating.

Giant Sun's attack was much more explosive than heroes among people. But looking at the duration and area of coverage, heroes among people undoubtedly covered a larger area and could last for a longer time.

Duke Long's expression changed.

He was barely able to match both Calamity Luck Altar and Seven Extreme Desolation, now that Northern Plains immortals were all attacking the refinement path formation, he was simply unable to defend it.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals gathered and formed a defensive line in front of the damaged refinement formation.

But under the berserk rush of the Northern Plains Gu Immortals, the defensive line was on the verge of breaking.

All kinds of immortal killer moves collided, Gu Immortal corpses fell from the sky from time to time.

Both sides staked their lives against each other, Gu Immortal deaths rose steeply around the thin defensive line.

Northern Plains' side was betting it all in this one fight while Heavenly Court members were defending with all their strength.

Both sides gained constant reinforcements.

Gu Immortals awakened from Heavenly Court immortal graveyard and rushed to the battlefield to reinforce the defensive line.

While from the phantom image of the River of Time, Northern Plains experts stepped out and went to fight without saying a word.

The defensive line was teetering on the edge of collapsing, Fairy Zi Wei had already joined the battlefield and was using all her might to resist the Northern Plains immortals' offense.

Suddenly, a faint shadow appeared beside Fairy Zi Wei.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortal expert Liu Liu Liu!

This person was a rank eight expert but did not have a good reputation. When he was alive, he was the only rank eight Gu Immortal in Liu tribe, and according to the customs, he should have inherited the first supreme elder's position.

But from a young age, Liu Liu Liu had never fought openly and only bullied the weak while fearing the strong. All his attacks were usually sneak attacks.

His reputation was so bad that others could not bring themselves to respect or trust him.

If he took the position and became Liu tribe's first supreme elder, it would instead burden the whole of Liu tribe and affect Liu tribe's image and reputation instead.

Liu Liu Liu was an anomaly and a unique existence in the history of Northern Plains. But because of this nature, he was still alive in this battlefield now.

Chapter 1737: Heavenly Court's Foundation

Liu Liu Liu had set foot in the battlefield very early, but within his batch of Northern Plains experts, the others were already killed and only he remained.

This battle was too dangerous and fierce, it was very common to see the sacrifice of rank eight Gu Immortals.

Liu Liu Liu's achievements in this battle were brilliant, having killed at least eight Heavenly Court members. With his plentiful battle experiences, he had long been paying attention to Fairy Zi Wei and had already deduced that she was a crucial key in this battle!

Now he suddenly sneak attacked, but this attack had been prepared for a long time.

At that very instance, Fairy Zi Wei's hair stood on end, she was suffocated with a feeling of fatal danger that filled her mind!

Fairy Zi Wei was well-aware that she was simply unable to block the enemy with just her defensive methods. But she did not have the time to activate other defensive measures at this point!

Right as Fairy Zi Wei was about to die, at the crucial moment, a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal rushed out from the side.

It was Wu Shuang, who had reinforced Duke Long earlier!

Swish!

With a muffled noise, Liu Liu Liu's killer move that was like a grey knife pierced through Wu Shuang and even stabbed into Fairy Zi Wei's shoulder.

"Damn it, this guy blocked most of the attack…" Liu Liu Liu's expression rapidly changed as he quickly disappeared on the spot.

Fairy Zi Wei was heavily injured but Wu Shuang was dead.

Liu Liu Liu disappeared without a trace, who knew whose life would be gone the next time he appeared.

Boom!

Air waves surged.

Duke Long was sent flying hundreds of steps before he barely stabilized himself.

He finally blocked Seven Extreme Desolation's killer move but the price he paid were his two hands and the dragon scales in front of his chest.

His hands drooped down powerlessly, his dragon scales were completely destroyed and blood had already dyed his chest.

Duke Long immediately activated healing methods but the dark path dao marks in his hands were extremely dense, moreover they were arranged in a mystical way which greatly hindered the healing effect.

"Hahaha, Duke Long, you have been struck by our snake lure and dark life entanglement, you still want to recover your injuries in such a short period? Keep dreaming!" A voice from within Seven Extreme Desolation sneered.

Next, Calamity Luck Altar changed its battle style as it suddenly drilled down into the ground and sneak attacked Duke Long from below.

An immortal killer move was activated and struck Duke Long.

A giant golden light sphere appeared and trapped Duke Long within it.

The light sphere was constantly shrinking, diminishing the space that Duke Long had, his bones were making creaking noises, his dragon scales were falling off continuously and his dragon horns showed evident cracks.

Bing Sai Chuan let out a huge breath of relief after seeing Duke Long trapped.

Duke Long's speed was too shocking while this killer move Calamity Luck Altar used was rather slow and would have been difficult for it to land on him.

Fortunately, Northern Plains Gu Immortals were highly adept in fighting, because they focused on his weaknesses, Duke Long's attention was drawn to them and he could only defend passively. The coordination with Seven Extreme Desolation was also growing increasingly, thus it created an opportunity for the killer move to strike Duke Long!

Crack.

A large part of Duke Long's dragon horns fell off.

A huge amount of purple hair scattered in the air.

The nine dragon phantoms of nine dragons protection killer move that coiled around Duke Long's body was barely resisting the huge pressure from the surroundings.

"Duke Long, your dominance has passed, fate Gu will belong to my Longevity Heaven! As for you, death awaits!" Bing Sai Chuan's voice spread throughout the battlefield. He could only entrap Duke Long within this short period and could not take his life, but it did not matter, he could use this to lower Heavenly Court's morale.

Sure enough, many Heavenly Court members were shaken when they saw Duke Long being trapped.

Duke Long suddenly laughed loudly: "Even if I die here, so what? You Northern Plains Gu Immortals are not afraid of death, do you think Heavenly Court members fear death?"

With just a few words, Heavenly Court's immortals cheered and their morale surged.

"We went to hibernate because of our responsibilities, it was not because we feared death."

"What a joke, would we fear death? We are members of Heavenly Court!"

"We defend the glory of humanity, we have never feared sacrifices since the Remote Antiquity Era!!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals began to counterattack, not hesitating to use their physical bodies to block the killer moves of Northern Plains Gu Immortals. Once there was a chance, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals would disregard their own bodies to attack fiercely and try to take the Northern Plains experts down together with them.

Northern Plains Gu Immortals were valiant but Heavenly Court Gu Immortals started to go crazy!

"Damn it." Bing Sai Chuan realized the situation, he had intended to lower Heavenly Court's morale, but Duke Long's words actually destroyed his plan.

Bing Sai Chuan sneered, his voice spreading throughout the battlefield once again: "Laughable! Your sacrifice is meaningless, no matter how many Gu Immortals are sacrificed on our side, they are only formed by the killer move of Red Lotus Demon Venerable, they were never alive to begin with. Using these dead people to exchange for your lives, we are definitely the ones winning here! How much foundation does your Heavenly Court have, how long can this go on?"

"Foundation?" Duke Long sneered: "We have more than enough!"

He began to retaliate.

He was unable to use his two hands but his aura started to inflate as it covered him like a sturdy wall.

Duke Long looked at Calamity Luck Altar with a gaze of disdain: "Your Longevity Heaven was founded in the Medieval Antiquity Era and it has only been about three hundred thousand years. As for our Heavenly Court? It has already been three million, eight hundred and seventy-nine thousand, six hundred and eighty-seven (3,879,687) years! Calculate it yourself, how many times longer it is compared to your Longevity Heaven! Don't try to estimate my Heavenly Court's foundation, hmph, you can never imagine it in your wildest dreams!"

"Bing Sai Chuan, take a look at the immortal graveyard and then look at your laughable phantom River of Time."

Bing Sai Chuan's expression sank but he was silent.

He did not need to look, he had all along been observing these two areas.

There were fewer and fewer Northern Plains Gu Immortals coming out from the phantom River of Time. But groups of Gu Immortals were still awakening from Heavenly Court constantly.

Heavenly Court's foundation was truly unfathomable.

Duke Long continued: "How many people can a tribe have? How many geniuses will rise from a tribe? Bing Sai Chuan, look at our Central Continent. We chose all kinds of geniuses from all the mortals in Central Continent!"

"Even if a tribe has a genius, can they truly nurture them? The tribe's blood and familial relations will become obstacles. This phenomenon of familial relations is much weaker in our sects. Moreover, the sect's competitions are more fair and transparent."

"Even if a genius appears in the family of a tribe's higher-ups, how much effort can a tribe's Gu Immortal spend to cultivate this genius junior? Gu Immortals also have many things to do and are extremely busy. But in sects, a genius junior will receive guidance from many people. From the moment they start cultivating until they become a Gu Immortal, they will receive appropriate guidance. There are many missions in sects which provide ample benefits for guiding juniors! Let me ask, how many tribes can do this?"

Duke Long's voice became louder and was filled with arrogance and pride: "Immortals of Northern Plains, you are truly courageous to dare to invade Heavenly Court! Unfortunately, your understanding is bound by your tribal system, you have really underestimated Heavenly Court's foundation!"

Bing Sai Chuan was silent.

He wanted to retort but there were no words he could say.

Because the truth was right here in full view!

There was a constant flow of Gu Immortals awakening from Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard.

Over three million years ago, Remote Antiquity Era.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable looked at the surrounding human Gu Immortals and nodded slightly: "All of Central Continent's Gu Immortals have gathered here, there are also a few friends from the other four regions."

"Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, we hurried here after receiving your call. We will listen to your instructions and teachings."

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable smiled and expressed his suggestion: "From today onwards, Central Continent will establish sects and take in disciples to impart our skills to the future generation."

"What?"

"Abolishing the clan system?"

"I had already heard of this rumor, but Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, you really want to do this?"

"Isn't this too…"

The human Gu Immortals discussed and showed reluctant expressions.

Someone tried persuading in a careful tone: "Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, you are the only rank nine Gu Immortal of the current world, if you want to establish your own clan, it will definitely be the number one super force in the whole world! Your children will inherit your glory and skills, all of our clans will definitely accept your clan's leadership."

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable shook his head slightly, he looked at the persuading Gu Immortal with a tranquil gaze: "Clan? I would like to ask you, in history, have there been any long lasting clans? Once a clan develops, the ties of blood relationship will become thin. When I had yet to be an Immortal Venerable, we fought with other variant human forces, besides our unity, it was because we made use of their internal conflicts. I want to create sects, an organization that does not rely on blood relations!"

The human Gu Immortals kept silent for a while before someone gave a forceful smile: "Lord Immortal Venerable, you are correct, once a clan dominates, it is easy for their unity to become loose. But you are different, you are the first Gu Immortal to cultivate to rank nine! There might not even be a rank nine Immortal Venerable in the future."

"As long as you are there in the clan, which member will dare to drift away? With your existence, this will be the clan with the strongest unity!"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable nodded: "You are right. But what if I am not there? How much longer can I live?"

The human Gu Immortals were dazed.

Someone said: "Lord Immortal Venerable, you are at your prime right now!"

Another person said: "We will constantly search for lifespan Gu, you will definitely be the Gu Immortal who will live the longest in history!"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable smiled, saying with a tranquil tone: "But I will still die. Who can live forever in this world?"

He shook his head and sighed, replying to himself: "No one."

The Gu Immortals were silent.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable continued: "Besides lifespan Gu, other lifespan extension methods all have flaws. But even if we gather lifespan Gu, we all know that lifespan Gu will keep on decreasing in production, isn't that so?"

The human Gu Immortals remained silent.

"This is heaven's will." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable raised his head, his gaze seemingly piercing through the cave walls, directly observing the clouds and heavens: "The way of heaven takes away surpluses while replenishing deficits, there has never been a supreme existence with eternal life! The tallest tree will suffer the greatest damage from the wind, a tall pile of sand will crumble from the rushing tides. New variant human experts will emerge to replace the old, our human race is also the same."

"I might be invincible in the world but it is only temporary, I will die one day. This involves the Heavenly Dao, Fate, as well as Rules and Regulations, they are all recorded in the <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>."

Chapter 1738: Primordial Origin Heavenly Court!

The atmosphere in the cave became increasingly repressed, a young Gu Immortal gave a forced smile: "Lord Immortal Venerable, you are only a few hundred years old now, you still have thousands of years and even more than ten thousand years of life left. Isn't it too early to consider this?"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's expression turned solemn, he looked at the young Gu Immortal with a calm gaze, the latter could not even last for a few breaths and quickly lowered his head.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable spoke with a serious tone: "He who gives no thought to far-flung problems will soon find suffering nearby. If we don't consider this early on and take precautions, after I die, all of our sacrifices will become meaningless. Our hard-earned achievements from countless battles will also crumble and disintegrate."

"Ignoring anything else, once I die, who among you will be able to take on the responsibility as leader once the variant humans retaliate?" Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable asked.

The Gu Immortals looked at each other, no one spoke.

Although humans had risen, they had relied on Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable alone. The others, no matter what ranks they were or even comparing quantity, were far from matching the variant human races.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable heaved a deep sigh: "Central Continent is too big, how many human Gu Immortals are there, and how many variant human Gu Immortals are there? What about mortals? What is the population of the entire human race and what is the population of the variant humans? Our difference is enormous."

"Even if we can rule Central Continent in our lifetimes and unite this region, what about the other four regions?"

"Currently, my strength has been exposed, variant humans are deeply aware they cannot fight me so they have already gone into hiding. We don't have any effective methods to find their accurate locations. Especially those variant human Gu Immortals' grotto-heavens and blessed lands, if they put them outside, we won't be able to notice them even if we are right in front of them."

The immortals fully understood the intention of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable now.

Even if the human race rose, it was by relying on Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable alone. And Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's lifespan was limited, he would die one day.

Moreover, even right now when he was still alive, it would be very difficult for the human race to unite Central Continent. Variant humans were too difficult to find, they could hide and still continue to thrive.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was invincible but he did not have an effective method to dig out their locations.

A certain elderly man among the Gu Immortals said with a heavy voice: "So, based on Lord Immortal Venerable's words, the way for humanity to rule in the long term is to give up our clan system and establish sects?"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable nodded solemnly: "Yes."

"How can we win against variant humans and provide a bright future for the whole of humanity? This is not possible with just me alone."

"Variant humans can hide away in the worst case scenario. Even if I am invincible, I can only lead Central Continent's humans to independence and make them gain a stable footing in the world."

"If we truly want humanity to rise, we must rely on ourselves. We must expand our population and also nurture as many Gu Immortals as we can. As long as our human race has stronger and many more Gu Immortals than the variant humans, humanity's future will be bright."

"If we use the clan system, what difference is there from the variant humans? We are already extremely behind, if we keep on using this clan system, we will never be able to surpass them."

"Establishing sects and actively looking and excavating geniuses is the only way. Not worrying about the costs and abandoning prejudices to nurture them, only then will we have the hope of surpassing these variant human races!"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable words sent the Gu Immortals into silence once again.

Many had already regained their calm, they knew Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's words were reasonable. But there were still some Gu Immortals who frowned, unable to accept this.

A Gu Immortal asked: "Can the sect system allow us to cooperate sincerely? Will we really be able to become meritocratic, does this mean there won't be internal conflict or suppression?"

"Of course not." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable shook his head: "An organization run by people will definitely have selfishness and conflict over personal gains. A clan bases its foundation on blood or marriage relations, while a sect decides based on abilities and talent, the latter is naturally more open and transparent, the limited cultivation resources will go to the more suitable people, which is more beneficial to the overall situation!"

That person opened his mouth but was unable to criticize the advantage of sects, he could only approach this from another angle: "Does this mean clans are unable to find talents? Clans also have the system of absorbing external talents through marriages or adopting children."

"You are right." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable nodded: "But how many marriages can you have? Even if you adopt many children, they will probably be ostracized and suppressed when compared to those blood related descendants of the clansmen, right?"

The human Gu Immortals finally had nothing to say.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable continued in an earnest voice: "I know that the sect system will not truly be accepted at first. We painstakingly seek the way of Gu Immortal cultivation, we paid an immeasurable price to obtain success, it is okay if we leave it to our own descendants, but a sect means that we need to give them to outsiders."

"But the truth is, establishing sects does not mean you are going to casually impart the profundities of your immortal cultivation to others. But you will be choosing geniuses, these geniuses must not only have great innate talent but also have upright moral virtues, and most importantly, they must be loyal to their sect."

"Furthermore, even if we don't have clans, will that mean your descendants cannot receive your help? Of course not. When these people enter the respective sects, they will naturally receive your care. But I hope you keep these actions quiet and not violate the sect rules openly."

"As long as we defend the sect rules, our descendants, disciples, and children will also actively abide by the sect rules. As long as we create sects and be united, I believe humanity can truly rise up in the future!"

"My influence cannot extend to the four regions far away, but in Central Continent, I hope that everyone will create sects and give up on the clan system. For the sake of humanity, I must emphasize this one point: Every Central Continent Gu Immortal needs to create or join a sect, you cannot establish a clan. Any future Gu Immortal will also follow this rule. If anyone breaks the rule, they will face judgment from me personally as well as the collective force of all other Gu Immortals!"

The human Gu Immortals did not utter a single word, when Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable showed a tough stance, they simply could not go against him.

But what made them thankful was that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable did not blindly forbid the clan system. The sect system only applied to Gu Immortals, that was to say, mortals and Gu Masters could use the clan system to continue living.

Moreover, even if Gu Immortals established sects, they could still take care of their descendants and friends.

This could be considered as Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's compromise towards reality, but this also showed his wisdom and foresight.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable continued: "As your leader, I shall set the example! I hereby take an oath that I will create sects and not clans. I will take in disciples and impart my life's learnings to them without holding back anything."

"Moreover, when I die in the future, my immortal aperture will also be contributed to be the foundation of the sect and it will not be left to my bloodline descendants."

"Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!"

"You…"

The human Gu Immortals were all shaken.

At this moment, they looked towards Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's calm expression and sensed his resolution to make sacrifices for the sake of the big picture.

If even Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was doing this, what reason did they have to not follow him?

"Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, you are correct, I will follow your orders!"

"From today onwards, we will create sects and not clans."

"The existence of Lord Immortal Venerable is truly the blessing of humanity!"

"Following lord is definitely the best decision I'll make in my life."

"Lord Immortal Venerable, I still have some things I don't understand about the sect establishment."

"Mm, do speak." Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable said.

"What kind of sect do you want to create, where should we build our sects? What rules does a sect have, what are the key factors in establishing a sect?"

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable took a deep breath: "I have already envisioned the concept of sects for a long time, this plan will involve all the possible aspects we can consider. Take me as an example, first, my sect will be named Heavenly Court…"

A long time passed.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable answered the questions of all the immortals.

They no longer had any doubts.

He then looked at the immortals: "Next, it will depend on you. I believe as long as we widely establish sects and progress, even if I die, humanity will become more prosperous, and if variant humans don't make any changes, they will definitely perish!"

"Please have faith in me!"

"Don't think that our sects are merely a concept and not reality."

"I believe as long as we go on with our plan, sects will gradually let out dazzling radiance in the long course of history. Heavenly Court and our sects will become renowned throughout the world, and we will become existences that our enemies fear!"

Three million eight hundred and seventeen thousand six hundred and eighty-seven years later.

Heavenly Court battlefield.

The fierce battle continued, Longevity Heaven, which had obtained Giant Sun's help, occupied the upper hand.

However, Heavenly Court members continued to awaken from the immortal graveyard.

"Who is it? Who has the guts to invade Heavenly Court!"

"This is the fruit of our ancestors' labor, I won't allow you to destroy it."

"Many people have given up their blood and lives, Longevity Heaven, which operates on a mere tribal system, wants to defeat Heavenly Court? Hmph, wishful thinking!"

"Longevity Heaven, you are despicable. For your personal gains, you incited an internal battle among humans?"

"Our Heavenly Court is the sacred land of humanity, the sanctuary of humanity, the rightful leader of humanity!"

"We represent the fighting spirit of humanity, it has not changed since millions of years ago!"

"I will follow Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, I will defend our Heavenly Court with my life!!"

Loud shouts resounded as old-looking, young-looking, male, and female Gu Immortals walked out of the immortal graveyard to join the battle.

Like what Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable said three million years ago, his Heavenly Court had become an enormous monster that loomed over the world.

His spirit continued to be inherited and had never changed!

Countless geniuses were found and nurtured by sects, following after the first venerable who had died long ago and upholding his spirit and ideology!

The Northern Plains Gu Immortals were incomparably valiant, but the Heavenly Court immortals were showing an aura of madness, even if they did not have their Immortal Gu, even if they perished together with the enemy, their faces did not show perplexity or fear.

Instead.

Their faces seemed to shine with brightness.

The glory of those who defended their beliefs…

It was so dazzling and brilliant!

"Why? We are clearly stronger, why are we being suppressed by Heavenly Court's momentum?!" Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth, his face turned ashen.

Chapter 1739: Heavenly Court's Sacrifice

Heavenly Court battlefield.

The battle of rank eight Gu Immortals had already become extremely tragic.

"Longevity Heaven! Your performance truly disappoints all of us!"

"Hmph, Heavenly Court's members really like to brag shamelessly, you have become used to being the leader for too long, watch now as I wipe the floor with all of you!"

"You and I both belong to the human race, our internal conflict has actually reached such a state. Northern Plains immortals, you are courageous but you don't have any beliefs."

"You will never understand our beliefs!"

Northern Plains Gu Immortals perished constantly, but the death of every Northern Plains expert was accompanied by the lives of several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

"Northern Plains! Longevity Heaven!" Duke Long was extremely furious: "Despite being equally matched, the grand Heavenly Court has actually been forced to such a miserable state… Unforgivable!"

Boom!

Duke Long suddenly raised his arms, finally breaking the sphere that trapped him.

But Calamity Luck Altar and Seven Extreme Desolation quickly responded, the three tussled continuously; the situation fell into a stalemate.

"Quick, quick!"

"Alright, the refinement path formation has finally been repaired."

"Yuan Qiong Du, it all depends on you now. We will protect you, and unless we die, no one will disturb this refinement path formation!!"

Several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals called out as they defended four directions, forming a firm defensive line.

Because Heavenly Court Gu Immortals defended selflessly, the refinement path formation was repaired and the defensive line was re-established.

Bing Sai Chuan saw this and quickly got away from Duke Long, trying to destroy Heavenly Court.

"Don't even think about it!" Duke Long gave a loud shout as he used all his strength to hold back Calamity Luck Altar and Seven Extreme Desolation without any regards to his injuries.

Bing Sai Chuan was unable to break free so he quickly mobilized his forces.

The Northern Plains immortals attacked once again, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals suffered heavy casualties, but with Gu Immortals constantly awakening from the immortal graveyard and filling up the gaps, the defensive line instead became more firm than before.

"Good, now is the time! Eh?!" Liu Liu Liu wanted to quietly sneak in, but his expression soon changed as his concealment was gone and his true body was revealed.

A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, with a large amount of jade pearls floating around him, flew towards him with killing intent: "You are the one? The culprit who is stained with the blood of many of my Heavenly Court friends! Your crimes shall end here."

"Is that Senior Yu Zhu Zi…" Yuan Qiong Du who was just about to enter the formation saw this scene by chance and was extremely happy.

In history, rank eight Gu Immortal Yu Zhu Zi was most proficient at exposing concealment. From the amount of jade pearls floating around him, he no doubt had most of his Immortal Gu. As such, Liu Liu Liu was restrained by him.

"We can win! With so many Heavenly Court seniors here, we can definitely win!"

"No, more accurately saying, victory will inevitably and naturally belong to my Heavenly Court!!"

Yuan Qiong Du's eyes flashed with resolution.

He entered the Gu formation once again and had just taken control of it when he pleasantly discovered this refinement path formation was much superior than the previous one.

"So that's it."

"To restore fate Gu, our seniors have added in so many Immortal Gu…"

Tears appeared in Yuan Qiong Du's eyes.

The more Immortal Gu used in this refinement path formation, the fewer Immortal Gu the Gu Immortals would have, they were more likely to die in the battlefield.

This was their sacrifice!

A willing sacrifice.

"I need to continue repairing fate Gu!" Yuan Qiong Du sat cross-legged, his expression was tranquil, but a fire was burning in his heart.

It was blazing!

A deep memory surfaced within the fire.

His master was standing before him: "Little Du, you are sleeping at the back of the mountain again. It is not good if you are so lazy all the time!"

The young Yuan Qiong Du woke up with a resentful expression: "Master!"

He mumbled and said angrily: "Master, why don't you transfer me back? I like fire path, a true man should choose fire path!"

"But Little Du, your talent in refinement path is extremely shocking, so master made you cultivate refinement path. In comparison, your fire path talent is too ordinary."

"But I like fire path, it looks so cool and awesome in fights…. As for refinement path, I have to constantly stay in a secret room and endlessly refine Gu. Not to mention there is high cost, Gu refinement fails frequently and all the effort will be wasted. More importantly, there is a huge danger in refining Gu just like in battle. Rather than dying from depression from refining Gu, I would rather use fire path and die grandly in the battlefield!"

His master sighed helplessly and said in a serious tone: "Little Du, you have to choose refinement path not because you like it but because it is your responsibility. Our refinement path faction really needs a genius like you to invigorate it! Don't let your temperament get the better of you, Little Du. You are already a man, you should accept your responsibility, understood?"

Young Yuan Qiong Du flung his head back indignantly: "Tsk, understood. If this is master's order, I will obey it."

His master sighed again: "It is not an order, it is your responsibility. Moreover, cultivating refinement path is quite delightful as well, you will feel this delight one day. So, take on the responsibility and refine Gu happily."

"How can that ever happen?!"

…

"The lazy me has never experienced a moment when such a heavy responsibility weighs down on my shoulders."

"Right."

"There is also another feeling — joy."

"Hehehehe, hahaha." Yuan Qiong Du curled his lips up as he laughed in his head.

Tears were overflowing on his face.

"Master, I finally understand your words!"

"Your disciple did not disappoint you in the end!"

"There is simply no need to divert my attention to protect myself with these comrades here, I do not need to worry."

"Let's make a push for it! When fate Gu is completely repaired, I will have completed my responsibility and will not have let down everyone's expectations. After that… I shall happily embrace death."

Yuan Qiong Du smiled as he activated a forbidden move. Once this move was used, whether the Gu refinement succeeds or fails, his death would be certain.

But so what if that was the case?

Some things were much more important than an individual's life!

Hidden Dragon Cave battlefield.

Four Eastern Sea Gu Immortals were surrounding Dragon Palace and attacking madly.

The Four Dragon Generals were suppressed and could only rely on Dragon Palace to defend themselves.

"It seems that becoming a dragonman is not without a cost!"

"Come out, didn't you want to trap us? Now, you are hiding inside the Immortal Gu House? A bunch of cowards!"

"You really underestimated us."

Song Qi Yuan, Qing Yue An and the rest were furious as they activated powerful killer moves one after the other, firmly suppressing the other side.

Even a kind person gets angry at times, let alone these four Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals. Duke Long's scheme and the betrayal of Zhang Yin's group thoroughly infuriated them, they erupted with an extremely powerful battle strength!

When comparing the temperament of people in the five regions, Eastern Sea was the most gentle and compromising.

But such an unmoving and calm sea also had the side of torrential waves and tsunamis.

When Eastern Sea people were truly angered, their enemies would comprehend what terror truly was.

Suddenly, the attacks of Song Qi Yuan's group slowed down.

"Someone is here!"

"Who is it?"

"It is clearly Heavenly Court's reinforcements!"

Song Qi Yuan's group of four quickly changed their tactics, two continued to attack Dragon Palace while the other two flew out to fight off enemy reinforcements.

"I can only send you all here." An old Heavenly Court Gu Immortal smiled as his body turned into light specks and dissipated.

His lifespan was exhausted.

"Qin Song, you can go peacefully. It is our turn now!" These were a number of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals that were carefully chosen by Fairy Zi Wei.

"Laughable, coming over so eagerly, you old timers want us to observe your deaths?" Hua Cai Yun and Shen Cong Sheng charged forward.

"Eastern Sea scoundrels, don't even dream about getting Dragon Palace!"

"Old timer who has a leg in his coffin already, why don't you just die obediently?!"

Boom boom boom!

Both sides fought immediately.

Infallible blessed land battlefield.

"Roar—!"

Countless dragon roars resounded throughout the whole battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Ghost Sword Dragon!

This compound killer move that comprised ancient sword dragon transformation, myriad self, yama child, emperor yama, and familiar face, was activated once again.

"He is Fang Yuan!!"

"Quick, protect the formation, we can't let him succeed."

"Fang Yuan, you have such guts!"

Fang Yuan sneered: "You want to stop me now? Too late!"

Thanks to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's attack that had attracted the attention of Central Continent's Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan was able to activate his killer move smoothly.

Myriad ghost sword dragon was extraordinary, not only did it have huge power, it was also difficult to get rid of. After all, this move expended Fang Yuan's soul path dao marks, it was similar to Wu Yong's unlimited wind.

The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation might be powerful but its inner core was still weak, after Fang Yuan's countless ghost dragons wreaked havoc, it was already showing signs of collapsing.

Fang Yuan turned into emperor yama, myriad dragons roared around him and his cold eyes looked at the Central Continent Gu Immortals who were helpless to do anything. The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation started to crumble at its core, from inside to outside.

The formation's collapse inflicted powerful backlash to the Central Continent Gu Immortals; without Fang Yuan having to attack, many were heavily injured and on the verge of dying.

"Fang Yuan really succeeded." Wu Yong mumbled with a complicated expression.

"Quick, attack them!" Yao Huang shouted, his aged and listless attitude was gone as he led the charge heroically.

"Let me deal with Prince Feng Xian, all of you leave."

Hairy Foot Mountain, the location of Infallible blessed land, was exposed.

"You want to repair fate Gu, hmph, wishful thinking! Although it is a slight pity to destroy Infallible blessed land, let's end this here." Fang Yuan laughed malevolently as he pointed like an emperor, countless sword dragons charged down like his fearless soldiers!

"With me here, don't even think about it, Fang Yuan!" At the crucial moment, a figure appeared and blocked the countless ghost dragons.

Rank eight fire path expert — Li Huang!

Immortal killer move — Verdant Sun Flame Cloak!

Countless ghost dragons were filled with drunkenness before they even neared and combusted spontaneously.

"With me, Li Huang, here, none of you shall move forward!" Li Huang shouted.

"Is that so… then I will let you have a taste of the consecutive move of myriad ghost sword dragon." Fang Yuan's eyes shined with cold light.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Fusion Ghost Dragon Sword!

Within a few breaths of time, countless ghost dragons gathered into one, forming an enormous pitch-black dragon marked soul sword!

The soul sword floated in the air, its tip was pointing towards Li Huang but it did not move.

Immortal killer move — Luo Po Seal!

Fang Yuan struck the soul sword with Luo Po seal.

At the next moment, the soul sword quickly stabbed forward.

Li Huang hesitated for a moment, the soul sword's speed was astonishing but he could still dodge with his speed.

But right now, he could not dodge! He had to face it head-on!

The soul sword quietly pierced through Li Huang.

The flames subsided, Li Huang's face became as pale as a dead man's. His eyes were wide open in disbelief, his body collapsed like a kite with its string cut.

"You dared to face the combined power of both my moves? It was a valiant effort but you could not be any more foolish." Fang Yuan glanced indifferently.

Li Huang was dead.

Chapter 1740: Karma Relocation

"Lord Li Huang!!!"

"Oh heavens, how could this happen?"

"Good job!"

In Infallible blessed land battlefield, Li Huang's corpse fell, shocking countless people.

Fang Yuan laughed malevolently as he continued to charge towards Hairy Foot Mountain while projecting his icy voice throughout the whole battlefield: "Anyone who dares to block me will face this ending!"

In an instant, his awe-inspiring demonic might shocked everyone, Central Continent's morale fell greatly, a dark light flashed past Wu Yong's eyes, while Yao Huang's group was greatly stunned.

Chu Du's expression was slightly complicated. Back when Fang Yuan was undergoing tribulation while rank six, he had fought with Fang Yuan.

Who could have thought that in just a few years, Fang Yuan had already become a person whom he had to look up to!

"Counting the first time I used myriad ghost sword dragon, this time's myriad sword ghost dragon usage as well as myriad fusion ghost dragon sword, about ten thousand of my soul path dao marks have been expended!"

Fang Yuan analyzed in his head.

Myriad ghost sword dragon was powerful, but it permanently expended Fang Yuan's soul path dao marks.

One activation of myriad ghost sword dragon expended four thousand soul path dao marks. After killing Li Huang, Fang Yuan's soul path dao marks had been shaved off by ten thousand.

Naturally, Fang Yuan did not have so many soul path dao marks yet, he was substituting them with transformation path dao marks.

In short, myriad fusion ghost dragon sword was a powerful move that could kill Li Huang who possessed verdant sun flame cloak, but the cost was extremely high as well.

The significance of dao marks was obvious to a Gu Immortal.

Permanently expending dao marks was directly reducing one's foundation, it could not be used easily unless absolutely necessary.

Moreover, this move had a flaw, the soul sword's speed was not outstanding and could be dodged easily.

Fang Yuan knew that Li Huang was protecting Hairy Foot Mountain and could not casually dodge the attack, so he used this move.

"Hairy Foot Mountain…"

Looking at Hairy Foot Mountain that was getting closer in his vision, Fang Yuan gave a moved sigh.

Who could have thought the majestic and renowned Infallible blessed land would be on Hairy Foot Mountain. From the outside, this mountain was extremely ordinary, it was like an inconspicuous hill.

But in truth, it was one of the most important areas to Heavenly Court in order to repair fate Gu, and now had become an area to determine victory or defeat in this arduous battle.

"Fang Yuan!!" At the next moment, another figure appeared and blocked Fang Yuan's path.

It was Chen Yi!

"Wu Yong did not kill you, then let me end your life instead." Fang Yuan called out as he prepared myriad fusion ghost dragon sword once again.

Chen Yi's face turned solemn.

Even Li Huang had perished, he did not have any confidence in facing myriad fusion ghost dragon sword.

"Hmm? This is!" At the crucial moment, Chen Yi suddenly felt his chest burning as if a hot iron was pressed on his flesh.

A powerful and mysterious force circulated and permeated his body.

Following the surging of this strength, Chen Yi's clothes were ripped apart, revealing his chest.

There was a painting on his chest, the painting of a tall tree wavering in the wind!

"Ahhh!" Chen Yi cried out in shock: "Isn't this painting the one which was engraved on my body when I inherited Genesis Lotus' true inheritance many years ago?"

At the same time, information was directly transmitted to his mind.

"This is Lord Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's arrangement!"

Chen Yi was surprised and happy, he quickly activated the strongest ability according to this information.

Immortal killer move — Karma Divine Tree!

Immediately, green smoke rose from Chen Yi's body.

The smoke gathered six feet above his head, gradually slowing down to a stop and circulating within itself, forming into the shape of a tree.

The tree was thick and sturdy with dense amounts of branches and lush leaves, and there were dozens of fruits hanging on it. But these fruits were very weird, they were in all kinds of shapes, colors and sizes. Some were like black peaches, some were pink but large like a basin, some had spikes on them, some had transparent skin, the flesh and core could be seen from the outside.

Karma divine tree formed quickly and the power within the painting transferred to karma divine tree.

Chen Yi seemed to have heard Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's voice: "Look closely, this is the consecutive move built upon karma divine tree — Karma Relocation!"

The killer move activated, as if intense winds were blowing, the green smoke flickered as karma divine tree started to sway and dance in the wind.

Myriad fusion ghost dragon sword attacked like a meteoric thunderbolt.

But just when it neared karma divine tree, with a whoosh, myriad fusion ghost dragon sword suddenly disappeared.

"What?!" Fang Yuan was shocked.

At that instant, he sensed that his connection to his killer move myriad fusion ghost dragon sword became negligible, as if myriad fusion ghost dragon sword was suddenly worlds apart from him!

"What method is this? It seems like instant transportation?" Fang Yuan immediately narrowed his eyes as sharp light flashed past them.

The connection between immortal killer moves and Gu Immortals had a certain limit in range. When it surpassed this limit, the immortal killer move would usually break apart.

Fang Yuan's myriad fusion ghost dragon sword was based on the killer move myriad ghost sword dragon and carried the trait of enslavement path, thus he could still maintain a trace of connection even if it was teleported over ten thousand li away.

But this connection was extremely faint, if it surpassed this distance even a little, the killer move would collapse by itself.

If that happened, Fang Yuan would suffer the backlash of killer move failure.

Myriad fusion ghost dragon sword was so powerful, its backlash absolutely would not be weak and would definitely make him cough out blood.

"It can forcibly teleport killer moves?" Wu Yong obtained the information from Fang Yuan: "Then let me see how you deal with my farewell friend wind."

Wu Yong sneered.

His figure appeared behind Chen Yi.

Immortal killer move — Farewell Friend Wind!

But Wu Yong had just touched Chen Yi's shoulder when his vision changed.

In an instant, he was teleported away from Infallible blessed land, returning to Southern Border.

"This?!" Wu Yong was dumbfounded as he stood at the peak of the mountain.

Soon afterwards, he came to his senses, his face was extremely dark as he quickly sent the information.

"Even rank eight Gu Immortals can be forcibly sent away?!"

"What killer move is this?"

"Karma divine tree still had such a mysterious ability?"

The Southern Border and Northern Plains immortals were shaken while Central Continent's morale rose again.

"We will continue defending like this!" Chen Yi was exulted but Fang Yuan's voice made him solemn once more.

Fang Yuan shouted: "I found it! His teleportation ability seems to be unstoppable but there is a limit in the amount of times he can use it. Because after using it twice, two fruits were consumed!"

"It was discovered so quickly?" Chen Yi smiled bitterly.

"Let me try!" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu flew over, his body shook slightly as he split into countless clones and charged forward like a giant wave.

This was a classic enslavement path battle tactic, a battle of attrition style.

Karma divine tree swayed with the wind, a fruit suddenly disappeared.

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body disappeared, Fang Yuan's group received his message shortly afterwards — he was teleported to Eastern Sea!

The immortals were in a clamor.

Fang Yuan sank into deep thought: 'This time, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's main body was directly teleported away, the enslavement path battle tactic has failed. According to conventional reasoning, shouldn't it be teleporting each clone? It actually directly affected the main body?!"

This time, Yao Huang's group charged over.

"Slow down, Brother Chu, you guys attack first." Fang Yuan instructed.

Chu Du attacked, he used a long range attack on Chen Yi but he quickly disappeared on the spot.

He was teleported back to Northern Plains, ending up in the northern icy plain.

Moreover because the distance was too long, he lost connection with the killer move he used, the killer move broke apart and he suffered the backlash.

Several people attacked next but they were all teleported away.

Fang Yuan suddenly came to a realization: "It seems that my main body is not influenced by this killer move because I am a complete otherworldly demon?"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan started a fierce wave of offense.

However, karma divine tree might be unable to influence him but it could affect his killer moves.

Fang Yuan's methods were all teleported away, the range was either far or short, some were teleported to some place in Central Continent, some were sent to other four regions, and some were even teleported to black heaven and white heaven.

Naturally, Chen Yi also did not have a good time.

It did not take long before he began to bleed from his seven orifices and his face was getting increasingly pale.

The burden to sustain such a wondrous killer move was clearly huge.

"Damn it, Hairy Foot Mountain is clearly in front of us, but because of Chen Yi alone…" Yao Huang clenched his teeth in helplessness.

Qing Ye and the rest quickly arrived and fought against the Northern Plains and Southern Border immortals.

Fang Yuan dodged the attack of Wind Sweeping Building and sent many myriad ghost sword dragons to attack Chen Yi.

Karma divine tree was constantly shaking, countless myriad ghost sword dragons disappeared, teleported to random locations.

It was okay for those that were teleported nearby, but those that were teleported far away broke apart immediately, inflicting backlash on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt that this situation was troublesome!

"Weak killer moves cannot expend karma divine tree's fruits even if they are teleported away. A strong killer move can expend one fruit but if it is teleported beyond the distance I can control, I will have to endure the backlash and might even be heavily injured if I am unlucky."

Fang Yuan did not dare to use myriad fusion ghost dragon sword.

He currently did not have winter coat or reverse flow protection seal to rely on, his defensive methods were weaker than Li Huang's. If myriad fusion ghost dragon sword failed, he would be in great trouble from the backlash.

Fang Yuan's luck was quite good as the previous myriad fusion ghost dragon sword did not inflict backlash on him.

"What do I do now?" Fang Yuan was anxious.

Bing Sai Chuan had been transmitting the situation in Heavenly Court to him, Fang Yuan knew that the repair of fate Gu had started again.

"This is a wood path method, I don't have much attainment in this path and won't be able to decipher it within a short period of time."

"Looks like I can only use a crude method, we will compete in a battle of attrition! Bai Ning Bing, you all can go ahead and fight now!"

Fang Yuan's eyes shined sharply as he sent the command resolutely.

Bai Ning Bing and other rank seven Gu Immortals charged towards Hairy Foot Mountain.

Karma divine tree activated, every time it teleported a rank seven Gu Immortal, a fruit was expended.

"Fang Yuan actually found the best countermeasure so quickly." Chen Yi felt anxious, his eyes were filled with blood and he was in a very weak condition.

A large number of rank seven Gu Immortals were teleported away, finally, karma divine tree's fruits were all spent.

Karma divine tree without any fruits faded away with the wind.

Chen Yi lowered his head, his aura had fallen to an extreme point of weakness.

"You dare to block my way, die!" Fang Yuan charged fiercely.

Chapter 1741: War Banner of Humanity!

Fang Yuan's charge was fatally ferocious and he was using myriad fusion ghost dragon sword, which raised his demonic might to another level.

Chen Yi looked at the sky as Fang Yuan approached with such momentum, his entire body shivered as he felt like the sky itself was falling towards him, it was unstoppable and unavoidable!

"In that case, there is no need to block it or evade it." Chen Yi who was already a spent force, had his chest standing firm as he faced his death nonchalantly.

"Lord Chen Yi!" Bai Cang Shui and other Gu Immortals shouted, wanting to come over to rescue him.

But Chi Qu You, Yi Hao Fang and others followed behind Fang Yuan and quickly blocked these reinforcements.

The enormous soul sword pierced through Chen Yi's body and struck Hairy Foot Mountain with its remaining force.

At the next moment, Hairy Foot Mountain disintegrated while Chen Yi's corpse fell powerlessly.

"Chen Yi is also dead!" The Southern Border and Northern Plains immortals were shaken.

Fang Yuan had successively killed two Heavenly Court experts, his demonic might was now ingrained in people's minds.

However.

"Hairy Foot Mountain is destroyed but Infallible blessed land is still standing!" Fang Yuan frowned as he looked at the pile of mountain rubble under him.

Heavenly Court had detected the precise location of Infallible blessed land but had never invaded it in their countless years of existence, instead they used human path methods to borrow the strength of Infallible blessed land and draw out success dao marks.

At this urgent moment, Fang Yuan was unable to damage Infallible blessed land, let alone destroy it.

Not long after Chen Yi died, another Gu Immortal died in Heavenly Court as well.

Yuan Qiong Du!

He was sitting cross-legged on the ground, dying with a smile on his face.

Following his death, Heaven Overseeing Tower's peak began to let out a vigorous aura.

"This is a rank nine Immortal Gu's aura."

"Fate Gu!!"

"Fried Yuan Qiong Du sacrificed himself..."

"Does this mean?!"

This aura's appearance froze the whole of the Heavenly Court battlefield. Longevity Heaven's members' expression changed greatly while the Heavenly Court immortals' eyes shined brightly and their faces were filled with joy.

"Damn it! We failed?" Bing Sai Chuan clenched his teeth: "Retreat!"

Seven Extreme Desolation remained behind as Calamity Luck Altar began to retreat.

"What's going on? Why do I have this feeling of emptiness?" In Infallible blessed land battlefield, Fang Yuan immediately felt something.

"Hahaha!" Duke Long laughed heartily, he did not obstruct Calamity Luck Altar.

He arrived inside Heaven Overseeing Tower and moved to the peak.

"Fate Gu, fate Gu..." Duke Long mumbled as tears flowed down his eyes.

He was too happy, too excited.

He was personally looking at a complete fate Gu right in front of his very eyes!

Many years of anticipation and desire, many years of longing had finally come to fruition at this moment!

The meaning behind repairing fate Gu was much more important and complicated to Duke Long than the other Heavenly Court members.

Because back then, it was his own disciple who had injured fate Gu!

"Hong Ting, master has atoned for your mistake. I did not let down Heavenly Court, I did not let down humanity! Hahaha, hahaha!"

Duke Long's loud voice resounded in Heavenly Court from the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower — "After over a million years! Heavenly Court has regained a complete rank nine fate Gu once again!"

Swoosh!

At the next moment, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals shouted in joy, some were red from their excitement, some cried, and some passed away in full satisfaction.

Heavenly Court's morale surged to an extreme point, while Longevity Heaven's Bing Sai Chuan and others were pale as they quickly retreated.

The die was cast!

There was nothing they could do now!

Longevity Heaven was decisive in invading Heavenly Court and was also decisive in retreating.

Over three million years ago.

Central Continent, Qi Breath Peak.

This peak was not a mountain, or more accurately speaking, it was only a mountain peak.

The peak contained a dense amount of qi path dao marks, it was extremely mystical. The peak could breathe out air just like the breathing of a human.

Every few decades or centuries, it would fly away and move to other places, continuing to breathe different air and then continuing this cycle.

Qi Breath Peaks were few in number, most had owners, and so did this Qi Breath Peak.

Its owner was Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, but right now, he was only a rank seven Gu Immortal.

Gu Immortal Primordial Origin was cultivating in Qi Breath Peak, using the ability of Qi Breath Peak to breathe in different kinds of qi and comprehend the profundities of qi path.

On this day, he slowly opened his eyes within a secret cave.

A mortal Gu Master had barged into his Qi Breath Peak.

He was slightly surprised.

He was a person who fully concentrated on cultivation, he was free and unrestrained. He only wanted to comprehend the Great Dao and did not want to be disturbed by external affairs. Thus, he had set up many arrangements not only on Qi Breath Peak but also around the surrounding mountains.

Not to mention mortal Gu Masters, even if many Gu Immortals came here, they might not be able to find his existence. They might even turn a blind eye to the mystical Qi Breath Peak.

"A mortal Gu Master has actually barged in today... interesting, interesting."

Primordial Origin felt interested and appeared in front of this Gu Master. But before he even spoke, that mortal Gu Master kowtowed: "Gu Master Yu Ji pays respects to Immortal Primordial Origin!"

"Oh? You actually know my name? Speak, who instructed you and helped you to pass through my obstacles with just a Gu Master's ability?" Primordial Origin immediately turned solemn.

How could a mortal Gu Master possess such an ability, he firmly believed that there was definitely a Gu Immortal helping the Gu Master.

But Gu Master Yu Ji shook his head: "Immortal Primordial Origin, I did not receive any Gu Immortal's help, but relied on the guidance of fate Gu."

"Fate Gu? Hmph, don't talk nonsense. This Gu is a rank nine Gu, it is protected in the Rockman Imperial Court and is watched by multiple rank eight rockman Gu Immortals all year round, you..." Primordial Origin had yet to finish speaking when his eyes suddenly opened wide.

The mortal Gu Master Yu Ji presented a Gu worm with both hands.

Rank nine aura overflowed, what else could it be but fate Gu?

Primordial Origin was instantly taken aback, his tranquil heart was greatly disturbed. He forced himself to remain calm: "Yu Ji, stand up, how did you steal this fate Gu and how did you bring this Gu here from such a faraway place?"

"Also, you said you received fate Gu's guidance? But according to what I know, no Gu Immortal can use fate Gu, only the Heavenly Dao can use this Gu. How can you have the ability to use fate Gu?"

Yu Ji spoke in detail: "I am a slave of the beloved grandson of the first supreme elder in the rockman tribe. I had been secretly working in place of master to clean the Rockman Sacred Hall and maintain the cleanliness of fate Gu's surroundings. I forgot which day it was, but I discovered that as long as I got near to fate Gu, I could sense fate's arrangements and the path of every living being's life."

"I received fate Gu's guidance like this and learned of many future events and also realized my mission. Afterwards, when featherman Gu Immortals infiltrated Rockman Sacred Hall and were discovered, I took fate Gu away amidst the chaos, I escaped using a hidden tunnel in the Rockman Sacred Hall."

"I had fate Gu but it restrained its aura by its own will. Although there were many dangers in my journey, be they Gu Immortals or any methods that obstructed me, I had ample time to prepare and successfully escape after receiving fate Gu's premonitions. Thus, there were dangerous situations in my journey but never fatal threats, eventually, I made my way here."

Primordial Origin could not help but evaluate Gu Master Yu Ji internally after hearing all this.

Yu Ji spoke lightly but looking at his scars, it was clear he had faced a lot of difficulties and suffering on this journey.

"You don't need to be modest, although you had the help of fate Gu, it is your bravery and planning that allowed you to achieve all these as a mortal Gu Master!" Primordial Origin praised, his expression became warm.

He asked again: "So why did you steal fate Gu and travel so far to bring it to me?"

Yu Ji said: "It was not I who stole fate Gu but fate Gu itself wanted to be brought to you. Lord immortal, you are fate Gu's master, I have already seen it through fate Gu. Not only this, lord immortal, you are... hmm, you should experience this personally."

Yu Ji then lowered his head while raising his hands, offering fate Gu to Primordial Origin.

Primordial Origin was not fully convinced, but the moment he held fate Gu, countless images flashed past his eyes and endless information was transmitted to his mind.

He immediately understood, everything was clear now!

"So it was not Yu Ji who could use fate Gu, but fate Gu itself let him see the changes in the world and the path of all beings' lives."

"According to fate, variant human races, who have been dominating the five regions, will decline. Humanity will replace them to become the leading figures of the world, we will trample on every variant human race and become the new overlord of the world!"

"Humanity will reign supreme!"

"And myself, as well as this Gu Master Yu Ji, will lead the rise of the human race, we will be the crucial characters to take on the challenges of variant human experts and suppress the situation."

After understanding everything, Primordial Origin was shaken as well as happy.

He could not help but feel happiness!

Because he was a member of the human race.

Although he had become a Gu Immortal, the status of humans was very low. Most humans were slaves sold and bought wantonly by variant humans, they were humiliated and oppressed.

Not only human mortals and Gu Masters, even human Gu Immortals had low status in the Gu Immortal world. Many human Gu Immortals were even slaves of variant humans!

Human Gu Immortals like Primordial Origin who lived freely might be besieged by many variant human Gu Immortals any day. If they were unlucky enough to be taken as a prisoner, they might become slaves of the variant humans!

"I really wanted to resist them but even after becoming a rank seven Gu Immortal, I cannot match the battle strength of many variant human Gu Immortals. That's why I had been cultivating endlessly and wanted to create a path that belonged solely to us humans."

"Now that fate Gu has shown me the way, the future belongs to us humans. I will even become the leader of the human Gu Immortals in the future, I will create qi path and lead humanity to prosperity!"

"Humanity will reign supreme!"

"This is heaven's will! This is the trend of the future! This is the heart of the people!"

Primordial Origin was extremely excited as he laughed loudly while holding fate Gu.

He was so happy that tears fell.

Yu Ji also grinned happily, he was also a human after all.

Humanity had been oppressed and suffered under the hands of variant human races for too long!

After taking a long breath, Primordial Origin calmed his feelings and took a deep look at fate Gu: "Yu Ji, you are a hero of our human race! A great hero!"

"You brought fate Gu to me, even though we cannot activate it at will, this is the greatest banner we can hold. I won't hide it from you, I already had thoughts of resisting the variant humans, but there are too few of us human Gu Immortals, and even more troubling is that many human Gu Immortals are slaves, they are treated like ants with not even a bit of respect and they also do not dare to offend their masters. Because they know how tiny they are when compared to the variant humans, they know how weak we humans are!"

"But now, with this fate Gu, we can show the world, we can let every human Gu Immortal know — The future belongs to us, humanity will reign supreme!!"

"Fate Gu will summon their lost courage, ignite their hope, and spur on their fighting spirit to resist! Moreover, we can unite all of the humans with this."

"This is a banner!"

"This is the war banner of humanity to rise and rule the world!"

Chapter 1742: Fate Vanquish

Inside Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Duke Long softly caressed fate Gu with tears silently flowing down his face.

Fate Gu looked like a spider, colored in black and white. Its aura had been weak, there was a scarlet wound on its body that almost cut it in two. This was the injury caused by Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

But now!

The scarlet wound was gone without a trace, the complete and intact fate Gu was lying down quietly with a vigorous aura.

Life or death is decreed by fate, success or failure is up to heaven!

All things in the world followed their own fixed trail which could not be changed.

This was fate.

Fate Gu was a representation of many things in Heavenly Court.

Relying on fate Gu, they changed the hearts of the people, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable led humanity to rise up, he established Heavenly Court!

Relying on fate Gu, Star Constellation made arrangements and Heavenly Court resisted three Demon Venerables!

Relying on fate Gu, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable inherited his predecessors' ambitions and progressed, Heavenly Court continued to hold onto the throne of the number one Gu Immortal force in the world!

Fate Gu was not just a rank nine Gu to Heavenly Court, it was the spirit and banner that had always throbbed in the hearts of countless generations of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals!

"So many years, after so many years…" Duke Long mumbled.

The turbulent waves in his heart gradually calmed down.

Duke Long's body no longer trembled from agitation, as if he was released from a heavy burden.

Indeed, he felt released from a heavy burden!

Differing from most Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, repairing fate Gu had much deeper meaning to Duke Long.

Because the one who injured fate Gu was none other than his proudest disciple!

In other words, he was one of the culprits who injured fate Gu!

All these years, Duke Long blamed himself for this. To repair fate Gu and repent for his sins, he did not hesitate in sacrificing his own life by activating heavenly dragon's last stand.

Even when he was hibernating, he had been uneasy and terrified.

"Can I really succeed in repairing fate Gu?"

"I must succeed in repairing it, I must!"

"Otherwise, how can I face the other two dukes, how can I face the common people, how can I face the later generations of Heavenly Court members, how I face the whole of humanity?!"

This was the voice that lingered in Duke Long's mind every day.

And now, he had finally accomplished it!

"It was not just because of me, this was the accomplishment of all my comrades! All our sacrifices were worth it." Duke Long smiled in satisfaction.

Right now, his hair was disheveled and his dragon horns were already broken, his whole body was bathed in blood.

His injuries were extremely severe but the more terrifying thing was that his lifespan was at its end.

He was about to die completely without leaving behind even a trace of his soul.

At the final moment of his life, although it was not his most blissful moment, it was absolutely his most free and relaxed moment.

So naturally, he felt fatigue.

Tired.

Too tired.

Both his body and mind were exhausted.

The torment and burden he had endured all these years was entirely let go of, the intense battle as well as his injuries made him extremely tired.

"I really want to rest well." Duke Long's breathing slowed down, his dragon eyes were like the sea which contained incomparably complex and profound emotions.

He slowly took back his hand and gave one last look at fate Gu before slowly turning around.

His gaze moved past Heaven Overseeing Tower and swept through the battlefield.

Although the battle was still going on intensely, Calamity Luck Altar had already retreated far away.

"It is time to end everything, this battle…" Duke Long took a deep breath and spoke loudly, his voice spreading throughout the whole Heavenly Court: "Longevity Heaven, you want to leave so easily? Hehe, aren't you too naive in thinking so?"

Duke Long controlled Heaven Overseeing Tower to fly into the air.

This Immortal Gu House which was renowned throughout the world had returned to being a genuine rank nine Immortal Gu House now!

Under Heavenly Court immortals' gaze, Heaven Overseeing Tower began to let out dazzling light, as if a deity had descended upon the battlefield.

Heaven Overseeing Tower, Heaven Overseeing Tower!

It monitored the world, followed the will of heaven and upheld justice for heaven!

"This is the true Heaven Overseeing Tower!"

"It has been so long, it has finally reappeared…."

"I am really fortunate, I could see such a scene in my final moments."

Countless gazes of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals turned blurry, many of them were at the end of their lives but they had satisfied smiles on their faces.

"Retreat—!" Bing Sai Chuan's voice was so loud that it turned hoarse.

Even the valiant Longevity Heaven looked scared right now as they retreated.

"It is pointless." Duke Long said softly from inside Heaven Overseeing Tower, his squinted eyes shined with a trace of pride.

Heaven Overseeing Tower suddenly let out an intense light!

Immortal killer move — Fate Vanquish.

Light.

Light was everywhere.

White light.

Filling the world from all directions.

This was a true rank nine killer move!

An attack decreed by fate that could not be dodge no matter which method was used.

If fate wants you to lose, you will lose no matter what.

This was an unavoidable attack.

Light dispersed, the Heavenly Court immortals were all standing proudly in the battlefield, while the many past experts of Northern Plains looked shaken or in disbelief, some had bitter smiles as they disintegrated.

The phantom River of Time also slowly disappeared.

Calamity Luck Altar was in a highly ruined state, like a mortal hut that had suffered from a hurricane.

Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan, Bull Demon, and Five Elements Grandmaster were heavily injured and coughed out mouthfuls of blood.

"Leave." Bing Sai Chuan gasped as he controlled the half-damaged Calamity Luck Altar.

Yellow light shined once again in the air, this was a backup plan prepared by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable; it paved out a road to retreat.

Calamity Luck Altar entered the yellow light successfully.

"You want to leave?"

"Where can you escape to!"

Heavenly Court immortals charged together.

"Leave quickly!" Mao Li Qiu clenched its teeth, it forcibly stood up with its dying body and blocked Heavenly Court's immortals with a resolute expression.

"Everyone, please step back." Duke Long sent out the command.

Heavenly Court's immortals were surprised.

Fairy Zi Wei: "Lord Duke Long?"

Duke Long sighed: "Preserve some foundation for Heavenly Court."

The immortals were silent.

Heavenly Court had suffered a disastrous loss in this battle.

It was truly a huge ordeal.

As a result of lacking Immortal Gu, many rank eight Gu Immortals had to use their own bodies to block Longevity Heaven's attacks, as such, many were sacrificed.

In Heavenly Court's situation, because of the immortal graveyard, they had many rank eight Gu Immortals but insufficient Immortal Gu!

Duke Long still remembered how Star Constellation's will had appeared and specially instructed him to have many rank eight Gu Immortals in hibernation. There undoubtedly were deeper reasons behind this, but in this battle, too many rank eight Gu Immortals had awakened in Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard and many of them were sacrificed.

Not only were there no new rank eight Gu Immortals in hibernation, it instead caused them to lose many existing ones.

Although fate Gu was successfully restored, Duke Long still felt uneasy because of this.

"Heavenly Court has now completely restored rank nine fate Gu, including myself, who can go against us? Even if it is a rank nine venerable method, I can fight against it using Heaven Overseeing Tower. Everyone, please return to the immortal graveyard, I will call for you if the need arises." Duke Long urged.

"Since it is so…"

"Alright, with fate Gu and Lord Duke Long here, which enemy can stop us?"

"Then let's go back to hibernating."

Most of the Gu Immortals returned to the immortal graveyard, but few remained. These people were already at the end of their lifespan like Duke Long, there was not much meaning for them to hibernate again.

Duke Long left behind Fairy Zi Wei and others to clean up the battlefield and guard Heavenly Court, while he led a small group to chase after Longevity Heaven with Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Calamity Luck Altar brought the defeated forces of Longevity Heaven and escaped Heavenly Court, but so what?

Their speed could never compare to Heaven Overseeing Tower's, and furthermore, they were in Central Continent.

Duke Long wanted to retain these people, whether it be killing them or taking them as prisoners, both would showcase the awe-inspiring might of Heavenly Court and let the other four regions' Gu Immortals understand the price for offending Heavenly Court!

"What? Longevity Heaven is retreating in defeat, Heavenly Court repaired fate Gu completely?!"

"Sigh, this battle is our defeat, let's retreat."

"Escape! Heaven Overseeing Tower with fate Gu is the number one Immortal Gu House in the current world!"

"Be it Duke Long or Heaven Overseeing Tower, we are not their match."

After getting this news, the battle situation in Infallible blessed land immediately underwent a complete change.

Southern Border and Northern Plains immortals had the intentions to retreat, even Fang Yuan was the same.

He felt a huge pity regarding this but he could do nothing about it.

Except, he could not imagine that at the next moment, he saw the arrival of the devastated Calamity Luck Altar as well as the Heavenly Court forces chasing them closely.

For some reason, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had created the retreat route for Longevity Heaven above Hairy Foot Mountain and it had not been discovered by anyone.

"Good, then I will take you all out at once!" Duke Long laughed heartily.